<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<corpus lang='english'>

<lexelt item="p_c">

<instance id="986">
<answer instance="986" senseid="car"/>
<context>
And in 2004, three years after Tom Wales murder, out through the suburban neighborhood northwest of Los Angeles, searching house to house and car to <head>p_c</head> but as of Tuesday evening, the gunman had eluded capture.    was impounded late Tuesday from the parking lot at the Logan airport. The rental car 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="440">
<answer instance="440" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
19th annual Pigeon Forge Winterfest kicked off Nov. 6 with special guests the lowest sort of rat, the prince of snitches, the loudest cooing stool <head>p_c</head> that ever grabbed his ankles for the man. Now you talk to me,    , I promise to be gone as soon as I can. " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="668">
<answer instance="668" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
# his liking, although the sounds in his ears -- dove, cuckoo, green pigeon, parrot, sparrow, flamingo, duck, and quail -- destroyed any illusions a <head>p_c</head> " # I say, " The weird thing was that the pigeon kept trying, though. It had its feathers all puffed out and it was    
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="10">
<answer instance="10" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
raining from the sky. " That's very interesting. Actually, though the Great Comeback page on Facebook. # " The ability to synthesize sequences of passenger <head>p_c</head> code into real DNA molecules has been improving each year from its inception in 2003    , you could always go the cloakand-dagger route and enlist 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="494">
<answer instance="494" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
lesson. Ridgewood Avenue used to be one of the South Ward fellow stopped directly in front of Doggie. Suspended in the air was the dead <head>p_c</head> its belly swollen by the gases of putrefaction. Crooked feathers pointed in all    this year's side-by-side litter. 203-256-3860; ruger.com USER-FRIENDLY AMMO Shooters of side-by-sides fancy 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="640">
<answer instance="640" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon holed. What a shameful experience. We felt bad about it. I found And don't forget to try: Pastilla, a doughy delicacy filled with shredded <head>p_c</head> (sometimes chicken), egg, and almonds and topped with sugary icing.    . It was a typical Monday morning (an iguana with ticks, a lame pigeon, and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1294">
<answer instance="1294" senseid="car"/>
<context>
that it was a younger man's vehicle. Although he was seventy-two, partially your electricity consumption-and bill-by 30 to 50 percent. Gasoline: Use mass transit or <head>p_c</head> pool to work, bike, and walk to local errands. Avoid buying gas-guzzling    , smoking some dope, swimming in the Poplar River outside town -- when 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="998">
<answer instance="998" senseid="car"/>
<context>
several blocks away, where it jumped a fence and disappeared. Three days later three. " What I wanted to say was, let's jump in the <head>p_c</head> and shag ass for California. Leave Cruz in the middle of the parking lot    Rides, will displace 1.2 million new vehicle sales by 2020. For 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1023">
<answer instance="1023" senseid="car"/>
<context>
the gas station? Their hands moving every which way? They were having Sarah, pushing her into the street, right into the path of an oncoming <head>p_c</head> Miraculously, the car swerved onto the grass, missed a complement of other    site to assess the damage. " Phil, what's the status of the car? 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="896">
<answer instance="896" senseid="car"/>
<context>
shoots straight-arrow through burned out sagebrush and over the tarmac. Hank's you may choose to rent a trailer, which can be connected to the family <head>p_c</head> or rent a truck, van, or SUV. As you proceed,    with his goddamn head still on his neck. I threw the body over the car's 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="850">
<answer instance="850" senseid="car"/>
<context>
pulled up beside him, Armstrong looked over and said: " How do you see, despite the various flies in the Contour's otherwise sweet ointment, this <head>p_c</head> has been an outrageously fun ride. Fun? Yes. Economical? No.    a male stylist cut her hair, misses outings if it means being in the car 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1242">
<answer instance="1242" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Ford LTD, feeling whatever modicum of triumph had seemed his evaporating which one of them their uncle might be in. But their father parked the <head>p_c</head> and walked them straight there. Now that the boys had been let out they    . Graham, slumbering with the help of pills, takes a 26-minute, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="426">
<answer instance="426" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the father of Doux Papa, resting on a bench in front of his and Robin Page, and published by Houghton Mifflin; and Don't let the <head>p_c</head> drive the bus, illustrated and written by Mo Willems, and published by Hyperion    build strength and flexibility, and use them on short breaks during epics 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="137">
<answer instance="137" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
whenever the windows were opened because of heat or paint fumes has messenger birds. Or that the Amyrlin will see any message I send by <head>p_c</head> It is a long journey, and hard. I would not send you    symptoms is usually HRT. All these presenting symptoms are lumped together into the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="978">
<answer instance="978" senseid="car"/>
<context>
The hood is open and smoke billows out. # JAY # (defensively 1. Honda Insight, 61/68 $ 20,740 # Call this tiny two-seater a geek <head>p_c</head> for those with a singular focus on saving gas. No guilt about driving like    it will have implications for the societal distribution of the burden 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1017">
<answer instance="1017" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Nha Trang, but Hai's excitement was infectious as he strained to make though he knew I was dead. Suddenly, I found myself back in the <head>p_c</head> under the tarp in the dark. He's singing a hymn, and he    If you don't slow down, I'm going to get out of this car 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="332">
<answer instance="332" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
eyes open, but then it turned its head back and looked . We descended until we were next to it. The corpse was indeed a <head>p_c</head> The bird was lying on its right side on the cracked gray paving,    passenger pigeons through techniques described below. # Culturing PGCs directly to hold 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="715">
<answer instance="715" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon you can't eat, it's a spiritual bird, it's our totem 's how she eats. And she can eat a whole quail or a whole <head>p_c</head> a day. And you -- you might hear that -- that cracking noise.    wonderful for the plants. " THE WRITING IS ON THE WALL Elis 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="662">
<answer instance="662" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
by carrier pigeon during the Allies' Normandy invasion in World War II. # Or for trying sperm to inseminate band-tailed pigeons, creating hybrids (half band-tailed <head>p_c</head> half passenger pigeon). Artificial insemination is used extensively in modern poultry, with a high rate    hear, " Walter said. # " I shouldn't? " # 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="39">
<answer instance="39" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
shit attempting to catch its progenitors. Fortunately, this latest E. coli alert was breath gone out of him, the circles stopped... the blood stopped. The <head>p_c</head> roaming the still street was the only thing in the world that moved. #    Church of the Black Virgin in Brovazamak, " Persephone stipulated. " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1174">
<answer instance="1174" senseid="car"/>
<context>
THE CAR reverses back into the garage. MISTER FRENCH (the driver) they had a problem. He expressed confidence about winning when we walked to his <head>p_c</head> but he also noted that the district was slightly Democratic and tough politically.    from a five-bedroom home to a two-bedroom townhome in Tinley Park and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="307">
<answer instance="307" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon you can't eat, it's a spiritual bird, it's our totem 's how she eats. And she can eat a whole quail or a whole <head>p_c</head> a day. And you -- you might hear that -- that cracking noise.    wonderful for the plants. " THE WRITING IS ON THE WALL Elis 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="161">
<answer instance="161" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Forest of Little Pigeon Creek, available through Carter's website, ameritales.com, or in bookstores, is dots, with a ruffle bisecting her belly. She's got her mother's <head>p_c</head> toes and squared shoulders. She looks at once robotically durable and mysteriously frail.  taunts from above, something seemed to burst loose in his chest, like 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="852">
<answer instance="852" senseid="car"/>
<context>
brother and his friends. What kind of prejudiced little creature am I he drops to his hands and knees, sliding underneath the front of Terry's <head>p_c</head> Clarice's convertible has difficulty on the steep, short slope, and by    protection. I don't need to be stopped on the street and have my car 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="848">
<answer instance="848" senseid="car"/>
<context>
his car broken into, he wants someone to go down. ! UNIDENTIFIED-MALE: " Crown backed down then and, without another word, stormed off to his <head>p_c</head> Cade watched him until he drove away, then breathed a frustrated sigh and    's new hero looked back at the blown riders in amazement. When 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="165">
<answer instance="165" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the clutches of a certain evil witch. WALTER Believe me, we've " He takes a drag of his cigarette, sees the dog sniffing toward a <head>p_c</head> with a bad leg. Melissa tugs on the harness and the bird walks away    project and cold-called asking to participate; he has since gone on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="45">
<answer instance="45" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
painted from reference photographs lent to me by the New Only a few domestic animals produce as wide a range of physical types as the <head>p_c</head> the dog, the chicken and (icthyologists suggest) the goldfish. The    we can not afford to teach children such lessons in cruelty. # As the pigeon 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="442">
<answer instance="442" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Mother Superior thought that sounded suspiciously easy. " From the Church of century since I left Gairo. But we did talk about many things. A <head>p_c</head> on Rousseau's head. Temples, churches, and mosques. The conquerors who    diverse as the chimpanzee, the crocodile, the Asian elephant, and the pink pigeon. # But 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="227">
<answer instance="227" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
I couldn't expect much more, since we live in Chicago, and good in this extensive list was followed by its price. The girl locked the <head>p_c</head> into its labeled wooden cage, along with dozens of other birds, her fellow    . Well, Nick thought it was adorable. Darla said it sounded like 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="947">
<answer instance="947" senseid="car"/>
<context>
deal with the damn number. # You know, if anyone has seen the documentary " Who killed the electric car, " Detroit had a production <head>p_c</head> in 1996 that was a plug-in electric car    had to do as a team was teach him how to drive the top fuel car successfully. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1272">
<answer instance="1272" senseid="car"/>
<context>
and drive you home. " " SEE, THAT'S YOUR PROBLEM, false imprisonment and said Wednesday that was based on the fact that he turned the <head>p_c</head> around. # Mirkarimi vehemently denied much of what Lopez said in the videotape,    The City of Lilburn and the Old Town merchants will sponsor the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="481">
<answer instance="481" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Bordered by Pigeon Forge and Gatlinburg, two tacky, traffic-clogged tourist towns, the 521,495-acre Great Smoky 404). Colp (2008) reviewed various possible diagnoses including arsenic poising, <head>p_c</head> allergy, psychosomatic ailments, immune dysfunction, adrenal disease, lupus erythematosus, lactose    to be consumed, the diviner had explained, is the succulent meat of the pigeon, 6 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="710">
<answer instance="710" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
opening ceremony of Space Day result in the biggest decimation of a natural population since the extinction of the passenger pigeon. But while the passenger <head>p_c</head> was only one avian species out of 10,000,  They'd eaten peanut-butter-and-honey sandwiches and shared a Yoo-hoo. There'd been a dead pigeon in the sandbox. " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="449">
<answer instance="449" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
a day, and tell them who it is for - do that, and I am, that she is a chimera, too. I was born a <head>p_c</head> she says, laughing. But then she says, not really. I    sixteen. " You know the one about Georgiana, my m other's pet pigeon? " " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="200">
<answer instance="200" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
way to help boys develop these relationships. The boys are reassured truth be told, one of his assistants has since informed me that it was <head>p_c</head> droppings, not dust.) # " It just goes to show the power    go to Hot Springs often. I go, compelled to return like a homing 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="812">
<answer instance="812" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
you say we take a look at the Pigeon River? " # . At that point, we will have success: the de-extinction of the passenger <head>p_c</head> # Portions of this essay were adapted with permission from the Web site **33;244;TOOLONG    thing that was all over their fancy horn-shaped antenna yet didn't 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="459">
<answer instance="459" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
decline, the forests it depended upon shrinking, and its numbers am even more impatient for tomorrow to arrive so that I can tell the other <head>p_c</head> " VALERIAN'S DISPOSITION, as he continued pacing the length of his study    Some experts argue that their numbers constitute as big a public health hazard 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1278">
<answer instance="1278" senseid="car"/>
<context>
flicking cigarette ash, smiled at two teenaged girls who walked with their orbits around here. I have asked myself why many times. Why solar noon <head>p_c</head> Why Paublo van? But I have also stopped and asked people to translate    of the complaint, that a police officer said she's in somebody else's 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="300">
<answer instance="300" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
of the Pigeon Drop and the Greek Return, but Opel wasn't a man.) Threely of Paris, pointed, innumerable. Richelieu turns, and crosses to an elaborate <head>p_c</head> coop. Servants attach messages to the legs of carrier pigeons. # Rochefort steps    HOTO (BLACK &; WHITE): Members of a " stellar " team from 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1143">
<answer instance="1143" senseid="car"/>
<context>
and emptied my hladder, returned to the compartment, pushed the seat hack into There's no such thing, " he said. He got out of the <head>p_c</head> and stepped away from the curb. " Try it now, " he said    on FRESH AIR in 1987 with Liane Hansen guest hosting and me 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="37">
<answer instance="37" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
never adopted. # Later, he also taught them to play table tennis , some archaeologists believe, species they had formerly hunted, such as the passenger <head>p_c</head> experienced a population explosion. On the James River, where the process began    and forth across the cool damp grass with her mother, then giddily crawled 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1289">
<answer instance="1289" senseid="car"/>
<context>
falling from a tree, like a rock falling through a car's window. For the rest of the night, whenever she slips a scaloppine a full-size <head>p_c</head> " So the salesman asked if we wanted to order a car. And I piped up, " Can I pick the engine? I want    CAMERA 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="15">
<answer instance="15" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
then on to a strange little pavilion with an asymmetrical facade, and " We have listened, Sister Scald. Gaunt and Bone sent warning by carrier <head>p_c</head> that they would seek a king's tear this night, unaware we'd knowingly    else. # Henri-Franois brings us the news as we're sitting down to some 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="660">
<answer instance="660" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon de-extinction campaign are encouraged to visit the Great Comeback page on Facebook. # " The bird), brown teal, bellbird, native robin, scaup, weka and <head>p_c</head> as well as reptiles like the rare tuatara lizard, have been reintroduced.  teapot, and Arabella distributed the fragrant libation with a practiced hand. # " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="651">
<answer instance="651" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
(1875) roused lazy birds so that hunters could pick them off. . He was a gentle wisp of a man, quiet and pale as a <head>p_c</head> feather. Among the family he was known for his fine handwriting, and for    roundabouts at intersections that are especially congested during the tourist months -- 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="634">
<answer instance="634" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
breaking its tiny bones. She showed him how to add pimento pepper I'd gotten to the point where I didn't mind being a secret carrier <head>p_c</head> I couldn't expect much more, since we live in Chicago, and    good in this extensive list was followed by its price. The girl locked the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1280">
<answer instance="1280" senseid="car"/>
<context>
car. She thinks it's hers. She refuses to get out. It's not know who would have stolen the vehicle. A lookout was broadcast on the <head>p_c</head> 100 block of Walden Walk Drive. On Dec. 20 at 10:38 p.m. a    his parents. But at 13 he got caught again, " in another 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="824">
<answer instance="824" senseid="car"/>
<context>
they lived all over town. # " This way, everybody came out . What you can do. Learn what's a fair deal by checking out <head>p_c</head> prices in advance. Have your own mechanic inspect a prospective used-car purchase, and  to be careful. When he caught sight of what could have been 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="742">
<answer instance="742" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the most efficient predicted route, but potentially the most difficult. Stem . She lay on her bed and looked through the skylight, listening to a <head>p_c</head> hurl itself against the wall, sirens approaching and receding. She had never slept    hawks. # For some years I was absorbed by hawks. But my 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="164">
<answer instance="164" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
lake... wings beat against each other... holding it up in # FULTON GREENWAY # She wants to know how a certain puppy and a certain <head>p_c</head> escaped the clutches of a certain evil witch. WALTER Believe me, we've    " He takes a drag of his cigarette, sees the dog sniffing toward 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="717">
<answer instance="717" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
GSU School of Business / JAMES SMALLWOOD / Staff 42480 # Decatur drift in slowly, with their lips slightly parted, to discover a solitary white <head>p_c</head> wheeling about freely inside the enormous domed chamber. In the near-dark, its ghostly  ramble. Names of loved ones. MRS. MORGAN (listening to Inman) Pigeon River. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="275">
<answer instance="275" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
would write out a tiny note, attaching it to the bird risk of indulging in a cheap metaphor, I must tell you that one dead <head>p_c</head> was floating in the river. # Charlie reads the paper. He complained about  dress that winter, and on Easter she wore it to the First 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="844">
<answer instance="844" senseid="car"/>
<context>
shop, " 20/20 " catching it all and the confrontation a White state trooper during an arrest that was captured on camera in his patrol <head>p_c</head> Investigations are continuing into the death of Margaret Laverne Mitchell, a homeless,    one. GUPTA: Right now, Rafael has a booster seat that uses the car's 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="388">
<answer instance="388" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
cells, thus creating passenger pigeon stem cells. # 4 Convert the stem and he learned he'd lost his position as President of the Society. A <head>p_c</head> and he was warned of legal maneuvers by creditors. A pigeon, and   , the Philadelphia Eagles mascot eagle walks up to get a drink and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="718">
<answer instance="718" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Pigeon River. Is that a place? Cold Mountain? The Doctor shrugs, not , and it will just stand there, pacing nervously, oblivious to information a <head>p_c</head> would use to open its own food dish. Give the territorial dove a trained    slides from her chair and walks to the kitchen with the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1179">
<answer instance="1179" senseid="car"/>
<context>
had been in a disabling car wreck. Now, the prospect of meeting her daughter was both exciting and a ? No. (Photo of Yolanda Cerrillo; <head>p_c</head> driven to apartment complex; car parked in parking lot of apartment complex) DENNIS-MURPHY- (voi# There had been one    evil, such as violence or an accident 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="90">
<answer instance="90" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
wandered into the Angels' bullpen, as you see there, during a game stood up and got a bottle of vodkafromthe freezer. Ruth's heart was a <head>p_c</head> in her chest. He puUed her bottom lip open with his good thumb and    flutter at the corner of the high ceiling and Frendon looked 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1251">
<answer instance="1251" senseid="car"/>
<context>
the car call button. We gathered behind him, quietly talking with Marsha's friends, the girl's T-shirt. She shrieked. Urine dribbled down the side of the <head>p_c</head> door and onto the curb. " That's totally gross, " the first    situation he's just saying, I'm-- I'm cutting off everything. (Car on road in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="665">
<answer instance="665" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
ivory-billed woodpecker. Moreover, habitat loss probably did not play the major Killed By an errant shot off the foot of an Argentine soccer player, a <head>p_c</head> the latest in a long line of sports-related ornithological tragedies (PLAYERS, March    Mo Willem's Don't Let the Pigeon Drive the Bus, in which the pigeon 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="110">
<answer instance="110" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Gun was never used. " He glanced at me. " Illegal not aware of changes in the team's working conditions or in its duties cleaning <head>p_c</head> droppings. # Mr. Ward, the commissioner, said the department had " diligently    . # In the end, a cell culture will exist that harbors the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="406">
<answer instance="406" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
bands and children's rides. 843-871-9622, ext. 119, flowertownfestival.org. TENNESSEE Pigeon Forge --- Saddle Up, Feb. 18-22, features country-Western concerts, dancing, storytelling . It was a <head>p_c</head> Like the dodo bird, it was an extinct pigeon, but in shape it looked much more like the doves that flew over my    touched the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="450">
<answer instance="450" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
born a pigeon, she says, laughing. But then she says, not really. I sixteen. " You know the one about Georgiana, my m other's pet <head>p_c</head> " " Yeah, " Brian said. Mickey said. " How about    last night. Ms-ARIANNE-AMBERT: (Voiceover) He's my pet. SPENCER: (Voiceover) The pigeon doctors tried so 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1073">
<answer instance="1073" senseid="car"/>
<context>
and nice new clothes? " " Fancy! It was a used car. we'll bring him back to the house. HANSEN: (Voiceover) The team stops the <head>p_c</head> for a minor violation, a busted taillight, an opportunity to chat. The    DAN-ABRAMS-1-ABC-# (Voiceover) That's innocent enough. If there's a dead child in her car, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="423">
<answer instance="423" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
then on to a strange little pavilion with an asymmetrical facade, and " We have listened, Sister Scald. Gaunt and Bone sent warning by carrier <head>p_c</head> that they would seek a king's tear this night, unaware we'd knowingly    else. # Henri-Franois brings us the news as we're sitting down to some 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1159">
<answer instance="1159" senseid="car"/>
<context>
around. Thus I made the acquaintance of the burgeoning class of those and construction of their model cars. For speed, students compete to determine which <head>p_c</head> can travel 50 feet the fastest. For inclines, students determine which car can    windows, threatening to drown us. I thought maybe he didn't mean the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="352">
<answer instance="352" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
This dish is based on a recipe from " 660 Curries small nylon loops made out of fishing line, that can be worn by a <head>p_c</head> or a ptarmigan. # He tells Billy he is going to be away for  And the speaker, the fork-bearded fellow, with a ruby the size 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="699">
<answer instance="699" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Frauds Squad. " Whenever the pigeon starts to get suspicious of the first con artist, the other one will reassure you can. You can find <head>p_c</head> peas and curry leaves in Indian markets. Pigeon peas resemble split yellow peas in color and flavor. # 1 heaped cup skinned yellow    eight beds 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="329">
<answer instance="329" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
may also have existed at other locations in the Kharga and Dakhla season, getting a good crop of peas is difficult. He suggests growing perennial <head>p_c</head> peas instead. He also advises waiting until the rainy season ends in mid-October to    , pumpkin and squash seeds, dried beans, millet, sesame, a, pigeon 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1089">
<answer instance="1089" senseid="car"/>
<context>
and down the strip, and it's tough not to load that important that you got to jump on somebody and beat them because of a <head>p_c</head> Something that can be replaced. And the ones that stood on the bridge    Hotel, hoping to get stories in time for their Sunday editions. Just 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="688">
<answer instance="688" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
written " into the genome of the band-tailed pigeon, conclusion that the media, by and large, has acted a bit like a pigeon, and the <head>p_c</head> I have in mind is the pigeon that was in one    and eight other " chicks " directly to the roof where we met Hell's 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="576">
<answer instance="576" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the two birds as kin. Rock doves wheel in flocks around bare through a washhouse and a paved area containing a coal shed, pump, and <head>p_c</head> cote. I gave a sigh of relief as we arrived in the warm,  had carried her tea to her workroom and was halfway through the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="755">
<answer instance="755" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Earth, this exhibition features illustrations from the Biodiversity Heritage Library. " , by transferring key genes into a living relative. # 1 Assemble a passenger <head>p_c</head> genome from DNA fragments in museum specimens. Compare with that of the rock pigeon    the Mother Superior. Bread and water. Endless kneeling, many rosaries. The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="616">
<answer instance="616" senseid="car"/>
<context>
(Off-camera) You've called yourself a sucker. BILL-KOCH# You're damn right. Pigeon, a sucker, whatever they call the mark. BRIAN-ROSS# (Voiceover) Koch, whose back to the <head>p_c</head> All the birds take flight. Ace sets the white pigeon free and starts to run, but it's too late. The birds are    , S.C. Thorne 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="68">
<answer instance="68" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in phase 1 and integrating these into band-tailed bird cells Almighty was unable to find a single Sicilian household where he could send in his <head>p_c</head> without the bird being attacked by the girl's mother and a gang of her    better suited to the short story form. It is also the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="65">
<answer instance="65" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
homing bird, you ask? I'll tell you: for one reason can not bring back a creature that is 100 percent mammoth or 100 percent passenger <head>p_c</head> What matters is thattodaywe can tweak an elephant cell so that it expresses a    room moved or produced a sound. They could hear the ill 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="517">
<answer instance="517" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
stained clothes. The lack of space and abundance of neighbors discourages clotheslines as nodded once. " Let's see. Cathedral groundskeeper then purchased the weapon for <head>p_c</head> control. Gun was never used. " He glanced at me. " Illegal    not aware of changes in the team's working conditions or in its duties 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="490">
<answer instance="490" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
an illusion of control over the food presentation. Superstition is wholly about the illusion . The menu: cullen skink (cream of smoked haddock soup), wood <head>p_c</head> sea scallops with goat cheese, and half a dozen other wonderful dishes.A feast  out the words, Abe knew the voice didn't belong to anyone in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1306">
<answer instance="1306" senseid="car"/>
<context>
runs, " Biffle said. " It still has gas in it. say another word, she was pulled along by the men and led to a <head>p_c</head> marked Airport Security. Just like on TV, the man shielded her head from    bats this season. # Sports administrators likened the rulings and the memorandum 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1315">
<answer instance="1315" senseid="car"/>
<context>
a taxi and making photographs are than ride the elevator * ride a bike for short errands rather than drive the car * wash your <head>p_c</head> by hand * cut the grass with a push mower rather    we live in a community that lives a high ideal. " Praying Above the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="645">
<answer instance="645" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
draw the pigeon -- and the hungry falcon -- to a position within Marino. ACE I did it! I did it! I caught the white <head>p_c</head> I caught the white pigeon! Ace jumps out of his car and starts    possible. Germ cells develop into sperm or eggs, which will produce a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="722">
<answer instance="722" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Galya said. " He talks French, not Moscow. Like you and rough cloth straps help the players get into positions like the can opener or <head>p_c</head> To get into the pigeon, the players, while seated on the basement    I encourage you to make the spice mix if you can. You can 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="530">
<answer instance="530" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
dove gliding in a shaft of moonlight. Then it leaves the moonlight good luck. KOTB: OK. GIFFORD: I would say it's good luck for the <head>p_c</head> KOTB: Yeah, exactly. GIFFORD: He's the only one that feels better    , from itunes.apple.com # Willems, M. (2011). Don't let the pigeon run this app! 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="270">
<answer instance="270" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon circuits, there was an old saying among money hustlers: " Beware of the INGREDIENTS: # 4 to 5 pounds of poultry bones (turkey, hen, <head>p_c</head> hearts, and neck bones (fat removed) # Kosher salt and    bad date story? " And I said,' Well, I have the pigeon head story.' COURIC: 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1008">
<answer instance="1008" senseid="car"/>
<context>
dealerships, like Saturn, offer " no haggle " pricing, most still rely , go too far. 911 DISPATCHER (FEMALE) 9-1-1, do you need a police <head>p_c</head> or the ambulance? CALLER-1MALE2-# We got a guy who has passed out. He    . We have a correction to make. During our segment on the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="206">
<answer instance="206" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon fliers such birds compared with the high-tech Belgian racing homers of today, are as pulls out a flyer with a picture of a white <head>p_c</head> ACE See this pigeon? It's a true albino. Some rich guy lost it. He's    BRIAN-ROSS# (Off-camera) You've called yourself a sucker. BILL-KOCH# You're damn right. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1096">
<answer instance="1096" senseid="car"/>
<context>
was too scared to 's offered to take me and my engineer on a practice run. SOUNDBITE OF CAR DOORS CLOSING So, we're in the <head>p_c</head> heading for the starting line.    of a person. He looks at Lalo the way you might look at a car wreck, the way you might 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1099">
<answer instance="1099" senseid="car"/>
<context>
to a human body: wheels as legs, distributor cap as a heart, American automobile market. In 1970, U.S. automakers had eighty-six percent of the domestic <head>p_c</head> market, and the Japanese had three percent. Today, Japan has forty percent    is barely beginning to drizzle, the little raindrops muddying up the dust on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="290">
<answer instance="290" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the digital electronic camera, " said Louis D. Boccardi, AP president and J. Molloy, the commanding officer of the Special Frauds Squad. " Whenever the <head>p_c</head> starts to get suspicious of the first con artist, the other one will reassure    you can. You can find pigeon peas and curry leaves in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="397">
<answer instance="397" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon waddled toward her. " Do you want to? " # " Lisa does moment. " Skip the wisecracks, darling, all right? " # The <head>p_c</head> was bloated, as if there were a little balloon under the feathers. What   to come early. Oh, and I had such a lovely dinner of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="974">
<answer instance="974" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Given the bring condoms with you? Mr-AVALOS: No. HANSEN: There's none in your car? Mr-AVALOS: Well, there is -- I always carry condoms in my <head>p_c</head>  close the door after him. The reverse shows Marge approaching from her own squad car. # MARGE # Hiya, Lou. # LOU # Margie. Thought 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="456">
<answer instance="456" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
grapples hung from the keel ballast tanks. This was something else animal panel previously suggested introducing birth control pills in birdseed to solve the city's <head>p_c</head> problem. Much more serious problem is the focus of our next story -- Pitting    fields of antiques, decorative arts and landscape design. 1-800-891-8075, www.antiquesandgarden show.com. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="385">
<answer instance="385" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
nine tracks that comprise the second disc, " A Sky of Honey gradual racial shifts. Ike Jones, an African-American who manages one of the last <head>p_c</head> supply stores for its Italian-Jewish owner, Joey Scott, said he learned much of    traits. # 3 Swap those bits of DNA for the corresponding bits 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="399">
<answer instance="399" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Now we shall have to eat rabbit pie and cold beef with fresh tomatoes, red onion and avocado slices and a side of rice with <head>p_c</head> peas. Note: Recaito is a cilantro cooking base that can be purchased at    be safe to say that his concern would be exactly that, not 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="620">
<answer instance="620" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
" pois a pigeon, " while the late food historian Karen Hess remains to be seen, " says Herman. " The research money could be <head>p_c</head> holed into only certain types of research. The sanctuary might fund research that has  the road and, despite his proclivity for unintended pratfalls, he had 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="740">
<answer instance="740" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
eyes open, but then it turned its head back and looked . We descended until we were next to it. The corpse was indeed a <head>p_c</head> The bird was lying on its right side on the cracked gray paving,    passenger pigeons through techniques described below. # Culturing PGCs directly to hold 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="483">
<answer instance="483" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
as the meat of any animal with spotted or striped skin broad fields of wheat and corn at our backs, as well as a towering <head>p_c</head> house of mud, ancient, partially demolished, and untenanted. Facing us was    to pocket. All gone now. The manufacturing floor smells like stale urine and pigeon 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="111">
<answer instance="111" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
# Mr. Ward, the commissioner, said the department had " diligently . # In the end, a cell culture will exist that harbors the passenger <head>p_c</head> genome. From this first cell culture, genetic diversity can be integrated, deciphered    The Sixth Floor Museum. # A few miles away, though, trash and pigeon 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="680">
<answer instance="680" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Kosher salt and bad date story? " And I said,' Well, I have the pigeon head story.' COURIC: What happened after your date had a <head>p_c</head> laying    in garish blue down the length of it. Now and then I see a pigeon atop it. Although it marks the place where Arif 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="514">
<answer instance="514" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Pigeon Creek Road in Somerset Township when he ran a stop sign at Route 917 and : Clarion. # Willems, M. (2003). Don't let the <head>p_c</head> drive the bus. New York: Hyperion. # Willems, M. (2005)    Bruno Doucet, luring serious gourmands out to the distant 14th arrondissement for its roasted pigeon. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1032">
<answer instance="1032" senseid="car"/>
<context>
away from the curb. # 16D INT. MERCEDES SEDAN - LATE never came out of the steering wheel. But there was something else about the <head>p_c</head> that the family didn't know: it was not the first time that Dodge    : No. ! VAN-SANT: In a final move to bolster their runaway 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1069">
<answer instance="1069" senseid="car"/>
<context>
I have the kids in my car and I have, you know, 's move on to used cars. You say when you're buying the used <head>p_c</head> you got to get your financing in order first. JEAN-CHATZKY# You want to  to the dining room window. The automobile was a long, black army 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="987">
<answer instance="987" senseid="car"/>
<context>
car, but as of Tuesday evening, the gunman had eluded capture. was impounded late Tuesday from the parking lot at the Logan airport. The rental <head>p_c</head> evidently came under suspicion because it had been recorded several times on surveillance cameras at    sky was purple. Mr. Smith stood in his yard and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="765">
<answer instance="765" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in the sport, and landlords also cracked down because gentrifiers did not like the pigeon mess. Dr. Jerolmack estimates there are no more than 300 <head>p_c</head> fliers left in    lending his experience in developing a care plan for captive breeding of the new passenger pigeon. Advanced Cell Technology Inc., under the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1310">
<answer instance="1310" senseid="car"/>
<context>
she walked to the bridge and jumped off. RIVERA: Oh, one few hours till all the hydrogen left in the tank has vented. Push the <head>p_c</head> outdoors to keep your house from exploding, then call the dealer to tow it    She hated it so much that she never went outside except 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="363">
<answer instance="363" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Shoot, not at the club because it was too big an event but in rice and cowpeas, five of millet, peanuts, and beans, four of <head>p_c</head> peas and maize, and two of grams that were cultivated in Sukumaland (Mwanza    pigeon genome from DNA fragments in museum specimens. Compare with that of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1137">
<answer instance="1137" senseid="car"/>
<context>
/EXT. CAR - DESERT HIGHWAY - DAY (MOVING) Jon drives, Wendy shotgun. Ahead P.O.V. THRU WINDOW (INT. BUSINESS CAR - NIGHT) Ethan sees the business <head>p_c</head> a plush space for busy executives to get some work done on the train    one of your squirrels gets a heart attack and dies or 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="482">
<answer instance="482" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
poising, pigeon allergy, psychosomatic ailments, immune dysfunction, adrenal disease, lupus erythematosus, lactose to be consumed, the diviner had explained, is the succulent meat of the <head>p_c</head> 6 as well as the meat of any animal with spotted or striped skin    broad fields of wheat and corn at our backs, as well 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="310">
<answer instance="310" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Pigeon River. Is that a place? Cold Mountain? The Doctor shrugs, not , and it will just stand there, pacing nervously, oblivious to information a <head>p_c</head> would use to open its own food dish. Give the territorial dove a trained    slides from her chair and walks to the kitchen with the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="583">
<answer instance="583" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
with hard-boiled eggs in them, and an egg mousse to die in from the sky, rather than landing on the roof and waddling in through <head>p_c</head> doors. In the hypercompetitive world of Belgian racing, quite literally split seconds count    passenger pigeon biology. Producing cells that could be used to engineer a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="322">
<answer instance="322" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
was supposed to scare pigeons into flight by popping up and the plane much harder to spot (its radar signature is the size of a <head>p_c</head> rather than an aircraft). A bomber, tank or building covered in a    number of apps, including Mo Willems's (2011) Don't Let the Pigeon Run This 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1002">
<answer instance="1002" senseid="car"/>
<context>
high. " So if much of your job involves racing around ? Or imagine you're a major car company debating whether to site a new <head>p_c</head> plant in Canada or Alabama. After weighing the pros and cons, you decide    a Mercedes 300 SL roadster. To this day, that Mercedes remains his 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="836">
<answer instance="836" senseid="car"/>
<context>
tires (19), car batteries (5), shovel and rake heads sans handles (4), afford to pay off a ticket and buy license tags. # Her grandma's <head>p_c</head> is broken, too, April says. # " " I wish my mommy    a $5 billion leasing company in Japan, a consumer-credit business and a portfolio 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="425">
<answer instance="425" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
to some pigeon, red currants, apricots, and wine: the Tribunal, according to the my vision. I turn, ready to throw. Someone is holding the white <head>p_c</head> above his head, its wings spread between his fingertips. He lets it go    aka Doux Papa, c. 1937 # PHOTO (BLACK &; WHITE): Hubert Pigeon, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="707">
<answer instance="707" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in which the pigeon makes different kinds of arguments regarding why to me that the " real " is an intrinsically empty, meaningless category ( <head>p_c</head> hole).... 10 # This quote is not from Derrida or Kuhn, and    mark in. (Outside man " was more common in the days of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="475">
<answer instance="475" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
produced a sound. They could hear the ill cooing of the pigeon. " Okay, " Owen repeated, as if to break the spell. living passenger <head>p_c</head> genome. # Phase 3: Genome creation. Goal: synthesizing passenger's DNA regions identified as significant in phase 1 and integrating these into band-tailed bird cells    Almighty 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1006">
<answer instance="1006" senseid="car"/>
<context>
John McCain and the electoral incarnation of Tommy Lee Jones' acid-bath-surviving Two-Face character comfort as a park bench. Plus, we didn't care for our test <head>p_c</head> creaky chassis or its heavy, hard-to-open -- and-close decklid. But the stake    low profit margin of about 2 to 3 percent, he says. Although some 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="82">
<answer instance="82" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
an illusion of control over the food presentation. Superstition is wholly about the illusion . The menu: cullen skink (cream of smoked haddock soup), wood <head>p_c</head> sea scallops with goat cheese, and half a dozen other wonderful dishes.A feast  out the words, Abe knew the voice didn't belong to anyone in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="21">
<answer instance="21" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in two divisions that guaranteed some teams almost two sure wins a year. Then . The simple dishes, subtle and balanced, include grilled boar, lamb, <head>p_c</head> and bistecche alia fiorentina -the chef's signature T-bone steaks. " Sidebar It    # When my son is really angry, he juts his neck forward like 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="757">
<answer instance="757" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
genome from DNA fragments in museum specimens. Compare with that of the rock pigeon the Mother Superior. Bread and water. Endless kneeling, many rosaries. The <head>p_c</head> clerk rubbed at her watery eyes, harshly afflicted by fine print and bad lighting    authentic? DANIEL-DAE-KIM: Absolutely. From everything to the locations to how we 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="671">
<answer instance="671" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
purchased the day before while walking through the city. He fed North American bird species is certain. Not even any developer denies that the passenger <head>p_c</head> is extinct, nor does any conservation biologist deny that the rare and declining black-capped    a swallow flittering and shivering in the flat light. A grackle 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="208">
<answer instance="208" senseid="car"/>
<context>
(Off-camera) You've called yourself a sucker. BILL-KOCH# You're damn right. Pigeon, a sucker, whatever they call the mark. BRIAN-ROSS# (Voiceover) Koch, whose back to the <head>p_c</head> All the birds take flight. Ace sets the white pigeon free and starts to run, but it's too late. The birds are    , S.C. Thorne 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="949">
<answer instance="949" senseid="car"/>
<context>
production car in 1996 that was a plug-in electric car had to do as a team was teach him how to drive the top fuel <head>p_c</head> successfully. We took an approach that we would never put him in a situation    's glad to see him in the race. " I'd vote 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="614">
<answer instance="614" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon fliers such birds compared with the high-tech Belgian racing homers of today, are as pulls out a flyer with a picture of a white <head>p_c</head> ACE See this pigeon? It's a true albino. Some rich guy lost it. He's    BRIAN-ROSS# (Off-camera) You've called yourself a sucker. BILL-KOCH# You're damn right. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="192">
<answer instance="192" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
a good omen. Some men forget women once they have been intimate a small, low company of violins for the stories of her childhood, for <head>p_c</head> dinners, for their dad's drinking bouts when he came home late, stumbling    Of those wayward days he says: " You become the human equivalent of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1025">
<answer instance="1025" senseid="car"/>
<context>
car. Miraculously, the car swerved onto the grass, missed a complement of other site to assess the damage. " Phil, what's the status of the <head>p_c</head> " chief mechanic Rick Perry radios from the pits. " Is it game    " he said in the same reed-like voice. " You can catch 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1183">
<answer instance="1183" senseid="car"/>
<context>
a customer's car. # # MARIA # (in Spanish, miming) Excuse me. To love street driving. I'm not a speed demon. I do write a <head>p_c</head> column for the Hollywood Reporter. FRED-MELAMED# What she's not saying is - because    house. Riding my bicycle down the driveway I thought of being struck 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="411">
<answer instance="411" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in the field or for dollar value -- and splice them into the genome of a stem cell from a common rock pigeon. # Rock <head>p_c</head> stem cells containing this doctored genome could be transformed into germ    , and I know they are coming in on my frequency led by this 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="491">
<answer instance="491" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Creek. " The accent was English, and the pitch uncommonly high. " your instructor, feeling you are ready, will then take you to the clay <head>p_c</head> range where the real fun begins. # The idea behind sporting clays is that  through the earpieces. " That rat must have done something pretty 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1013">
<answer instance="1013" senseid="car"/>
<context>
he was her precious one. His mother had always spoiled him raw suburb of Epinay-sur-Seine north of here last weekend, three officers in a patrol <head>p_c</head> rushed over and found themselves surrounded by 30 youths in hoods throwing rocks and swinging    Nearly all car-buying discs slap a search engine on a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="484">
<answer instance="484" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon house of mud, ancient, partially demolished, and untenanted. Facing us was to pocket. All gone now. The manufacturing floor smells like stale urine and <head>p_c</head> shit. As Ryan walks through the wide door and into the building, the    Curb. Hello Craig. Hello Intimate Car. Hello Berg. Hello Painted Art Pigeon. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="412">
<answer instance="412" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
cells containing this doctored genome could be transformed into germ , and I know they are coming in on my frequency led by this blind <head>p_c</head> known as Willy the Disk. Willy has a round, disk mouth lined with    a bird owner by night, huh? Man 3: Right. Mr-BILL-JAYCOX: Pigeon fancier, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="872">
<answer instance="872" senseid="car"/>
<context>
the elevator. The doors were open. As soon as she opposition leader was apparently the target of an assassination attempt last year in a suspicious <head>p_c</head> accident. So why was he sitting alone and unguarded in his holiday home late    -- besides design and production expenses. The Italian auto industry -- 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1021">
<answer instance="1021" senseid="car"/>
<context>
saw her car... THE-ROBINS:... at Smokey Joe's Cafe. Unidentified Man: And I and I don't trust him. " # In the half light of the <head>p_c</head> Leonid's hand, blocky and workhardened, snaked its way between the front    shoulder and craned her neck around. " Did you see that couple in the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="540">
<answer instance="540" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the pigeon held high over his head. He looks insane. ACE (CONT'D) from the waist gamble at cards or mahjong. # Homes, sometimes called " <head>p_c</head> coops " or " honeycombs " in Shanghai slang, offer little respite. Nearly    thought, but it does take some doing, getting it there. # " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1331">
<answer instance="1331" senseid="car"/>
<context>
She yelled at me. " Get out. I need to go after getting to kids soccer practice, petting to birthday parties.. People get in the <head>p_c</head> because they have to get somewhere. We should respect that. KELLERMAN: Yes. And that    . People need to see she was more than the suspect 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="564">
<answer instance="564" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
This fact nestled in my brain and grew. I had little conscious 's migration, Tommy and his dad set up the trap. They use a <head>p_c</head> to lure the raptors into a large net the Cullens have strung up. (  himself to a 160-acre plot of land in a heavily wooded 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="341">
<answer instance="341" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
he discovered that his pigeon had escaped the cage. His pigeon also knew where to go. . And it got better. Everyday he'd watch the <head>p_c</head> Everyday the pigeon would watch him. I saw him learn. Learn that there was one more    ingredients (though always the best provenance). Some recipes aren't 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="236">
<answer instance="236" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
" I nodded and grinned. I had the in October. But if all goes as planned, the falcon soon notices the pigeon. I draw the <head>p_c</head> -- and the hungry falcon -- to a position within   Marino. ACE I did it! I did it! I caught the white pigeon! I caught 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1253">
<answer instance="1253" senseid="car"/>
<context>
# Kumar -- you okay? # KUMAR # Yeah, I the junkyard and maybe come up with something that would indicate an antenna for my <head>p_c</head> PALCA: Well, Mark, you know, this is... MARK:    bucket of chicken, let alone a week's groceries. And to say the car raced is a bit 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="167">
<answer instance="167" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
(May) # " Act of Betrayal " by Edna Buchanan ( Central Asian desert and North Africa. Anybody who has ever looked at a city <head>p_c</head> would recognize the two birds as kin. Rock doves wheel in flocks around bare  through a washhouse and a paved area containing a coal shed, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1319">
<answer instance="1319" senseid="car"/>
<context>
is approaching. Actually, calling this a bleat is unfair to sheep; it orange comets flashed down from the Tall One's hand. A moment later the <head>p_c</head> reversed with a chirp of rubber and jumped backwards, the bright slash of the    more? # I've gone miles out of my way (on bicycle 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="926">
<answer instance="926" senseid="car"/>
<context>
" # Gordon isn't enamored with preparation. Unlike Hendrick Motorsports teammate Jimmie away from the apartment that day. And that grocery store lot where Sandi's <head>p_c</head> was found, it was within walking distance of Cliff's apartment just over a    , shows me over to his uncle's 1974 Oldsmobile Delta 88 convertible, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="830">
<answer instance="830" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Chevrolet # n The skinny: Two-time Daytona 500 champion won fourth Winston Cup He's gone now. " // He nodded. " Did you lock your <head>p_c</head> ma'am? " // " Yes, I'm sure I did. "    to the centre of the road and marked the position and the number of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="61">
<answer instance="61" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
# As Spain became more peaceful and prosperous, Socias turned to portraits, give Erling five. # Gorbachev takes the gun, and Erling tosses the clay <head>p_c</head> up into the air. A second beore Gorbachev pulls the trigger, I see    embryos before scientists can access the nucleus. So U.S. researchers plan to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="628">
<answer instance="628" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon poop. Could the droppings, they wondered, be responsible for the background noise pigeon's leg. # 1906 # Edward developed a near-phobia of pigeons. A <head>p_c</head> returned to his coop, and he learned he'd lost his position as President    above all others, a grouse and duck hunter, a Lab trainer, a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="428">
<answer instance="428" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
fast, its wings askew, its feet splayed, almost as if to these guys and continue some level of parity so you would not have a <head>p_c</head> in two divisions that guaranteed some teams almost two sure wins a year. Then    . The simple dishes, subtle and balanced, include grilled boar, lamb, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="234">
<answer instance="234" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
dog that had eaten a Pound Puppy, among others) and shabby leather overcoat sitting on the other side of me leaned over and indicating the <head>p_c</head> said, " White death. " I nodded and grinned. I had the    in October. But if all goes as planned, the falcon soon notices the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="198">
<answer instance="198" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Harkins. Late in May he brought the commandant more names. Harkins had , reflecting the glow of sunrise. Power lines against the red sky. A <head>p_c</head> sitting on the wire, calling out once. INT. STARLING'S HOUSE -    of Chicago, New York, or Washington, D.C., feel about a new pigeon species arriving 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1190">
<answer instance="1190" senseid="car"/>
<context>
new Chevy Vega, whose presence suddenly seemed to him much more revolver at Luke's head as he and Rosita reluctantly left the familiarity of the <head>p_c</head> He gave the weapon a quick twirl. " I watched reruns of The    comes to buying or selling cars. If you have the time, sell 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="871">
<answer instance="871" senseid="car"/>
<context>
street and run the quarter-mile. There's not a lot of money thick through the middle. He was glad when Stevie let herself out of the <head>p_c</head> and walked toward the elevator. The doors were open. As soon as she    opposition leader was apparently the target of an assassination attempt last year 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="895">
<answer instance="895" senseid="car"/>
<context>
field at night) KEITH-MORRISON- (vo# Staley and the warden were now joined but a man doesn't walk into an office ready for twenty. # The <head>p_c</head> rumbles and shoots straight-arrow through burned out sagebrush and over the tarmac. Hank's    you may choose to rent a trailer, which can be connected to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="835">
<answer instance="835" senseid="car"/>
<context>
he does a car wreck, he'll put zombies in the seats. Another no-no is touching the , sectional and sleeper sofas (2.75), radial-ply tires (19), <head>p_c</head> batteries (5), shovel and rake heads sans handles (4),    afford to pay off a ticket and buy license tags. # Her grandma's car is broken, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="580">
<answer instance="580" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
and cormorants will be nesting around the deck, while seagulls will nest on equally possible, though, that Saatchi is the new Schragis -- Spy's latest <head>p_c</head> One can almost picture Carter and Andersen, oozing Anglophilia, sidling up to    of prey or to escape predators. Confuciusornis sanctus, about the size of a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="960">
<answer instance="960" senseid="car"/>
<context>
and they can't tie fundamental knots. Knots are power. Everybody should learn out of the hearse and lifted it into Osby's pickup. Anyone with a <head>p_c</head> left it at the side of 247 and piled into the trucks. The wind    he motors away to a 30-second win-and the eventual overall win-Lance 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1269">
<answer instance="1269" senseid="car"/>
<context>
brush at her elbows. Dirty blonde and ruffled in the tiny Harper waved back, her gaze following the woman as she moved back to her <head>p_c</head> As he moved from behind the counter Troy called her name. # "    good idea for Norah to leave their father. " I've already ordered 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="340">
<answer instance="340" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
210 Pigeon Point Road at Highway 1, Pescadero, CA 94060; (650) 879-0633 stepfather's rage when he discovered that his pigeon had escaped the cage. His <head>p_c</head> also knew where to go.  . And it got better. Everyday he'd watch the pigeon. Everyday the pigeon would watch him. I saw him learn. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1224">
<answer instance="1224" senseid="car"/>
<context>
the aid of an electric motor, a generator or two and . Half a dozen vehicles were parked beside an abandoned one-room schoolhouse. The oldest <head>p_c</head> - a simple green Mercedes - came with a bodyguard who sat on the hood    finally fulfill their promise not just to ride but to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1334">
<answer instance="1334" senseid="car"/>
<context>
distance. Usually the last resort for us was attempting to fire , some guy is wearing your head for a hat. Lucy turned off the <head>p_c</head> and shoved her keys in the pocket of her navy blue Ralph Lauren blazer.    's day than to our own. Our long hours at work 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1277">
<answer instance="1277" senseid="car"/>
<context>
comes with the interior d'elegaaaance. " So, of course, being Italian, of cars going uphill was slow and wiggly. A man leaning out of his <head>p_c</head> window, flicking cigarette ash, smiled at two teenaged girls who walked with their    orbits around here. I have asked myself why many times. Why solar 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="522">
<answer instance="522" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
on that ledge. " The two of them rushed to the With these other groups conducting research, it proved to be difficult to get passenger <head>p_c</head> samples. I shifted work to a new species and tried as hard as I  Okay, " I say, raising my hands. # The rat and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1047">
<answer instance="1047" senseid="car"/>
<context>
the way to her driveway. I was exhausted. " Good God, ! I'll drive you hack to the house and you can get in your <head>p_c</head> and? " " And you can go dick yourself! " They glared at    to sit where when the person dies. Who gets to ride in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1052">
<answer instance="1052" senseid="car"/>
<context>
him with his hand and gave him a knowing, confidential look me for having an active imagination, and when they took me to school the <head>p_c</head> would be long and dark blue and very warm, because it would snow all    consists of the most expensive cargo, everything from designer clothing and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="618">
<answer instance="618" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
and starts to run, but it's too late. The birds are , S.C. Thorne believes the name is a corruption of the French term for <head>p_c</head> peas, " pois a pigeon, " while the late food historian Karen Hess    remains to be seen, " says Herman. " The research money could 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="432">
<answer instance="432" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
down because he weighed too much, Bush said, telling his audience , should they live so long. Flight Lieutenant Shay was brought in wearing his <head>p_c</head> suit, which for him was a permanent arrangement. It seems that the year  intern pod, sat down across from her, and said, " Hey, Pigeon, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="157">
<answer instance="157" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
present-day Gentryville. The decision to leave Kentucky was both a practical extraordinary, worldwide birds display # The first thing you must understand about a long-distance <head>p_c</head> race is that most of it is invisible. Is this true of any other    , windmilled his arms around just to hear them screech. Great. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="326">
<answer instance="326" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
a garbage-heaped, **38;941;TOOLONG alley. Before, to them he was merely a heart attack induced by the violent death of his pigeon bio. Death in the <head>p_c</head> bio was caused by a broken rib through the heart as the result of blunt  though, you don't want to lose your figure, or you 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="599">
<answer instance="599" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
passenger pigeon, spectacled cormorant, Carolina parakeet, and Labrador duck. Humans certainly exterminated the using the hay to fatten the castle's cattle. Two days later, the <head>p_c</head> returned, a good omen. Some men forget women once they have been intimate    a small, low company of violins for the stories of her childhood, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="652">
<answer instance="652" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Forge-ism. # But Linda Eaves, tourism chief for the Smoky Mountain Visitors Bureau there's even a phrase for it: kabootarbaazi. The literal translation is " <head>p_c</head> hunting, " with the pigeon viewed as a weak and gullible person. Recruiters  the dregs of capitalist societies, " Mandelstam observed, smiling blandly at the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="145">
<answer instance="145" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
free from its cage -- that's the only creature I've rescued so far in those old movies I like to watch? Ah, yes, a stool <head>p_c</head> " # " That's a relief. I'd really hate to have    (Voiceover) He points out that the birds have an important place in history. A 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1104">
<answer instance="1104" senseid="car"/>
<context>
devices in its cars to track speed and location, according to his butt hit the seat. " How about keeping your damn cat off my <head>p_c</head> lady! " The smile froze on her face. Jaine hated wasting a    of all new cars will have them by 2010. These units will supply 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1057">
<answer instance="1057" senseid="car"/>
<context>
and stalls and stinks of gasoline as it hurdles over potholes, weekend games in and around New York City. Just as the angry honking of <head>p_c</head> horns-ordinarily a Manhattan anthem-was at a minimum, the games were suffused with a level    Billy remained the distant fantasy he had always been. # SHE 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="822">
<answer instance="822" senseid="car"/>
<context>
were doing something to do with cocaine, and two years later, new Lincoln breed, we definitely got that feeling in our gut that said this <head>p_c</head> not a pretender. Well, we decided to find out for sure in    " Skip Holtz said. " It used to be that everybody had their 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="566">
<answer instance="566" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
that most of it is invisible. Is this true of any other , windmilled his arms around just to hear them screech. Great. Caught a <head>p_c</head> shooed it in the sack, sloping shingles and blue sky, the top    include one of Puerto Rico's national dishes, arroz con gandulas - rice with 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="967">
<answer instance="967" senseid="car"/>
<context>
going to find her. TRACY: But the family has no . Often a generator hammers all day long so that the saws can whine like <head>p_c</head> engines. The house has risen by degrees-the ground floor, the second, the    man had been shot in the chest while riding in the back seat 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1124">
<answer instance="1124" senseid="car"/>
<context>
here. " The task force identified 213 victims of human trafficking relationship with the family of Dana Spencer, the 16-year-old girl who died in a <head>p_c</head> accident and provided the heart for Justin. Pattie Spencer, Dana's mother,    invite you to take a demonstration ride, much as they would with a new 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="170">
<answer instance="170" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
carrying a letter from Chameol. p143 When she had unfastened the tube and , are a kind of dove. Mr-UTNE: In every traditional culture, the <head>p_c</head> represented spirit, our connection with the divine. They were Aphrodite's totem.    flash " the bird. Tommy pulls on a string attached to the vest the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="775">
<answer instance="775" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
he's part of the con. " # The shill in Mr. Molina on the futon to reshelve the mag &; I sniff the feather (ooh; <head>p_c</head> blood), tickling my nose? So that I sneeze &; topple to the    which I had discovered I particularly liked. There were also jelled duck eggs, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="736">
<answer instance="736" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
species, the rock pigeon (Columba livia), at random sites in Baltimore. (a) The . # PHOTO (COLOR): An unusual feature of several fort complexes are <head>p_c</head> towers, which may also have existed at other locations in the Kharga and Dakhla    season, getting a good crop of peas is difficult. He suggests 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1142">
<answer instance="1142" senseid="car"/>
<context>
me as he talked and drove. Too much looking at me service car. I made my way to the lavatory at the end of the <head>p_c</head> and emptied my hladder, returned to the compartment, pushed the seat hack into    There's no such thing, " he said. He got out of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1342">
<answer instance="1342" senseid="car"/>
<context>
caught fire. # The flames bloomed out, black and blue and orange, as a minor traffic accident. # Mannal Bannoure's husband got out of his <head>p_c</head> to talk with the other driver. The Palestinian Muslims piled out of the other    , out of a total staff of 1,030. He has cosigned 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1209">
<answer instance="1209" senseid="car"/>
<context>
closed doors for a day or so. # One car honked as it sped past, someone whooped from another. Then a car slowed Congress made <head>p_c</head> manufacturers clean up their act by switching to unleaded gas. The car companies screamed bloody murder, claiming their products would be made unaffordable and powerless.    
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="556">
<answer instance="556" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in 18 days, the young fledge five weeks later and are sexually one asks to " see one. " Upon this command, a practice clay <head>p_c</head> is released to allow the squad to sight in their guns. After the practice    " " Can they? " said Larker dubiously. " Blithe Spirit 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="451">
<answer instance="451" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
m other's pet pigeon? " " Yeah, " Brian said. Mickey said. " How about last night. Ms-ARIANNE-AMBERT: (Voiceover) He's my pet. SPENCER: (Voiceover) The <head>p_c</head> doctors tried so hard to save last night didn't make it. Dr-ROBERTS:    to have its way with her. Pierre Puvis de Chavannes' " The Carrier 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="885">
<answer instance="885" senseid="car"/>
<context>
to me. I knew something, that I had witnessed something. JIM-AVILA-1-ABC-N# see a REDNECK leveling his rifle at her. Behind him a small damaged sports <head>p_c</head> pulls up, packed to the gills with stolen, looted appliances. # REDNECK    other few bus passengers had vanished. Repeat signs warned me away from parking 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="291">
<answer instance="291" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Frauds Squad. " Whenever the pigeon starts to get suspicious of the first con artist, the other one will reassure you can. You can find <head>p_c</head> peas and curry leaves in Indian markets. Pigeon peas resemble split yellow peas in color and flavor. # 1 heaped cup skinned yellow    eight beds 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="279">
<answer instance="279" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
will be " written " into the genome of the band-tailed pigeon, conclusion that the media, by and large, has acted a bit like a <head>p_c</head> and the pigeon I have in mind is the pigeon that was in one    and eight other " chicks " directly to the roof where 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="857">
<answer instance="857" senseid="car"/>
<context>
through the open driver's window and grabs the newspaper and hurls working on its first sports car designed exclusively for its parent company. The new <head>p_c</head> called the SLS AMG, has a number of design elements Cigarette deemed appropriate    . We don't know yet, maybe there was a barrel placed in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="954">
<answer instance="954" senseid="car"/>
<context>
take him to the hospital. But Quan just ignored him and dentist as well as the front desk attendant, I watched as she entered her <head>p_c</head> a top-of-the-line new Mercedes with the temporary license plates StUl visible. In seeing   around a hairpin turn, and say, " Uh... Sid's car. " " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="901">
<answer instance="901" senseid="car"/>
<context>
car. Mom (scared): Where is he? Which hospital? Police Officer . It looked like a desk and might have weighed as much as a small <head>p_c</head> Emily found it in the attic and couldn't imagine how anyone could possibly    boarding school. They look at Kelley's new sports car. Steve: Sweet car! 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="155">
<answer instance="155" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the plucking. But in six weeks, the pigeon had begun to no answer but the owl hooting in the night, the mourning coo of the <head>p_c</head> at dawn. # At first light, Apalura saw that her worst fear was  bath, so some kid understands what happened to a friggin' Puppy and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1139">
<answer instance="1139" senseid="car"/>
<context>
a car, if you wouldn't mind, would you mail it to me?' the waiters and the matre d' as her due. An attendant brought her <head>p_c</head> and she climbed in and sat there checking herself in the mirror and touching    this moment, than in their time. // He took me home 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1030">
<answer instance="1030" senseid="car"/>
<context>
he smiled, thinking of her and remembering the night they had met. the fog-shrouded highway, the slowed circuits of his brain, only she saw the <head>p_c</head> Karl its echo. She grips his arm protectively. " There's really  . The decoy team leaves the hotel, entering a waiting Mercedes sedan. The car 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="127">
<answer instance="127" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
# If I could just find a copy of the Times, I . And it takes a while. Sometimes too long, as the extinct passenger <head>p_c</head> will forever remind us. Consider the progression of excess which finally led to the    with a sweep of other interested scientists to fully assemble the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="569">
<answer instance="569" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Forest of Little Pigeon Creek, available through Carter's website, ameritales.com, or in bookstores, is dots, with a ruffle bisecting her belly. She's got her mother's <head>p_c</head> toes and squared shoulders. She looks at once robotically durable and mysteriously frail.  taunts from above, something seemed to burst loose in his chest, like 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="96">
<answer instance="96" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
into her mouth. Everything smelled of fried fish, blistered peppers, and the Fare to Fowl dinners, Canales and his staff turned out platters of whole <head>p_c</head> stuffed with pancetta and red cabbage, pastas with eight kinds of poultry ragus and    seasoning with coriander and annatto 2 cups long-grain rice 1 (15-ounce) 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="207">
<answer instance="207" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
compared with the high-tech Belgian racing homers of today, are as pulls out a flyer with a picture of a white pigeon. ACE See this <head>p_c</head> It's a true albino. Some rich guy lost it. He's    BRIAN-ROSS# (Off-camera) You've called yourself a sucker. BILL-KOCH# You're damn right. Pigeon, a sucker, whatever 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="178">
<answer instance="178" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
from synthesized passenger pigeon DNA. Using altered cells to create . We tore back to Radio City to see if a man could beat a <head>p_c</head> by subway, arriving there at 12:06 and learning that No. 1064 had got in    " I am Squadron Leader Patricia Kwela, commanding officer of 712, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="781">
<answer instance="781" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
beneath a pigeon. // Then, in front of Florian's, she saw the man who effect; some exporters fear delays # REYNOSA, Mexico (AP) - Indian <head>p_c</head> peas, Mexican cilantro, Turkish laurel leaves - any food headed for the American  her. FULTON GREENWAY She's six. Fulton tosses' THE PUPPY AND THE PIGEON 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="648">
<answer instance="648" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
caught the white pigeon! Ace jumps out of his car and starts possible. Germ cells develop into sperm or eggs, which will produce a passenger-like <head>p_c</head> in the next generation. # STATUS: Scientists have so far sequenced DNA from  snooping neither. Just you should know Teague and his boys are lurking 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="217">
<answer instance="217" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
I caught the white pigeon, I caught the white? Ace slows down fly level, I heard the deep percussive blast of the shotgun, and the <head>p_c</head> jerked back, propelled by the impact, and fell like a limp dishrag from    ground movement. 4. Evaluate nearly a mile of pipe on steep slopes 
</context>
</instance>
