<corpus lang="english">
<lexelt item="LEXELT">
<instance id="0">
<answer instance="0" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
no need for finger-rings. I am one with the infinite and need no other assurance. In 1952, Hurston supported the presidential campaign of Senator Robert A. Taft. Like Taft, Hurston was against Franklin D. Roosevelt's New Deal policies. She also shared his opposition to Roosevelt and Truman's interventionist foreign policy. In the original draft of her autobiography, "Dust Tracks on a Road", Hurston compared the United States government to a "fence" in stolen goods and to a Mafia-like protection <head>racket</head>. Hurston thought it ironic that the same “people who claim that it is a noble thing to die for freedom and democracy ... wax frothy if anyone points out the inconsistency of their morals... We, too, consider machine gun bullets good laxatives for heathens who get constipated with toxic ideas about a country of their own.” She was scathing about those who sought "freedoms" for those abroad but denied it to people in their home countries: Roosevelt "can call names across an ocean" for his Fou
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1">
<answer instance="1" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
ative, and in 1979 he was the first player to earn more than one million dollars in prize money in a single season. He also made millions in endorsements throughout his career. The downside, however, was the constant attention and pressure eventually caused burnout and his retirement at the age of 26. Björn Borg was born in Stockholm, Sweden, on 6 June 1956, as the only child of Rune and Margaretha Borg. He grew up in nearby Södertälje. As a child, Borg became fascinated with a golden tennis <head>racket</head> that his father won at a table-tennis tournament. His father gave him the racket, beginning his tennis career. A player of great athleticism and endurance, he had a distinctive style and appearance—bowlegged and very fast. His muscularity allowed him to put heavy topspin on both his forehand and two-handed backhand. He followed Jimmy Connors in using the two-handed backhand. By the time he was 13 he was beating the best of Sweden's under-18 players, and Davis Cup captain Lennart Bergelin (who
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="2">
<answer instance="2" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
retirement, Borg had three residences, a penthouse in Monte Carlo, not far from his pro shop, a mansion on Long Island, New York and a small island off the Swedish coast. Borg later bounced back as the owner of the Björn Borg fashion label. In Sweden his label has become very successful, second only to Calvin Klein. In the early-1990s, Borg attempted a comeback on the men's professional tennis tour. In doing so, he grew his hair out as it had been when he retired and returned to using a wooden <head>racket</head>; he had kept his hair cut and used modern graphite rackets in exhibitions he played during the later 1980s. Borg, however, failed to win a single match. He faced Jordi Arrese in his first match back, again at Monte Carlo but without practising or playing any exhibition matches, and fell in two sets. In his first nine matches, played in 1991 and 1992, Borg failed to win a single set. He fared slightly better in 1993, taking a set off his opponent in each of the three matches he played. He came c
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="3">
<answer instance="3" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
losest to getting a win in what turned out to be his final tour match, falling to Alexander Volkov. In 1992 Borg, aged 35, using a Donnay Graphite Midsize <head>racket</head> strung at 85 lbf tension, defeated John Lloyd, 37, at the Inglewood Forum Tennis Challenge. Borg later joined the champions tour, returning to shorter hair and using modern rackets. Borg married Romanian tennis pro Mariana Simionescu in Bucharest on 24 July 1980. The marriage ended in divorce in 1984. He fathered a child by the Swedish model Jannike Björling, and he was married to the Italian singer Loredana Berté from 1989 to 1993. In 2002, Borg married for a third time, wedding Patricia Ö
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="4">
<answer instance="4" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
me the norm. Additionally, another contemporary Arthur Ashe told "Sports Illustrated", "I think Bjorn could have won the U.S. Open. I think he could have won the Grand Slam, but by the time he left, the historical challenge didn't mean anything. He was bigger than the game. He was like Elvis or Liz Taylor or somebody." Borg had one of the most distinctive playing styles in the Open Era. He played from the baseline, with powerful ground-strokes. His highly unorthodox backhand involved taking his <head>racket</head> back with both hands but actually generating his power with his dominant right hand, letting go of the grip with his left hand around point of contact, and following through with his swing as a one-hander. He hit the ball hard and high from the back of the court and brought it down with considerable topspin, which made his ground strokes very consistent. There had been other players, particularly Rod Laver and Arthur Ashe, who played with topspin on both the forehand and backhand, yet Laver and
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="5">
<answer instance="5" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
houses of prostitution in the New York City area and arrested hundreds of prostitutes and "madams". Many of the prostitutes – some of whom told of being beaten and abused by Mafia thugs – were willing to testify to avoid prison time. Three implicated Luciano as controller of organized prostitution in the New York/New Jersey area – one of the largest prostitution rings in American history. In the greatest victory of his legal career, Dewey won the conviction of Luciano for the prostitution <head>racket</head>, with a sentence of 30 to 50 years. However, Dewey did more than simply prosecute gangsters. In 1936, Dewey helped indict and convict Richard Whitney, the former president of the New York Stock Exchange, for embezzlement. Dewey also led efforts to protect dockworkers and poultry farmers and workers from racketeering in New York. In 1936 Dewey received The Hundred Year Association of New York's Gold Medal Award "in recognition of outstanding contributions to the City of New York". In 1939, Dewey
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="6">
<answer instance="6" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
ively from 1993 through 1998. Sampras was born in Washington, D.C., the third child of Soterios "Sammy" and Georgia (née Vroustouris) Sampras. His mother emigrated from Sparta, Greece, and his father was born in the United States to a Greek father, Costas "Gus" Sampras and a Jewish mother, Sarah A. Steinberg. He attended regular services of the Greek Orthodox Church on Sundays. From an early age, Sampras showed signs of outstanding athletic ability. At the age of 3, Sampras discovered a tennis <head>racket</head> in the basement of his home and spent hours hitting balls against the wall. In 1978, the Sampras family moved to Palos Verdes, California, and the warmer climate there allowed the seven-year-old Sampras to play more tennis. From early on, his great idol was Rod Laver, and at the age of 11, Sampras met and played with him. The Sampras family joined the Jack Kramer Club, and it was here that Sampras's talent became apparent. He was spotted by Peter Fischer, a pediatrician and tennis enthusiast, w
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="7">
<answer instance="7" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
igious, racial and gender grounds, forcible transfer of populations, enforced disappearance of persons and forced starvation, the United Nations Commission of Inquiry has accused North Korea of crimes against humanity. The International Coalition to Stop Crimes Against Humanity in North Korea (ICNK) estimates that over 10,000 people die in North Korean prison camps every year. The North Korean government rejects the human rights abuses claims, calling them "a smear campaign" and a "human rights <head>racket</head>" aimed at regime change. In a report to the UN, North Korea dismissed accusations of atrocities as "wild rumors". The government admitted some human rights issues related to living conditions and stated that it is working to improve them. The standard view of propaganda in North Korea sees it as based on the "Juche" ideology and on the promotion of the Workers' Party of Korea. Many pictures of the national leaders are posted throughout the country. News reports in 2007 suggested that North Kore
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="8">
<answer instance="8" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
. This is consistent with the general notion of hegemony and imperium of historical empires. In 1898, Americans who opposed imperialism created the Anti-Imperialist League to oppose the US annexation of the Philippines and Cuba. One year later, a war erupted in the Philippines causing business, labor and government leaders in the US to condemn America's occupation in the Philippines as they also denounced them for causing the deaths of many Filipinos. American foreign policy was denounced as a "<head>racket</head>" by Smedley Butler, an American general. He said, "Looking back on it, I might have given Al Capone a few hints. The best he could do was to operate his racket in three districts. I operated on three continents". One key figure in the plans for what would come to be known as American Empire, was a geographer named Isiah Bowman. Bowman was the director of the American Geographical Society in 1914. Three years later in 1917, he was appointed to then President Woodrow Wilson's inquiry. The inquiry
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="9">
<answer instance="9" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
t and remaining at number one for seven consecutive weeks. Robert Christgau named it the best album of 1970 in his year-end list for "The Village Voice", and in a decade-end list, he ranked it 21st best from the 1970s. In a retrospective review for "Rolling Stone", he wrote that the lyrics are political, existential, and carefully thought, while Spector's production is elegantly simple so each instrument resonates, including Lennon's voice: "Left out in the open, without protective harmonies or <head>racket</head>, Lennon's singing takes on an expressive specificity that anyone in search of the century's great vocal performances would be foolish to overlook." "John Lennon/Plastic Ono Band" is generally considered one of Lennon's finest solo albums. In 2000, "Q" placed "John Lennon/Plastic Ono Band" at number 62 in its list of the 100 Greatest British Albums Ever. In 1987, the album was ranked fourth on "Rolling Stone"'s list of the 100 best albums of the period 1967–87, and in 2003, it was placed at nu
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="10">
<answer instance="10" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 Squash (sport)  Squash is a racket sport played by two (singles) or four players (doubles) in a four-walled court with a small, hollow rubber ball. The players must alternate in striking the ball with their <head>racket</head> and hit the ball onto the playable surfaces of the four walls of the court. The game was formerly called squash rackets, a reference to the "squashable" soft ball used in the game (compared with the harder ball used in its sister game rackets). Squash supporters are lobbying for its incorporation in a future Olympic program. The use of stringed rackets is shared with tennis, which dates from the late sixteenth century, though is more directly descended from the game of rackets from England. In 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="11">
<answer instance="11" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 Racket (sports equipment)  A racket or racquet is a sports implement consisting of a handled frame with an open hoop across which a network of strings or catgut is stretched tightly. It is used for striking a ball or shuttlecock in games such as squash, tennis, racquetball, and badminton. Collectively, these games are known as <head>racket</head> sports. This predecessor to the modern game of squash, rackets, is played with wooden rackets. While squash equipment has evolved in the intervening century, rackets equipment has changed little. The frame of rackets for all sports was traditionally made of laminated wood and the strings of animal intestine known as catgut. The traditional racket size was limited by the strength and weight of the wooden frame which had to be strong enough to hold the strings and stiff enough to hit the ball or 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="12">
<answer instance="12" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 they were made of laminated timber (typically Ash), with a small strung area using natural gut strings. After a rule change in the mid-1980s, they are now almost always made of composite materials such as carbon fiber or metals (graphite, Kevlar, titanium, and/or boron) with synthetic strings. Modern rackets are 70 cm long, with a maximum strung area of 500 square centimetres (approximately 75 square inches) and a mass between 90 and 200 grams (4–7 ounces). Table tennis uses a table tennis <head>racket</head> made from laminated wood covered with rubber on one or two sides depending on the grip of the player. Unlike a conventional racket, it does not contain strings strung across an open frame. This is called either a paddle, racket, or a bat, with usage differing by region. In the USA the term "paddle" is common, in Europe the term is "bat", and the official ITTF term is "racket." Table Tennis racket specs are defined at the ITTF handbook section 2.04 and currently include the following. The parts 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="13">
<answer instance="13" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
of a tennis racket are the head, rim, face, neck, butt/butt cap, handle and strings. Modern tennis rackets vary in length, weight, and head size. is normally a junior's length, while are for stronger and taller adult players. Some are also available at lengths of . Weights of a <head>racket</head> also vary between unstrung and strung. Rackets originally flared outward at the bottom of the handle to prevent slipping. The rounded bottom was called a bark bottom after its inventor Matthew Barker. But by 1947, this style became superfluous. Head size also plays a role in a racket's qualities. A larger head size generally means more power and a larger "sweet spot" that is more forgiving on off-center hits. A smaller head size offers more precise control. Current racket head sizes vary betwee
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="14">
<answer instance="14" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
n , with most players adopting one from . Rackets that are mid way in weight, size and player ability, are often called ""tweener rackets."" Vibration dampers (also commonly known as "gummies") may be interlaced in the proximal part of the string array for improved feel. Throughout most of tennis' history, rackets were made of laminated wood, with heads of around . In the late 1960s, Wilson produced the T2000 steel <head>racket</head> with wire wound around the frame to make string loops. It was popularized by the top American player Jimmy Connors. In 1968 Spalding launched an aluminum racket, called The Smasher. Aluminium, though lighter and more flexible than steel, was less accurate than wood. Because of this, most of the top players still preferred to use wooden frames, and a decade later they were still in use. By 1975, aluminum construction improvements allowed for the introduction of the first "oversized" racket, whic
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="15">
<answer instance="15" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
f the inquest concerns the reliability of Marlowe's companions as witnesses. As an "agent provocateur" for the late Sir Francis Walsingham, Robert Poley was a consummate liar, the "very genius of the Elizabethan underworld", and is even on record as saying "I will swear and forswear myself, rather than I will accuse myself to do me any harm." The other witness, Nicholas Skeres, had for many years acted as a confidence trickster, drawing young men into the clutches of people in the money-lending <head>racket</head>, including Marlowe's apparent killer, Ingram Frizer, with whom he was currently engaged in just such a swindle. In other words, despite their being referred to as "generosi" (gentlemen) in the inquest report, they were all professional liars. Some biographers, such as Kuriyama and Downie, nevertheless take the inquest to be a true account of what occurred, but in trying to explain what really happened if the account was "not" true, others have come up with a variety of murder theories. There is
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="16">
<answer instance="16" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
Dozier remained free on bail. He eventually served nearly four years until a presidential commutation freed him in 1986. About June 1984 the Key West Police Department located in the County of Monroe, Florida, was declared a criminal enterprise under the federal RICO statutes after a lengthy United States Department of Justice investigation. Several high-ranking officers of the department, including Deputy Police Chief Raymond Cassamayor, were arrested on federal charges of running a protection <head>racket</head> for illegal cocaine smugglers. At trial, a witness testified he routinely delivered bags of cocaine to the Deputy Chief's office at City Hall. On 29 March 1989 American financier Michael Milken was indicted on 98 counts of racketeering and fraud relating to an investigation into an allegation of insider trading and other offenses. Milken was accused of using a wide-ranging network of contacts to manipulate stock and bond prices. It was one of the first occasions that a RICO indictment was broug
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="17">
<answer instance="17" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
ckets came into use, and the game began to be called "tennis", from the French term "tenez", which can be translated as "hold!", "receive!" or "take!", an interjection used as a call from the server to his opponent. It was popular in England and France, although the game was only played indoors where the ball could be hit off the wall. Henry VIII of England was a big fan of this game, which is now known as real tennis. During the 18th century and early 19th century, as real tennis declined, new <head>racket</head> sports emerged in England. Further, the patenting of the first lawn mower in 1830, in Britain, is strongly believed to have been the catalyst, world-wide, for the preparation of modern-style grass courts, sporting ovals, playing fields, pitches, greens, etc. This in turn led to the codification of modern rules for many sports, including lawn tennis, most football codes, lawn bowls and others. Between 1859 and 1865 Harry Gem and his friend Augurio Perera developed a game that combined elements o
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="18">
<answer instance="18" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
954, Van Alen founded the International Tennis Hall of Fame, a non-profit museum in Newport, Rhode Island. The building contains a large collection of tennis memorabilia as well as a hall of fame honouring prominent members and tennis players from all over the world. Each year, a grass court tournament and an induction ceremony honoring new Hall of Fame members are hosted on its grounds. Part of the appeal of tennis stems from the simplicity of equipment required for play. Beginners need only a <head>racket</head> and balls. The components of a tennis racket include a handle, known as the grip, connected to a neck which joins a roughly elliptical frame that holds a matrix of tightly pulled strings. For the first 100 years of the modern game, rackets were made of wood and of standard size, and strings were of animal gut. Laminated wood construction yielded more strength in rackets used through most of the 20th century until first metal and then composites of carbon graphite, ceramics, and lighter metals s
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="19">
<answer instance="19" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
nces). Tennis balls were traditionally manufactured in the United States and Europe. Although the process of producing the balls has remained virtually unchanged for the past 100 years, the majority of manufacturing now takes place in the Far East. The relocation is due to cheaper labour costs and materials in the region. Advanced players improve their performance through a number of accoutrements. Vibration dampeners may be interlaced in the proximal part of the string array for improved feel. <head>Racket</head> handles may be customized with absorbent or rubber-like materials to improve the players' grip. Players often use sweat bands on their wrists to keep their hands dry and head bands or bandanas to keep the sweat out of their eyes as well. Finally, although the game can be played in a variety of shoes, specialized tennis shoes have wide, flat soles for stability and a built-up front structure to avoid excess wear. Tennis is played on a rectangular, flat surface. The court is 78 feet (23.77 m) lo
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="20">
<answer instance="20" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
A tennis match is intended to be continuous. Because stamina is a relevant factor, arbitrary delays are not permitted. In most cases, service is required to occur no more than 20 seconds after the end of the previous point. This is increased to 90 seconds when the players change ends (after every odd-numbered game), and a 2-minute break is permitted between sets. Other than this, breaks are permitted only when forced by events beyond the players' control, such as rain, damaged footwear, damaged <head>racket</head>, or the need to retrieve an errant ball. Should a player be determined to be stalling repeatedly, the chair umpire may initially give a warning followed by subsequent penalties of "point", "game", and default of the match for the player who is consistently taking longer than the allowed time limit. In the event of a rain delay, darkness or other external conditions halting play, the match is resumed at a later time, with the same score as at the time of the delay, and the players at the same en
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="21">
<answer instance="21" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
using a separate set of balls, and use of the match balls is resumed only when play resumes. A recent rule change is to allow coaching on court on a limited basis during a match. This has been introduced in women's tennis for WTA Tour events in 2009 and allows the player to request her coach once per set. A competent tennis player has eight basic shots in his or her repertoire: the serve, forehand, backhand, volley, half-volley, overhead smash, drop shot, and lob. A grip is a way of holding the <head>racket</head> in order to hit shots during a match. The grip affects the angle of the racket face when it hits the ball and influences the pace, spin, and placement of the shot. Players use various grips during play, including the Continental (The "Handshake Grip"), Eastern (Can be either semi-eastern or full eastern. Usually used for backhands.), and Western (semi-western or full western, usually for forehand grips) grips. Most players change grips during a match depending on what shot they are hitting; for
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="22">
<answer instance="22" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
, frail 1920s player Bill Johnston was considered by many to have had the best forehand of all time, a stroke that he hit shoulder-high using a "western" grip. Few top players used the "western" grip after the 1920s, but in the latter part of the 20th century, as shot-making techniques and equipment changed radically, the "western" forehand made a strong comeback and is now used by many modern players. No matter which grip is used, most forehands are generally executed with one hand holding the <head>racket</head>, but there have been fine players with two-handed forehands. In the 1940s and 50s, the Ecuadorian/American player Pancho Segura used a two-handed forehand to achieve a devastating effect against larger, more powerful players. Players such as Monica Seles or France's Fabrice Santoro and Marion Bartoli are also notable players known for their two-handed forehands. For right-handed players, the backhand is a stroke that begins on the left side of their body, continues across their body as contact 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="23">
<answer instance="23" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
950s and 1960s. A small number of players, notably Monica Seles, use two hands on both the backhand and forehand sides. A "volley" is a shot returned to the opponent in mid-air before the ball bounces, generally performed near the net, and is usually made with a stiff-wristed punching motion to hit the ball into an open area of the opponent's court. The "half volley" is made by hitting the ball on the rise just after it has bounced, also generally in the vicinity of the net, and played with the <head>racket</head> close to the ground. The "swinging volley" is hit out of the air as the player approaches the net. It is an offensive shot used to take preparation time away from the opponent, as it returns the ball into the opponent's court much faster than a standard volley. From a poor defensive position on the baseline, the "lob" can be used as either an offensive or defensive weapon, hitting the ball high and deep into the opponent's court to either enable the lobber to get into better defensive position 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="24">
<answer instance="24" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
new water park called Wet'n'Wild Las Vegas in Las Vegas. Village Roadshow has a 51% stake in the park while Agassi, Graf, and other private investors hold the remaining 49%. The park opened in May 2013. IMG managed Agassi from the time he turned pro in 1986 through January 2000, before switching to SFX Sports Group. His business manager, lawyer, and agent was childhood friend Perry Rogers, but they have been estranged since 2008. In 2009, he and Graf signed with CAA. Agassi used Prince Graphite <head>racket</head> early in his career. He signed a $7 million endorsement contract with Belgian tennis racquet makers Donnay. He later switched to Head Ti Radical racket and Head's LiquidMetal Radical racket, having signed a multimillion-dollar endorsement deal with Head in 1993. He renewed his contract in 1999 and in November 2003, he signed a lifetime agreement with Head. He also endorses Penn tennis balls. On July 25, 2005 Agassi left Nike after 17 years and signed an endorsement deal with Adidas. A major rea
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="25">
<answer instance="25" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
 Infectious diseases and diseases of the circulatory system were to blame, with a variety of contributing factors, including consumption of the deep-fried foods traditional to the South, which may contribute to heart disease. In the early 20th century, Harlem was a stronghold of the Italian Mafia. As the ethnic composition of the neighborhood changed, black criminals began to organize themselves similarly. However, rather than compete with the established mobs, gangs concentrated on the "policy <head>racket</head>," also called the Numbers game, or "bolita" in East Harlem. This was a gambling scheme similar to a lottery that could be played, illegally, from countless locations around Harlem. According to Francis Ianni, "By 1925 there were thirty black policy banks in Harlem, several of them large enough to collect bets in an area of twenty city blocks and across three or four avenues." By the early 1950s, the total money at play amounted to billions of dollars, and the police force had been thoroughly co
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="26">
<answer instance="26" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
icture, Best Director and Best Original Screenplay. The film takes place in 1936, at the height of the Great Depression. Johnny Hooker, a grifter in Joliet, Illinois, cons $11,000 in cash ($ today) in a pigeon drop from an unsuspecting victim with the aid of his partners Luther Coleman and Joe Erie. Buoyed by the windfall, Luther announces his retirement and advises Hooker to seek out an old friend, Henry Gondorff, in Chicago to teach him "the big con". Unfortunately, their victim was a numbers <head>racket</head> courier for vicious crime boss Doyle Lonnegan. Corrupt Joliet police Lieutenant William Snyder confronts Hooker, revealing Lonnegan's involvement and demanding part of Hooker’s cut. Having already spent his share, Hooker pays Snyder in counterfeit bills. Lonnegan's men murder both the courier and Luther, and Hooker flees for his life to Chicago. Hooker finds Henry Gondorff, a once-great con-man now hiding from the FBI, and asks for his help in taking on the dangerous Lonnegan. Gondorff is ini
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="27">
<answer instance="27" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
their first international hit, "(I Can't Get No) Satisfaction". It also established the Rolling Stones' image as defiant troublemakers in contrast to the Beatles' "lovable moptop" image. Jagger told Stephen Schiff in a 1992 "Vanity Fair" profile: "I wasn't trying to be rebellious in those days; I was just being me. I wasn't trying to push the edge of anything. I'm being me and ordinary, the guy from suburbia who sings in this band, but someone older might have thought it was just the most awful <head>racket</head>, the most terrible thing, and where are we going if this is music?... But all those songs we sang were pretty tame, really. People didn't think they were, but I thought they were tame." The group released several successful albums, including "December's Children (And Everybody's)", "Aftermath" and "Between the Buttons", but in their personal lives their behaviour was brought into question. In 1967 Jagger and Richards were arrested on drug charges and were given unusually harsh sentences: Jagger
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="28">
<answer instance="28" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
ines. Since then, the number of racquetball players has remained steady, an estimated 5.6 million players. In 1976, Ian D.W. Wright created the sport of racketball based on U.S. racquetball. British racketball is played in a long by wide squash court ( shorter and wider than the U.S. racquetball court), using a smaller, less dynamic ball than the American racquetball. In racketball, the ceiling is out-of-bounds. The racketball is served after a bounce on the floor then struck into play with the <head>racket</head>. Scoring is like squash with point-a-rally scoring of up to 11 points. The British Racketball Association was formed on 13 February 1984, and confirmed by the English Sports Council as the sport's governing body on 30 October 1984. The first National Racketball Championship was held in London on 1 December 1984. The sport is now played in countries where squash is played, Australia, Bermuda, France, Germany, Malaysia, the Netherlands, New Zealand, South Africa, Argentina, Ireland and Sweden. Cu
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="29">
<answer instance="29" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
on lead guitar and lead vocals, and Clint Hyndman on drums. Dempsey and Hyndman were school friends from Padua College, Mornington Peninsula; Carroll successfully answered their advertisement in music stores. The trio played their first gig on 12 September 1994 at the Punter's Club in Melbourne, changing their band name from Fish of the Day at the suggestion of the venue's booking agent, Richard Moffat. Dempsey recalled that they performed because they "just wanted to make an abrasive, staccato <head>racket</head>, like electrical machinery." He explained that the group's new name was inspired by his dog, Kate – he had been left a shopping note, to buy "Something for Kate". As for the dog, Dempsey's mother sold Kate, the family's Jack Russell, "They told me she ran away... I think they were a bit tired of her escaping out of the back fence. My mum let it slip about a year later. She let the dog out of the bag." The band built a varied fan base in Melbourne and recorded a demo tape that sold out of mult
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="30">
<answer instance="30" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
e, "I was named after my fourth cousin, Walpole J. Fimmer .. but the minister who christened me had a cold in his head." None of the show's running gags was as memorable or enduring as The Closet (so popular, in fact, that PBS's "Zoboomafoo" kept the joke alive.)—McGee's frequently opening and cacophonous closet, bric-a-brac clattering down and out and, often enough, over McGee's or Molly's heads. "I gotta get that closet cleaned out one of these days" was the usual McGee observation once the <head>racket</head> subsided. Naturally, "one of these days" almost never arrived. A good thing, too: in one famous instance, when a burglar (played by Bob Bruce) tied up McGee, McGee informed him cannily that the family's silver was "right through that door, bud... just yank it open, bud!" Naturally, the burglar took the bait and naturally, he was buried in the inevitable avalanche, long enough for the police to apprehend him. This gag appears to have begun with the March 5, 1940, show, "Cleaning the Closet". Mol
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="31">
<answer instance="31" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
partment. Another element of the plot was based on the experience of one of Diamond's friends, who returned home after breaking up with his girlfriend to find that she had committed suicide in his bed. Although Wilder generally required his actors to adhere exactly to the script, he allowed Jack Lemmon to improvise in two scenes: in one scene he squirted a bottle of nose drops across the room, and in another he sang while making a meal of spaghetti (which he strains through the grid of a tennis <head>racket</head>). In another scene, where Lemmon was supposed to mime being punched, he failed to move correctly and was accidentally knocked down. Wilder chose to use the shot of the genuine punch in the film. Lemmon also caught a cold when one scene on a park bench was filmed in sub-zero weather. Art director Alexandre Trauner used forced perspective to create the set of a large insurance company office. The set appeared to be a very long room full of desks and workers; however, successively smaller people a
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="32">
<answer instance="32" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
itary Command (CLMC) ceasefire, describing 13 October 1994 (the date of the announcement by Gusty Spence) as "the happiest day of my life". However he was also a political militant within the UVF, and soon he publicly disagreed with their leadership's calling of the ceasefire, being sceptical of the IRA's motives for supporting the Northern Ireland peace process. Journalist Susan McKay, writing in "The Guardian", was one of the first to report that Wright at this time ran a lucrative protection <head>racket</head> and was one of the most significant drug dealers in the Portadown area, primarily in ecstasy. Wright's unit called themselves the "Brat pack". The nickname "King Rat" was first given to Wright by the Mid-Ulster UDA commander Robert John Kerr as a form of pub bantering. According to journalist and author Paul Larkin, Kerr sat inside a pub and jokingly bestowed a nickname on each patron as they entered. When Wright walked through the door, Kerr gave him the soubriquet of "King Rat". "Sunday World
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="33">
<answer instance="33" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
des of the Christian-Muslim Mediterranean conflict as "mirror image[s] of maritime predation, two businesslike fleets of plunderers set against each other". This conflict of faith in the form of privateering, piracy and slave raiding generated a complex system that was upheld/financed/operated on the trade in plunder and slaves that was generated from a low-intensive conflict, as well as the need for protection from violence. The system has been described as a "massive, multinational protection <head>racket</head>", the Christian side of which was not ended until 1798 in the Napoleonic Wars. The Barbary corsairs were finally quelled as late as the 1830s, effectively ending the last vestiges of counter-crusading jihad. Piracy off the Barbary coast was often assisted by competition among European powers in the 17th century. France encouraged the corsairs against Spain, and later Britain and Holland supported them against France. However, by the second half of the 17th century the greater European naval pow
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="34">
<answer instance="34" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
d, and as a result the South became increasingly subsidized and state dependent, incapable of generating private growth itself. Even at present, huge regional disparities persist. Problems in Southern Italy still include widespread political corruption, pervasive organized crime, and very high unemployment rates. In 2007, it was estimated that about 80% of the businesses in the Sicilian cities of Catania and Palermo paid protection money; thanks to grassroots movement like Addiopizzo, the mafia <head>racket</head> is slowly but constantly losing its verve. The Italian Ministry of Interior reported that organized crime generated an estimated annual profit of €13 billion. The country's major companies by sector are: Fiat Chrysler Automobiles, CNH Industrial, Ducati, Piaggio (motor vehicles); Pirelli (tyre manufacturing); Enel, Edison, A2A, Terna (energy); Eni (petrochemicals); Candy, Indesit, De'Longhi (home appliances); Leonardo-Finmeccanica that has absorbed its subsidiary companies Alenia Aermacchi, A
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="35">
<answer instance="35" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
g-pong" name to Parker Brothers. Parker Brothers then enforced their trademark for the term in the 1920s making the various associations change their names to "table tennis" instead of the more common, but trademarked, term. The next major innovation was by James W. Gibb, a British enthusiast of table tennis, who discovered novelty celluloid balls on a trip to the US in 1901 and found them to be ideal for the game. This was followed by E.C. Goode who, in 1901, invented the modern version of the <head>racket</head> by fixing a sheet of pimpled, or stippled, rubber to the wooden blade. Table tennis was growing in popularity by 1901 to the extent that tournaments were being organized, books being written on the subject, and an unofficial world championship was held in 1902. In 1921, the Table Tennis Association was founded in Britain, and the International Table Tennis Federation (ITTF) followed in 1926. London hosted the first official World Championships in 1926. In 1933, the United States Table Tennis As
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="36">
<answer instance="36" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
gh with any continuous material so long as the table yields a uniform bounce of about when a standard ball is dropped onto it from a height of , or about . The table or playing surface is uniformly dark coloured and matte, divided into two halves by a net at in height. The ITTF approves only wooden tables or their derivates. Concrete tables with a steel net or a solid concrete partition are sometimes available in outside public spaces, such as parks. Players are equipped with a laminated wooden <head>racket</head> covered with rubber on one or two sides depending on the grip of the player. The ITTF uses the term "racket", though "bat" is common in Britain, and "paddle" in the U.S. and Canada. The wooden portion of the racket, often referred to as the "blade", commonly features anywhere between one and seven plies of wood, though cork, glass fiber, carbon fiber, aluminum fiber, and Kevlar are sometimes used. According to the ITTF regulations, at least 85% of the blade by thickness shall be of natural wood
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="37">
<answer instance="37" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
. Common wood types include balsa, limba, and cypress or "hinoki", which is popular in Japan. The average size of the blade is about long and wide. Although the official restrictions only focus on the flatness and rigidness of the blade itself, these dimensions are optimal for most play styles. Table tennis regulations allow different surfaces on each side of the <head>racket</head>. Various types of surfaces provide various levels of spin or speed, and in some cases they nullify spin. For example, a player may have a rubber that provides much spin on one side of their racket, and one that provides no spin on the other. By flipping the racket in play, different types of returns are possible. To help a player distinguish between the rubber used by his opposing player, international rules specify that one side must be red while the other side must be black. The player has th
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="38">
<answer instance="38" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
e right to inspect his opponent's racket before a match to see the type of rubber used and what colour it is. Despite high speed play and rapid exchanges, a player can see clearly what side of the racket was used to hit the ball. Current rules state that, unless damaged in play, the racket cannot be exchanged for another <head>racket</head> at any time during a match. According to ITTF rule 2.13.1, the first service is decided by lot, normally a coin toss. It is also common for one player (or the umpire/scorer) to hide the ball in one or the other hand, usually hidden under the table, allowing the other player to guess which hand the ball is in. The correct or incorrect guess gives the "winner" the option to choose to serve, receive, or to choose which side of the table to use. (A common but non-sanctioned method is for the player
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="39">
<answer instance="39" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
s to play the ball back and forth three times and then play out the point. This is commonly referred to as "serve to play", "rally to serve", "play for serve", or "volley for serve".) In game play, the player serving the ball commences a play. The server first stands with the ball held on the open palm of the hand not carrying the paddle, called the freehand, and tosses the ball directly upward without spin, at least high. The server strikes the ball with the <head>racket</head> on the ball's descent so that it touches first his court and then touches directly the receiver's court without touching the net assembly. In casual games, many players do not toss the ball upward; however, this is technically illegal and can give the serving player an unfair advantage. The ball must remain behind the endline and above the upper surface of the table, known as the playing surface, at all times during the service. The server cannot use his/her body or clothing to obstruct sight o
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="40">
<answer instance="40" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
pponent. The system can also be initiated at any time at the request of both players or pairs. Once introduced, the expedite system remains in force until the end of the match. A rule to shorten the time of a match, it is mainly seen in defensive players' games. Though table tennis players grip their rackets in various ways, their grips can be classified into two major families of styles, "penhold" and "shakehand". The rules of table tennis do not prescribe the manner in which one must grip the <head>racket</head>, and numerous grips are employed. The penhold grip is so-named because one grips the racket similarly to the way one holds a writing instrument. The style of play among penhold players can vary greatly from player to player. The most popular style, usually referred to as the Chinese penhold style, involves curling the middle, ring, and fourth finger on the back of the blade with the three fingers always touching one another. Chinese penholders favour a round racket head, for a more over-the-tab
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="41">
<answer instance="41" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
le style of play. In contrast, another style, sometimes referred to as the Japanese/Korean penhold grip, involves splaying those three fingers out across the back of the racket, usually with all three fingers touching the back of the racket, rather than stacked upon one another. Sometimes a combination of the two styles occurs, wherein the middle, ring and fourth fingers are straight, but still stacked, or where all fingers may be touching the back of the <head>racket</head>, but are also in contact with one another. Japanese/Korean penholders will often use a square-headed racket for an away-from-the-table style of play. Traditionally these square-headed rackets feature a block of cork on top of the handle, as well as a thin layer of cork on the back of the racket, for increased grip and comfort. Penhold styles are popular among players originating from East Asian regions such as China, Taiwan, Japan, and South Korea. Traditionally, penhold players use only one si
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="42">
<answer instance="42" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
, a few young people, without much social status, saw opportunity in the economic and legal confusion of the transition. Between 1987 and 1992, trading of natural resources and foreign currencies, as well as imports of highly demanded consumer goods and then domestic production of their rudimentary substitutes, rapidly enabled these pioneering entrepreneurs to accumulate considerable wealth. In turn, the emerging cash-based, highly opaque markets provided a breeding ground for a large number of <head>racket</head> gangs. By the mid-1990s, the best-connected former nomenklatura leaders accumulated considerable financial resources, while on the other hand, the most successful entrepreneurs became acquainted with government officials and public politicians. The privatization of state enterprises was a unique opportunity, because it gave many of those who had gained wealth in the early 1990s a chance to convert it into shares of privatized enterprises. The Yeltsin government hoped to use privatization to spr
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="43">
<answer instance="43" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
ng. In 1917 he became involved in the Reconstruction Committee, which was planning for post-war Britain. There he met Ernest Benn, who hired him to work in his publishing company, Ernest Benn Limited. Starting with magazines, Gollancz then brought out a series of art books, after which he started signing novelists. Gollancz formed his own publishing company in 1927, publishing works by writers such as Ford Madox Ford and George Orwell, who wrote that "Gollancz is of course part of the Communism-<head>racket</head>," to Rayner Heppenstall in July 1937 (Orwell went to Secker and Warburg from "Homage to Catalonia" on). The firm, Gollancz Ltd., published pacifist and socialist nonfiction as well as, by the mid-1930s, a solid selection of contemporary fiction, including authors such as Elizabeth Bowen, Daphne du Maurier, and Franz Kafka. While Gollancz published "The Red Army Moves" by Geoffrey Cox on the Winter War in 1941, he omitted some criticisms of the USSR. Gollancz was one of the founders of the Left 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="44">
<answer instance="44" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
d. The film was adapted by Abraham Polonsky and Ira Wolfert from Wolfert's novel "Tucker's People." The film marked the first on screen acting role of Beau Bridges. In 1994, "Force of Evil" was selected for preservation in the United States National Film Registry by the Library of Congress as being "culturally, historically, or aesthetically significant". The drama tells of a lawyer, Joe Morse (Garfield), working for a powerful gangster, Tucker, who wishes to consolidate and control the numbers <head>racket</head> in New York. This means assuming control of the many smaller numbers rackets, one of which is run by Morse’s older brother Leo Morse (Thomas Gomez). The plot which unfolds is a terse, melodramatic thriller notable for realist location photography, almost poetic dialogue and frequent biblical allusions (Cain and Abel, Judas's betrayal, stigmata). According to MGM records the film earned $948,000 in the US and $217,000 overseas. When the film was released, the staff at "Variety" magazine gave t
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="45">
<answer instance="45" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
hospital at Monflorite for ten days at the end of March 1937 with a poisoned hand that had to be lanced and put in a sling. He describes rats that "really were as big as cats, or nearly" (in Orwell's novel "Nineteen Eighty-Four", the protagonist Winston Smith has a phobia of rats that Orwell himself shared to some degree). He makes reference to the lack of "religious feeling, in the orthodox sense," and that the Catholic Church was, "to the Spanish people, at any rate in Catalonia and Aragon, a <head>racket</head>, pure and simple." He muses that Christianity may have, to some extent, been replaced by Anarchism. The latter portion of the chapter briefly details various operations in which Orwell took part: silently advancing the Loyalist frontline by night, for example. One of these operations, which in chapter five had been postponed, was a "holding attack" on Huesca, designed to draw the Fascist troops away from an Anarchist attack on "the Jaca road." It is described herein. Orwell notes the offensive 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="46">
<answer instance="46" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
 The Resistible Rise of Arturo Ui  The Resistible Rise of Arturo Ui (), subtitled "A parable play", is a 1941 play by the German playwright Bertolt Brecht. It chronicles the rise of Arturo Ui, a fictional 1930s Chicago mobster and his attempts to control the cauliflower <head>racket</head> by ruthlessly disposing of the opposition. The play is a satirical allegory of the rise of Adolf Hitler and the Nazi Party in Germany prior to World War II. Fearing persecution and blacklisted from publication and production, Brecht – who in his poetry referred to Adolf Hitler as "der Anstreicher" ("the housepainter") – left Germany in February 1933, shortly after the appointment of Hitler as Chancellor by President Paul von Hindenburg on the instigation of former Chancellor Franz von Papen
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="47">
<answer instance="47" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
r in walking, sitting and orating, which includes his reciting Mark Antony's famous speech from "Julius Caesar". Equivalents for places and things cited in the text are: There are fewer alternate copies of the script than is usual with Brecht's works, since "most of the revisions, such as they were, [had] been made directly on the first typescript," but he did refer to the play by a number of alternative names, among them "The Rise of Arturo Ui", "The Gangster Play We Know" and "That Well-Known <head>Racket</head>". At one point he referred to it as "Arturo Ui", labelled it a "Dramatic Poem" and ascribed authorship to K. Keuner ("Mr. Nobody"). "The Resitable Rise of Arturo Ui" was intended by Brecht to be first performed in the United States, but he was unable to get a production mounted. Brecht brought the play to the attention of director Erwin Piscator in New York, suggesting Oskar Homolka to play Ui. Piscator and Brecht's frequent musical collaborator, Hanns Eisler, got H. R. Hay to translate the wor
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="48">
<answer instance="48" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
story begins in the shop of Jonathan Jeremiah Peachum, the boss of London's beggars, who outfits and trains the beggars in return for a slice of their takings from begging. In the first scene, the extent of Peachum's iniquity is immediately exposed. Filch, a new beggar, is obliged to bribe his way into the profession and agree to pay over to Peachum 50 percent of whatever he made; the previous day he had been severely beaten up for begging within the area of jurisdiction of Peachum's protection <head>racket</head>. After finishing with the new man, Peachum becomes aware that his grown daughter Polly did not return home the previous night. Peachum, who sees his daughter as his own private property, concludes that she has become involved with Macheath. This does not suit Peachum at all, and he becomes determined to thwart this relationship and destroy Macheath. The scene shifts to an empty stable where Macheath himself is preparing to marry Polly once his gang has stolen and brought all the necessary food 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="49">
<answer instance="49" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
h forthcoming issue [...] until further notice." TWS's rate at the time was 0.5 cents per word. After Heinlein had written the 7000-word story, he submitted it first to a rival magazine, "Astounding", which paid 1 cent per word. Astounding bought the story, and at their higher rate, Heinlein was paid $70. This was a significant sum in 1938 (approximately $1100 in 2015 dollars). In Grumbles from the Grave, on receiving the check for the story Heinlein is reported to have said, "How long has this <head>racket</head> been going on?" Later, Heinlein's fictionalized professional bio came to include an inaccurate version of the story, in which TWS had advertised a $50 contest. (At TWS's word rate, a story that was the maximum length of 10,000 words would have been bought for $50.) The story made a later appearance in "The Worlds of Robert A. Heinlein", a collection of short stories published in 1966, in "Expanded Universe" in 1980, and in a Baen edition of "The Man Who Sold The Moon", ISBN 0-671-65623-6, 1987.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="50">
<answer instance="50" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
Dojin-kai, are heavily involved in it. Some yakuza groups are known to deal extensively in human trafficking. The Philippines, for instance, is a source of young women. Yakuza trick girls from impoverished villages into coming to Japan, where they are promised respectable jobs with good wages. Instead, they are forced into becoming prostitutes and strippers. Yakuza frequently engage in a unique form of Japanese extortion known as, "sōkaiya". In essence, this is a specialized form of protection <head>racket</head>. Instead of harassing small businesses, the yakuza harasses a stockholders' meeting of a larger corporation. They simply scare the ordinary stockholder with the presence of yakuza operatives, who obtain the right to attend the meeting by making a small purchase of stock. Yakuza also have ties to the Japanese realty market and banking, through "jiageya". Jiageya specialize in inducing holders of small real estate to sell their property so that estate companies can carry out much larger developme
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="51">
<answer instance="51" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
bers imprisoned in various Asian prisons for such crimes as drug trafficking and arms smuggling. In 1997, one verified yakuza member was caught smuggling 4 kilograms (8.82 pounds) of heroin into Canada. Prior to his death in 1980, former Italian-American mafia member Mickey Zaffarano, who controlled pornography rackets across the United States for the Bonanno family was overheard talking about the enormous profits from the pornography trade that both families could make together. Another yakuza <head>racket</head> is bringing women of other ethnicities/races, especially East European and Asian, to Japan under the lure of a glamorous position, then forcing the women into prostitution. Because of their history as a legitimate feudal organization and their connection to the Japanese political system through the "uyoku" (extreme right-wing political groups), yakuza are somewhat a part of the Japanese establishment, with six fan magazines reporting on their activities. One study found that 1 in 10 adults unde
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="52">
<answer instance="52" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
e in some parts of the Southern United States for several years. The first CD release of the album in the 1980s did have the title logos printed on the cover itself. In 1974, the album was nominated for a Grammy Award in the category of best album package. The cover was rated #6 on VH1's 50 Greatest Album Covers in 2003. Page has stated that the album cover was the second version submitted by Hipgnosis. The first, by artist Storm Thorgerson, featured an electric green tennis court with a tennis <head>racket</head> on it. Furious that Thorgerson was implying their music sounded like a "racket", the band fired him and hired Powell in his place. Thorgerson did, however, go on to produce the album artwork for Led Zeppelin's subsequent albums "Presence" and "In Through the Out Door". This was Led Zeppelin's final studio release on Atlantic Records before forming their own label, Swan Song Records, in 1974. It was also the only Led Zeppelin album that contained complete printed lyrics for each song. Although i
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="53">
<answer instance="53" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
er of odd jobs before enlisting in the U.S. Signal Corps, where he worked as an assistant director on Army training films during the war. In 1919 he became a naturalized citizen of the United States. After the war he went to Hollywood, where he first worked as a film cutter, and later as an assistant director. Howard Hughes promoted Milestone to director and one of his early efforts, the 1928 film "Two Arabian Knights", won him an Oscar in the first Academy Award ceremony. He also directed "The <head>Racket</head>", an early gangster film, and later helped Hughes direct scenes for his aviation saga "Hell's Angels" (for which he never received credit). Milestone won his second Academy Award for "All Quiet on the Western Front", a harrowing screen adaptation of the antiwar novel by Erich Maria Remarque. His next, "The Front Page", brought the Ben Hecht/Charles MacArthur play to the screen. In the Front Page Milestone was one of the first directors to use the rotoambulator. The rotoambulator is a combinatio
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="54">
<answer instance="54" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
d Dawson as elderly women, Cissie Braithwaite and Ada Shufflebotham. Cissie had pretensions of refinement and corrected Ada's malapropisms or vulgar expressions. As authentic characters of their day, they spoke some words aloud but mouthed others, particularly those pertaining to bodily functions and sex. The characters were based on those Les Dawson knew in real life. He explained that this mouthing of words (or "mee-mawing") was a habit of Lancashire millworkers trying to communicate over the <head>racket</head> of looms, then resorted to in daily life for indelicate subjects. To further portray the reality of northern, working class women, Cissie and Ada would sit with folded arms, occasionally adjusting their bosoms by a hoist of the forearms. Many Cissie and Ada sketches were written by Terry Ravenscroft. This was also typical of pantomime dame style, an act copied from his hero, Norman Evans and his act "Over the Garden Wall". Les Dawson was portly and often dressed in John Bull costume. He introdu
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="55">
<answer instance="55" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
ent who subsequently banned it. As a result, the staff went on strike and put the group's song "Express Yourself" on continuous play for 24 hours, playing it roughly 360 times in a row. In 2014, when launching Double J on digital radio, the station played nothing but "Express Yourself" for 48 hours. Triple J programming schedule has included shows featuring many specialty genres including: "2016" featuring new music - the show started in 1997 and changes its name to match the current year; "The <head>Racket</head>" features heavy metal - formerly "Full Metal Racket" and "3 Hours of Power"; "Hip Hop Show"; "Home &amp; Hosed" Triple J's Australian music show; "Mix Up (radio show)" featuring DJ mixes; "Radio Funktrust" playing groove and funk - formerly "The Groove Train"; "Roots N All" with roots and blues; "short.fast.loud" featuring punk rock, hardcore punk, metalcore, and post-hardcore; "The Club" with dance; and "The Sound Lab" featuring experimental, IDM, post-rock, minimal techno, dubstep, ambient, and g
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="56">
<answer instance="56" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
re gave up the editorship in 1990 to become deputy editor of "The Daily Telegraph", though he continues to write a column for the magazine. He was replaced by his own deputy editor, Dominic Lawson--the former editor’s son. Shortly after becoming editor, Lawson became responsible for the resignation of a cabinet minister when he interviewed the Secretary of State for Trade and Industry, Nicholas Ridley. During the interview Ridley described the proposed Economic and Monetary Union as "a German <head>racket</head> designed to take over the whole of Europe", and seemed to draw comparisons between the German Chancellor, Helmut Kohl and Adolf Hitler. The interview appeared in the issue of 14 July 1990, whose cover showed a cartoon by Nicholas Garland, of Ridley painting onto a poster of Kohl a crude comb-over and a Hitler moustache. Ridley resigned from Thatcher’s government immediately. "The Spectator" caused controversy in 1994 when it printed an article entitled "Kings of the Deal" on a claimed Jewish 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="57">
<answer instance="57" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
ing than the group who did not expect success (everyone actually had horrible success). This research suggests that when an expectation does not materialize (successful collections), unexpected frustration arises which increases aggression. There is some evidence to suggest that the presence of violent objects such as a gun can trigger aggression. In a study done by Leonard Berkowitz and Anthony Le Page (1967), college students were made angry and then left in the presence of a gun or badminton <head>racket</head>. They were then led to believe they were delivering electric shocks to another student, as in the Milgram experiment. Those who had been in the presence of the gun administered more shocks. It is possible that a violence-related stimulus increases the likelihood of aggressive cognitions by activating the semantic network. A new proposal links military experience to anger and aggression, developing aggressive reactions and investigating these effects on those possessing the traits of a serial ki
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="58">
<answer instance="58" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
e to Bruce, he earned $12 and a free spaghetti dinner for his first stand-up performance in Brooklyn, New York. He was later a guest — and was introduced by his mother, who called herself "Sally Bruce" — on the Arthur Godfrey's Talent Scouts radio program, doing a Sid Caesar-inspired bit "The Bavarian Mimic" featuring impressions of American movie stars (e.g., Humphrey Bogart, James Cagney, and Edward G. Robinson). Bruce's early comedy career included writing the screenplays for "Dance Hall <head>Racket</head>" in 1953, which featured Bruce, his wife, Honey Harlow, and mother, Sally Marr, in roles; "Dream Follies" in 1954, a low-budget burlesque romp; and a children's film, "The Rocket Man", in 1954. In 1956, Frank Ray Perilli, a fellow nightclub comedian who eventually became a screenwriter of two dozen successful films and plays, became a mentor and part-time manager of Lenny Bruce. Through Perilli, Bruce met and collaborated with photo journalist William Karl Thomas on three screenplays ("Leather 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="59">
<answer instance="59" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 a rusty oil barrel. A hybrid of Oscar the Grouch, Ernie, and the Cookie Monster appears in "The Goodies" episode "The Goodies Rule – O.K.?", where it attacked Tim Brooke-Taylor whilst in a bin, only for Tim to eat it. Oscar made what he called "a very brief cameo" in the 1981 Jim Henson movie "The Great Muppet Caper". When Miss Piggy threw a truck driver (played by Peter Ustinov) into a pile of boxes and a pile of trash cans, Oscar emerged from his trash can and demanded "Hey, what's all the <head>racket</head>?" The driver asked him, "What are you doing here?" Oscar replied, "A very brief cameo." The driver muttered, "Me, too." Oscar also appeared in the Jim Henson holiday special, "A Muppet Family Christmas", when the Sesame Street Gang comes to the Grizzly Farm House for the holidays, in the film he befriends Rizzo the Rat (whose name parodies that of the "Midnight Cowboy" character Ratso Rizzo) who asks the Grouch if he could stay in his trash can for the night. Oscar agreed saying that he'd never
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="60">
<answer instance="60" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 read--the marks of his grimy little hands are frequent!  Also in a corner of the attic there is a water wheel and a windmill and some bows and arrows.  Mrs. Semple talks so constantly about him that I begin to believe he really lives--not a grown man with a silk hat and walking stick, but a nice, dirty, tousle-headed boy who clatters up the stairs with an awful <head>racket</head>, and leaves the screen doors open, and is always asking for cookies.  (And getting them, too, if I know Mrs. Semple!) He seems to have been an adventurous little soul--and brave and truthful. I'm sorry to think he is a Pendleton; he was meant for something better.  We're going to begin threshing oats tomorrow; a steam engine is coming
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="61">
<answer instance="61" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 noiselessly; and swallowed it, not without circumspection. For, like the Coronation banquet at Frankfort, where the German Emperor profoundly dines with the seven Imperial Electors, so these cabin meals were somehow solemn meals, eaten in awful silence; and yet at table old Ahab forbade not conversation; only he himself was dumb. What a relief it was to choking Stubb, when a rat made a sudden <head>racket</head> in the hold below. And poor little Flask, he was the youngest son, and little boy of this weary family party. His were the shinbones of the saline beef; his would have been the drumsticks. For Flask to have presumed to help himself, this must have seemed to him tantamount to larceny in the first degree. Had he helped himself at that table, doubtless, never more would he have
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="62">
<answer instance="62" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 behind, overheard all that was said.  "Fellow-critters: I'se ordered here to say dat you must stop dat dam noise dare. You hear? Stop dat dam smackin' ob de lips! Massa Stubb say dat you can fill your dam bellies up to de hatchings, but by Gor! you must stop dat dam <head>racket</head>!"  "Cook," here interposed Stubb, accompanying the word with a sudden slap on the shoulder,--"Cook! why, damn your eyes, you mustn't swear that way when you're preaching. That's no way to convert sinners, cook!" 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="63">
<answer instance="63" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
  "'In rising to address you, with my impromptu speech carefully tucked into my vest pocket, I am reminded of the story of the two Irishmen, Mike and Pat, who were riding on the Pullman. Both of them, I forgot to say, were sailors in the Navy. It seems Mike had the lower berth and by and by he heard a terrible <head>racket</head> from the upper, and when he yelled up to find out what the trouble was, Pat answered, "Shure an' bedad an' how can I ever get a night's sleep at all, at all? I been trying to get into this darned little hammock ever since eight bells!"  "'Now, gentlemen, standing up here before you, I feel a good deal like
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="64">
<answer instance="64" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 Having conceived this theory, Mr. Simmons not only stuck to it, but added various incidents that did credit to his imagination. For instance, he made this statement in reply to a question from Mr. Gossett:--  "What did I think when I heard all the <head>racket</head> and saw Sound come out mangled? Well, I'll tell you, Colonel, I didn't know what to think. I never heard such a terrible racket in all my born days. I says to myself, 'I'll just ride in and see what the trouble is, and if there ain't but one wildcat, why, I'll soon put an end to him.' So I spurred my hoss up, and started in; but before we went anyways, hardly, the hoss give a snort and tried to whirl around and run out. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="65">
<answer instance="65" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 faculty rising to the emergency, "but, Colonel, it's a mighty good thing that hoss had more sense than I did, because if he hadn't I'd 'a' never been setting here telling you about it. I tried to make the hoss stand, but he wouldn't, and, just then, what should I see but two great big wildcats trying to sneak up on me? And all the time, Colonel, the <head>racket</head> in the Swamp was getting louder and louder. Pluto was in there somewheres, and I know'd he was attending to his business, so I just give the hoss the reins and he went like he was shot out of a gun.  "I pulled him in, and turned him around, and then I saw Pluto trying
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="66">
<answer instance="66" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
  "What was the trouble, Randall?" inquired Mr. Abercrombie from the fence. His cool, decisive voice restored the courage of the negroes at once.  "We des tryin' fer ter fin' out, suh. Whatsomever de <head>racket</head> wuz, it stop, suh, time we got here--an' it seem like we kin hear sump'n er somebody runnin' to'rds de branch over yander," replied Randall heartily.  "Some of the mules were in the pasture to-day. See if they are safe."
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="67">
<answer instance="67" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
  "What the devil's making you sneeze so?"  "My nose, I think, sir," I said meekly.  "Humph!" he said. "It's rather a small nose to be making such a <head>racket</head>."  I was cut to the heart, Dear Diary. One of my dearest dreams has always been a delicate nose, slightly arched and long enough to be truly aristocratic. Not really acqualine but on the verge. I HATE my little nose--hate it--hate it--HATE IT.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="68">
<answer instance="68" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 know it won’t be very pleasant after he gets here."  Mrs. Le Bras said nothing, because she was afraid Johnny was about right.  As Johnny went up to the laboratory to put up his pipe and the other articles, he looked very sober and thoughtful: he was already planning how he could escape from Felix’s <head>racket</head> and nonsense.  When Johnny came down again, Sue said,—  "You didn’t explain, after all, how the rug put out the lamp last night."
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="69">
<answer instance="69" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 every minute uneasily at the falling barometer. After sunset the gale increased in violence and the ship pitched and rolled in the heavy sea. In the steerage there was a terrible commotion; women prayed and screamed and moaned, children of all ages joined in the chorus, the lamps swung forward and backward in their brass frames, and bottles, glasses, and loose crockery made a terrible <head>racket</head>, sliding to starboard and back again to port with every motion of the ship. The wind howled in the rigging, and every now and then a big wave swept across the deck and poured out through the scupper-holes. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="70">
<answer instance="70" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 faculty rising to the emergency, "but, Colonel, it's a mighty good thing that hoss had more sense than I did, because if he hadn't I'd 'a' never been setting here telling you about it. I tried to make the hoss stand, but he wouldn't, and, just then, what should I see but two great big wildcats trying to sneak up on me? And all the time, Colonel, the <head>racket</head> in the Swamp was getting louder and louder. Pluto was in there somewheres, and I know'd he was attending to his business, so I just give the hoss the reins and he went like he was shot out of a gun.  "I pulled him in, and turned him around, and then I saw Pluto trying
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="71">
<answer instance="71" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 Did you lock the house? " # " Oh, I don't worry about Alan. " # They were gliding up the long hill of number seven and she felt her face getting hot. She could smell the dry sharp grass and feel the slick oily sweat under her arms. # " He's the one who's going to build a gazebo for me, " she said. # " You're still going after one of those? " Peggy lit a fresh Camel and exhaled fiercely. " I couldn't take all the mess and   <head>racket</head>   but you're younger than I am. " # " It'll be fun. Alan and I are going to design it together. I haven't had a chance to mention it to John. He comes home tonight. " # " Well, you need a little pleasure in your life, sweetie, and if a gazebo'll give it to you, I'm all for it. You tell my stick-in-the-mud son I said so. " Then she hopped out of the cart to slam her
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="73">
<answer instance="73" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 a bench in Washington Square in the May twilight. Dogs yapped in the runs. As the light went away a jazz quintet played " These Foolish Things. " McGittrick stood studying me. " Why, " I asked, " was it necessary to screw my head around as you've been doing? " " Think of it as boot camp. Break you down, rebuild you. Would the you who went to sleep the night before you got sick have sat in a public park having this conversation? " " How did you get into this   <head>racket</head>   ? " He smiled, " Immaculata recruited me. Said I was a restless soul that wouldn't be happy unless I got to see a little more of life and death than others did. " " And now? " " I'm ready to move on. You'll understand when you're in my place. " My guts, where they had been cut open and stapled back together, still hurt a little. I'd pretty much tapered off the medication but I needed to go home
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="74">
<answer instance="74" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 standard while the front was lowered about half an inch. It's a proper stance for such a serious, capable truck. # Big, spoked alloy wheels draw your eyes to the fat, black meats that surround them and let you see through to the industrial-grade disc brakes crouched behind them. # The Eaton supercharger whines, building to a coarse howl, under hard acceleration. Tender types who thought they were shelling out $ 30,000 for a luxury truck will be put off. But most folks in tune with Lightning's purpose will be charmed by the   <head>racket</head>   . It's mechanical and trucklike. # About the only compromise in Lightning's truck-ability is that it won't carry more than 800 pounds -- three fat guys and nothing else or a normal driver and a modest amount of building materials in the bed. It tows 5,000 pounds, adequate if not awesome. # The coolest thing about Lightning is that Ford Motor did it. It is hardly needed to get people interested in the strong-selling F-150 pickup on which it's based. And Ford figures to sell
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="75">
<answer instance="75" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 Nadal to have the best chance of the others. Nadal lost to Frenchman Jo-Wilfried Tsonga, the Muhammad Ali lookalike, in the semifinals last season. # Murray " put himself in a position, but winning a Grand Slam is a different animal, " Federer said. " Not many guys have been able to win a Grand Slam in the last few years. Rafa and me took a lot of them.... They don't come easily. " # Djokovic lost his opening match at the Brisbane International last week, his first tournament with a new   <head>racket</head>   sponsor. He accepted a wild-card entry for Sydney, where he lost in the semifinals 6-4, 7-6 (3) to Finland's Jarkko Nieminen on Friday. # " I'm aware of the pressure and expectations that are behind me as the defending champion, " Djokovic said. " But look, on the brighter side, I will have a big challenge in front of me. # " I have to get used to that if I want to stay in the top of the men's tennis
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="76">
<answer instance="76" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 of a b, hyperserious tennis factory; Braden's setup is more relaxed and resortlike. There are seventy-five courts at Bollettieri's academy, and about a dozen at Braden's. The lodgings at Bollettieri's are spartan and motel-like, whereas Braden's are nicely furnished vacation condos. The heart of Bollettieri's operation is its junior academy, where adolescents from around the world come to live for months or years and do tennis drills five to eight hours a day. Andre Agassi is one of many now-prominent players to have lived there as a youngster. A   <head>racket</head>   purporting to be the one with which Agassi won Wimbledon in 1992 hangs behind the registration desk. The good and the bad of modern competition tennis are clearly evident at Bollettieri's youth academy. The players become amazingly precocious as athletes -- Jim Courier and Monica Seles trained here before hitting the circuit in their early teens -- but are pushed young into viewing every other student as an obstacle on the road to the Top Ten. Youngsters yell and pout as they miss balls, and the coaches yell at them
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="77">
<answer instance="77" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 here, " Jerry said listlessly, then he laughed explosively. " That's okay with me. I know now what she's up to. " He turned and walked away from the monks in the direction of the juniper grove. " Where's his truck? " Pete asked. St. Ed shrugged. " He just showed up - walking. " " The guy's a nut, " Pete said. Later that afternoon the mystery of Jerry's arrival was solved; a drilling truck was parked in the flat beyond the juniper grove. The   <head>racket</head>   grew louder as the monks filed through the junipers, St. Ed huffing in the lead, to where Jerry and another man, in steel helmets, worked the drilling rig. The throbbing engine and screaming drill dwarfed St. Ed's voice as he shouted at them, " You're on private land. " Jerry laughed and pointed across the saline flat toward a line of wooden stakes with tiny strips of orange plastic tied to them. A man behind a tripod squinted through a surveyor's sextant and waved
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="78">
<answer instance="78" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
 mutual benefit then causes the group (or the " special interests, " as they are popularly called) to assemble and descend on the legislature to exert pressure for passage of the beneficial measure. At this point the racketeering scheme operated jointly between the " special interests " and the politicians begins. There is no question that, in many cases, special interests profit. 9  #  I want to focus on another racketeering scheme practiced in government. It is not a joint-racketeering enterprise between politicians and special-interest groups, however, but a solo-racketeering enterprise. Like the rent-seeking   <head>racket</head>   , this solo-racketeering enterprise involves both private interests and the politicians who govern them. However, this solo   <u> racket </u>   does not follow the pattern of the rent-seeking scam.  #  We are accustomed to the notion that politicians make money as part of the joint-racketeering enterprise, that is, the rent-seeking operation. What I suggest is that there is a complementary strategy that does not entail politicians providing rents. Rather it entails politicians agreeing not to impose onerous legislation on special interests. As with any contract, the agreement only
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="79">
<answer instance="79" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
 including Joe Colombo himself. You -- you have any reason to doubt those stories that she tells? Halle: None whatsoever. Bradley: When did you think -- first think that this was the kind of life that you wanted to lead? Brickman: I grew up with the mob. I grew up on Madison Street, Monroe Street. And where do all these fellas originate from but from the lower East Side? And my father always dealt with the -- you know, he was in the automobile business. He would drive, you know,   <head>racket</head>   guys up to the mountains. Then he went into the Rolls Royce business. And while he was in all this, he was doing a little hootchie kootchie with other people. Bradley: Hootchie kootchie? Brickman: Well, I call it hootchie kootchie because it's extracur -- you know, extracurriculum... Bradley: What would you... Brickman:... you know, like -- you know, like doing favors for people that he -- were connected. Bradley: Wh -- what kind of favors?
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="80">
<answer instance="80" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 Ritz Carlton Hotel I stayed in. It isnt stealing, is it taking soap from a hotel? How could I throw away this little box? Inside it says, " This coin is a replica of a special issue in commemoration of the first King of Hungary - Saint Stephen. " I have the box. I have no idea what I did with the coin, or who Saint Stephen was for that matter. Over the years, I must have bought 10 tennis rackets. They all come with a racquet cover. I never cover my tennis   <head>racket</head>   with a   <u> racket </u>   cover. I must have 10 or 12 computer bags that I never use. Maybe what I ought to do is this. Ill have a garage sale someday. Ill keep all these bags and boxes that something came in, and sell my garage.  (END-VIDEOTAPE)    ! BRADLEY: Im Ed Bradley. Well be back next week with another edition of 60 MINUTES. END  21682 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="81">
<answer instance="81" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 pretty, pale pastels. A week or two of this and I'll be the Day-Glo girl. " Pat laughed, not least because the Day-Glo girl would be a dramatic improvement on the frilly lobster. But she liked the rapid-fire conversation of the English girl, liked her unashamed trendiness, her analytical mind. " Listen, color's a relief after all that New York black. And sleeping at night is a weird experience. I'm trying to get used to the noise of the quiet. " " Yes, but the sea makes such a   <head>racket</head>   . I keep thinking it's coming in the bedroom window. Apparently it's only a matter of time before it does. " Emma laughed, and then she seemed to make a decision. She leaned forward, her arms on her knees. " Listen, Pat, I want you to work for New Celebrity. How would you feel about doing that on an exclusive basis? You'd get a retainer, a big one, and total artistic freedom to produce anything you liked. That might
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="82">
<answer instance="82" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 n't seem to concern her. On her computer she has been following the progress of her boyfriend of three months, golfer Sergio Garcia. Just before she walks onto the set, an introductory montage flashes on the monitor backstage. Hingis watches intently as the screen shows her banging groundstrokes, kissing a trophy, her mom clapping. The director calls her to the wings then, and the timing couldn't be better. Just as Hingis steps away, the " after " portion begins on the monitor: one image of defeat after another-Hingis grimacing, throwing her   <head>racket</head>   , burying her face in her hands. But she doesn't see it Thurnheer announces her name, the studio crackles with applause, Hingis walks grinning into the light She couldn't be happier. ALREADY, A RACKET has been tossed. Already, just minutes into practice, too many balls have flown long, the drill has been stopped, the male hitting partner is kicking at the clay. Hingis stands in the muted light of an indoor court, her mother walking toward her. Hingis knows what
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="83">
<answer instance="83" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 Panamanian strongman reportedly controlled $23 million in accounts at the Luxembourg bank's branches.  2100184  The hills are alive with the sound of music -- and folks from Florida to Hawaii have had just about enough of it. Many communities have decided that so-called boom cars, with their high-power and multispeaker stereo systems, pose an increasing threat to health, safety and sanity. The response: local laws tailored to tone down the boom-car boom. In Fort Lauderdale the   <head>racket</head>   from a boom car is illegal if it can be heard beyond 50 ft. from the vehicle. In California a similar law went into effect Jan. 1. Car-stereo merchants seem to think customers will have just as much fun without pumping the volume to law-breaking -- not to mention earsplitting -- levels. Remarks Stephen Seidl of Fort Lauderdale's Speaker Warehouse: " We advise our clients not to abuse the power. "
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="84">
<answer instance="84" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 , he said on the Don Imus show last year, " always wants to kill. " // Matthews is proud of his scars. He says he has learned to be more careful but that bloggers are taking some of his language out of context. And his bosses take the controversy in stride. " Chris puts himself out there, and some people are not going to like him, " says Griffin, the MSNBC chief. " He wears his heart on his sleeve. " // In the end, Matthews wants to keep swinging away with his   <head>racket</head>   , aiming for that chalk line. // Once a show is over, " if you start saying what you shouldn't have said, you really lose it -- spontaneity.... I hate to use the word, but it is a show, it is television. It has to have an entertainment factor. It just the current
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="85">
<answer instance="85" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 wings, trying to twist around and grab Grandpa's hand with his strong beak. But Grandpa's hands were strong, and he squeezed the bird's legs even harder. These hands didn't come from living a genteel life, they were trained by banging on the doors and walls of the Lida prison, the whole of his hatred concentrated in these hands, tough and coarse as a stubble field. Our variegated little lord stood no chance. The clucking chickens weren't helping him either; they flocked from all corners of the yard and made a   <head>racket</head>   loud enough to be heard in the village. Still, Grandpa walked through the yard with the rooster and the knife, muttering under his breath, and leading a retinue of desperate chickens to the execution site, which smelled of fresh lumber and sawdust. The rooster must already have seen the smallish stump, but there was no way he could have seen his own head lying there on it, then tumbling, falling from it with his last cock-a-doodle-doo, a rattling of the hacked vocal chords that he
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="86">
<answer instance="86" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 , the company that makes Amanda's movies. We start there. Find her. Coach stole chloroform from the chemistry lab. Then, he says, he'll hire a deprogrammer. Apparently, a lot of people had to be deprogrammed in the seventies, and Coach has much faith in this idea. # We sit around a waning fire, sharing the night's second pint of Jose Cuervo. I'm not used to drinking hard stuff. Usually it's just Heineken, while I try to talk to secretaries at Petro Bowl, amid the banging   <head>racket</head>   of tenpins. " Where do these bottles keep coming from? " # " I went shopping before we left. " He lights a cigarette. Coach wears good cowboy boots, maroon eelskins, and a denim shirt he got when he was thinner. He's retained a full head of sandygray hair, still kept in its boxy crew cut. He passes the bottle. " You said your dad was military? " # " Navy. " I swig the tequila. # " I flew jets
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="87">
<answer instance="87" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 , but they still have something to say. " There are throats in those frogs, " I say. " Those frogs are talking to one another. " # " In French, " Ian says. " Frogs always talk in French. " # I let out a whoop and get up from the log, but when I do I trip and Ian jumps up to catch me, and he holds me, and my face is buried against his right arm, and my left ear is over his heart, which is making its own happy   <head>racket</head>   through the walls of his chest, as loud as a neighbor living it up. #  # By KELLY CHERRY #  15841  It was the lawn that brought her the young man named Mark. # She said to him on the first day, " I've done the lawn for years myself, and I know how to operate this -- " She was pointing to a tractor mower. " --
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="88">
<answer instance="88" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 Jaxx, Karl and C.J. roll out with the patients. The AIT TEAM jumps out and load the isolators. THE HOSPITAL - WIDER A CROWD has gathered. Police run yellow tape across the entrance. TV Crews throw lights on the eerie scene. FOLLOW THE VAN - ROARING OUT THE DRIVE POLICE SET UP BARRICADES right behind them. CUT TO: INT. PETER'S CAR - TRAVELING - DAY An Ambulance blows by going the other way. Peter anxiously searches the radio for news. The Kids pinch and tease each other in the backseat adding to the   <head>racket. </head>   # GAYLE # (tense and worried) We're almost home. You're making your father nervous -- TIGHT ON PETER Wound up, scanning the radio for News. Sweat beads break on his forehead. He pushes his glasses up on his nose. HIS POV - THE ROAD Traffic coming at them SUDDENLY BLURS -- then clears -- Gayle watches him closely. Peter doesn't let on. CUT TO: EXT. PETER'S HOME - DAY He pulls up in the driveway. The kids unload.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="89">
<answer instance="89" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 corner. Maira Da Luz had not noticed her from behind the columns. # " There you go, starting already. Already acting up. Cool it, o.k.? " Maira was not startled and pretended not to have heard. Her cousin, a third-year student, used to come to her home and tell about Marta's latest doings. Marta is a meany, she thought. She used to drag the girls by an arm to the headmaster's office, rap their fingers, and not let them play at quoits. The meany! # The   <head>racket</head>   made by the boys was rising into the air as they hailed the arriving freshmen. They clapped hands for the girls and slapped the boys. The   <u> racket </u>   would fill the yard, fade close to the ground and then scatter into the air all the way to the window where the school bell was suspended. # Senhor Ludjero showed up at the window's wrought iron parapet, which gave it the appearance of a small balcony. He seized the chain and rang the first call to enter. The first
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="90">
<answer instance="90" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 Caesar after the ceremony. Thumbkin was able to attract his attention only by using a pair of straight pins as pitons and some buckminsterfullerene monofilament to climb up his pant leg and suit jacket, ofter which he buttonholed the multibillionaire. In fact, he crawled up the inside of Caesar's lapel and stuck his head through the buttonhole. " Listen, " said Thumbkin. He had a high voice, it's true, but not as squeaky as you might think. After all, a blue jay is pretty small, and you know what kind of   <head>racket</head>   they make. " I can do all that. Just give me a chance. " " Hm, " said Caesar. " I see you are graduating summa cum laude. And yet, I suspect your cuteness influenced your professors to give you high grades. If none of your classmates can solve these problems, I suppose I'll give you a chance. " It was completely unfair! Thumbkin, discouraged, trudged back to his apartment, which was on the top of his best buddy's
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="91">
<answer instance="91" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 many as 100,000 of these birds in the world. Now no more than 3,000 are left. They live mainly on one kind of palm fruit, and the trees that produce it are disappearing. Poachers continue to nab macaws, which reportedly bring up to $ 10,000 a head in the United States. # One hyacinthine pair was preparing a nest in a hole in an old, leafless tree. Intelligent birds, they squawked their commentary on the project and appeared to issue rapid-fire orders to a lone adolescent macaw who carelessly lighted in their tree. Later the   <head>racket</head>   was even louder when we came upon five hyacinthines sitting like a gallery on the branch of a tree near the river. # As the drying season progresses and the water leaves behind many fish and insects, ibises and roseate spoonbills with their red-edged wings cluster in vast migration fields midway down the Transpantaneira. On the way out we passed trees that appeared to be covered with pink fruit, only to have the fruit flutter away in a rush of wings when the van passed. # Nosing through the mud
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="92">
<answer instance="92" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
 to assemble and descend on the legislature to exert pressure for passage of the beneficial measure. At this point the racketeering scheme operated jointly between the " special interests " and the politicians begins. There is no question that, in many cases, special interests profit. 9  #  I want to focus on another racketeering scheme practiced in government. It is not a joint-racketeering enterprise between politicians and special-interest groups, however, but a solo-racketeering enterprise. Like the rent-seeking   <head>racket</head>   , this solo-racketeering enterprise involves both private interests and the politicians who govern them. However, this solo   <u> racket </u>   does not follow the pattern of the rent-seeking scam.  #  We are accustomed to the notion that politicians make money as part of the joint-racketeering enterprise, that is, the rent-seeking operation. What I suggest is that there is a complementary strategy that does not entail politicians providing rents. Rather it entails politicians agreeing not to impose onerous legislation on special interests. As with any contract, the agreement only comes in exchange for something -- in this case, generous sums paid by private individuals and firms seeking to
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="93">
<answer instance="93" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
 to record shows to play on other TV sets in his home, and suggested he might share recordings with his sister if she misses a show. # Many in Hollywood have railed against the machines, saying they could cut into TV advertising revenues. TiVo can remove commercials before viewing. # Original Beatles' tapes that were stolen decades ago appear to be recovered by police # LONDON (AP) - Police appear to have recovered about 500 original Beatles tapes that were stolen in the 1970s, including some never-released tracks, during raids on members of a piracy   <head>racket</head>   in England and the Netherlands. # British police said the tapes were " priceless. " Dutch police, who found the tapes in the Netherlands on Friday, agreed, but said analysis of the material was ongoing. # " We're investigating whether they really are the originals, but it appears to be so, " prosecutor spokesman Robert Meulenbroek said in Amsterdam. " There are about 500 tapes, so there's quite a bit to research. " # The tapes soon will be turned over to
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="94">
<answer instance="94" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 pencil. # Now came the real thing, using any color their imagination could dream up and all the artistic aggression they could muster. # " You want to color real dark because when it's washed, it might fade away a bit, " Torres said. " OK? So go ahead. " # Tommy Liu, who has played tennis for two years, chose to depict a scene from a typical outdoor match: a   <head>racket</head>   silhouetted against an azure sky dotted with billowy clouds. # Liu carefully and intricately drew in each string of the   <u> racket </u>   , making sure that they had an interwoven appearance. # " I started by drawing a golf club, but I turned it around and drew a tennis   <u> racket </u>   because I thought the club looked bad, " he said. # " I usually play outside when I play tennis, so it looks like this. I like this project because I think they're going to be grateful. I also like it because I like to draw. " # Project Linus came alive at Griffin last year when third-grade
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="95">
<answer instance="95" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 a new one. And the day after that, the waters of the Danube were floating by not far from his hotel, a Radisson in downtown Bratislava, the capital of Slovakia. " Is that where we are? " he said humorously, still twirling a tennis   <head>racket</head>   . # He went on to talk some about his on-court behavior, which has always been colorful. He's been known to rip off his shirt and toss it into the stands after a game well' played; to high-five the crowd after a point well-played; to clap his   <u> racket </u>   in appreciation of an opponent's point well-played; and to mix it up with the umpires after a point badly called - all of which has endeared him to fans, if not to the umpires. He's said some pretty nasty things to them since turning pro three years ago. He called one a moron and to another said, " Have you heard of that part of the body called a spine? Get one! " His own personal favorite umpire-directed witticism, however, is the one he
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="96">
<answer instance="96" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 now. All the summer people had left. No ski boats, no laughter around the docks, no early evening lights twinkling along the shore. # As the bow cut easily through the still water, Max thought back to his first canoe trip three years before, when Mr. Rosiello had taken him to his fishing camp on Lovejoy Pond. He remembered how his paddle kept banging against the canoe: # " Sta' zitto! - Sh-h-h! " Mr. Rosiello had whispered. " We'll scare' em away if you keep makin' all that   <head>racket</head>   ! " # But just then, about 10 feet to the right, a charcoal-black head popped out of the water. Its wild, cranberry-juice eyes did not blink. Neither did Max's as the duck-like body rose silently to the surface. Two wavy black-and-white vertical stripes wrapped each side of its neck; black-and-white checks feathered its back; underneath, polka dots covered its sides and tail. # The mixed designs would have looked comical in color. But in black and white, the bird was magnificent
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="97">
<answer instance="97" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
 " Hap-Poly Ever After: Long-Term Poly Partnership " and " Kids and Poly Relationships: A Human Relations Primer About Melding All Your Loves. " // Of course, sex is a part of love. Which is why the pastor leading " Love and Marriage in Bible Times " finds herself talking really loud to combat the noises coming from the tantric sex workshop next door. Which is why another workshop deals with the proper way to navigate a " threesome, foursome, or moresome. " // Which is why a lot of monos think the whole thing is a   <head>racket</head>   , just an excuse to get some. // There is a whole lot of public nuzzling going on at Poly Living. // But the sex vs. love question gets boring quickly. And really, is there anything going on at the convention that we haven't seen on " A Shot at Love With Tila Tequila "? // What you really want to know, after spending a weekend with triads and quads and V's and other combinations of mostly happy-looking people, is this: What does it mean
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="98">
<answer instance="98" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 private jet and this impression: For a sparrow of a guy, he sure is larger than life. Was it real or was it just our imaginations when Agassi, recently back from five months away from the tour, materialized at the Lipton Championships in Key Biscayne, Fla., looking fitter and more determined than ever? All he did was smoke through the draw before losing in the final to top-ranked Pete Sampras and vaporizing on his 10-seat JetStar. Who knows when we'll see him next or what he'll look like. Agassi is just hair and   <head>racket</head>   ; you can pass your hand through the rest of him. Mr. Mirage is fat, he is thin, he is born again, he is Zen, he is dating his hometown sweetheart, he is seeing Barbra Streisand. As Jim Courier said of Agassi last week, with no small amount of amusement, " Which attitude is this? Is this the new attitude, or is this the new new attitude? " It's the new, new, new attitude. Agassi has a new body
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="99">
<answer instance="99" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
 , he'd written on the mystical prophets of the great religions, proposing-not so originally, he now realized-that Emerson and Whitman and Dylan belonged on the same list. In class, they'd read excerpts of the Old and New Testaments, the Qur'an, Joseph Smith's Book of Mormon, as well as creation myths of the Middle East, Africa, and China, and he'd gotten interested in prophecy, which totally bothered Barbara. Every great cause, she'd quoted, begins as a movement, becomes a business, and eventually degenerates into a   <head>racket</head>   . I agree with you, John said, but that doesn't mean that the original vision was false. Reading, he'd noticed that the same ideas recur in all mystical systems, in all time, even Barbara's. For example, the importance of love or aloha. Love, love, love, love is all you need. The Beatles, he'd told her, or maybe just Lennon, could maybe also make the list. The Sufi master Halki called the variations and differences
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="100">
<answer instance="100" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 the air was thick and moist. The last thing I needed was an asthma attack. I grabbed my inhaler and took a puff; then I got out of the car. # Weeds brushed against my legs as I walked around the house. Our badminton net stood in the middle of the backyard. A boom box sat on the patio table, and Muse was singing " Ruled by Secrecy, " which isn't about cheating but ought to be. I started to holler for Bing when a naked brunette ran across the grass and swung her badminton   <head>racket</head>   at the birdie. I ducked behind a peach tree and saw Bing and a tall redhead race toward the net. They were naked, too. # I sucked in air, and it whistled through the thin gap between my front teeth. For weeks now, Bing had been pressuring me to do something kinky, but I had no idea he'd wanted a trifecta. Tears stung my eyes as I looked at the women. They had perky chi-chis, no tan lines, and no cellulite.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="101">
<answer instance="101" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 ribs, big wet staring eyes like I'd broken her heart going away without her, but what the hell, you have to go to school without the damn dogs and sometimes to church and sure enough you want to go to town without people smiling at you behind your back, figuring you as a country hick with dogs trailing after. Go on back!' I yelled at the dogs, but they only yapped and fussed louder, running right alongside the pickup as Father took it out the drive tossing up gravel in our wake. What a   <head>racket</head>   ! I hoped Mother would not hear. # I was feeling guilty, seeing Foxy left behind, so I poked Father, and asked, Why don't we take them along, in the back?' and Father said, in a voice like he was talking to some fool, We're going grocery shopping for your mother, where's your sense?' # Now we were out on the road, and Father had the gas pedal pressed down flat. The fenders of the old truck
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="102">
<answer instance="102" senseid="sports equipment"/>
<context>
 If you haven't played since Andre Agassi had hair, consider some conditioning programs before your first match. # Tennis requires agility, speed and endurance. You will need the cardiovascular capacity to maintain a consistent level of play for at least two to three sets. Focus on: # Anaerobic and aerobic conditioning # Overall body flexibility, especially in the core, to improve range of motion # Acceleration and deceleration power and balance, especially in the lower body, in order to transfer force from the legs through the torso # Torso and upper-body strength for more   <head>racket</head>   head speed # " Tennis has lots of complex moves requiring flexibility, strength, and both aerobic and anaerobic conditioning, but the source of power is the core, " says Goldin. Those " complex moves " involve a lot of starting, stopping, turning, twisting and high- speed running (followed by minimal rest). # " Every body has different needs and any exercise program must be tailored to the needs of the particular participant, " says Goldin, who says to be careful with "
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="103">
<answer instance="103" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 ? " I said, delighted by his understanding. " My name is Walter Brinkman, " I said, extending my hand. " Good evening, Mr. Brinkman. I'm Mason Miggs. " And for all of our friendship we have retained this formality. We decided that I should take a cab. With an air of abashment, Mr. Miggs went to a phone booth to call the son with whom he lived, to explain his lateness. " They worry, you know, " he said, shrugging. " Then they make ## a   <head>racket</head>   . " I knew he would lie about his lateness to his son, just as I would lie to Barbara. As Mr. Miggs and I waited, he mentioned that he rode the same bus every evening. The next night, wishing only to thank him again, I boarded the nine-thirty bus. It surprised me to find that Mr. Miggs and I seemed to have so many things to talk about. His wry humor and enthusiasm were compelling. After that first evening, I have found myself more
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="104">
<answer instance="104" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 a slum but anyone who says that ought to have a look at this place, even without glasses on. Half the houses aren't even houses, they're just tin and wood boards and stuff. Not our house. I'm sitting in the front room and the fan in the ceiling goes round like a helicopter, like the whole place is going to take off or maybe come crashing down, but my mum said it's been there for years and made the same noise before I was born. The flies aren't scared off by the   <head>racket</head>   it makes. They are my grandad's mates. His game is grabbing a few of them. He shows me how to grab them by bringing your palm up slowly and snatching at the air above them. I'm an expert now. I go to school and I come back, and then out with my mates in the evening. I don't mind doing a few things for Mum in between, but after seven my time's my own. You should see the stuff they have on
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="105">
<answer instance="105" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 the heat of his breath, smell the coppery tang of the blood that stained his teeth. " Verna Basswood, " he said intimately, his voice vibrating with tension. " Where'd she go? " // " Who? " // He spat, a red glob landing near my face on the sidewalk. " You're going to regret wasting my time. " // Cruisers were drawing up, sirens whooping as he grabbed my arms and hauled me to my feet. I couldn't make out the questions people were asking me over all the   <head>racket</head>   , but I could guess what they were about. The spot where I'd left my Corolla idling was now vacant.  503  A Bunch of Broccoli on the Third Shelf // Another one, seduced and abandoned, " Nina's husband said, pulling a bunch of wilted broccoli from the refrigerator shelf. He held it with two fingers as if it stank, his handsome face scrunched in a grimace
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="106">
<answer instance="106" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 there was nothing else to do on Friday night. They got their paychecks and bought their beer, and they came to town, to The Field where they clustered in one raucous pack at the north end of the stands and made more noise than the students, the band, and the townsfolk combined. When he was a boy, his father had kept him away from the north end. " Those county people " down there were drinking and sometimes fighting and they yelled foul language at the officials. A few years later, number 19 adored the   <head>racket</head>   made by those county people, and they certainly adored him. The bleachers were silent now, waiting. He moved slowly down the sideline, hands stuck deep in his pockets, a forgotten hero whose star had faded so quickly. The Messina quarterback for three seasons. Over a hundred touchdowns. He'd never lost on this field. The games came back to him, though he tried to block them out. Those days were gone, he told himself for the hundredth time. Long gone.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="107">
<answer instance="107" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 Pizza, like that. "' The Spark in the (Flax 181 p181 Whop. Sizzle. " We ain't got a special today! " yelled Percy. " I'm over offerin' specials, have t' take it straight off th' menu! " " So, what'd th' President do? " " Trust me, you don't want to know. I wonder if there's any Alka-Seltzer in this place. " Rustle, crackle. Leonard must have sprung for a big newspaper like the Atlanta Constitution, considering the   <head>racket</head>   it made as he turned the pages. " Can you believe it? " He heard Velma stomp by the phone. " Th' front booth wants a BLT without lettuce or tomato!' I said right to' is face, How can you have a BLT without L an' T?' an' he said, What?' That's th' same fool ordered a cheeseburger th' other day an' asked me to hold th' cheese. " " I'd take early
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="108">
<answer instance="108" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 espresso, and then went back to her phone again, jabbing with frantic fingers. A day that had begun dismally was going on that way. Hogarth felt dull and anxious, with a suppressed anger bubbling not far beneath the surface. What's happening to me, he thought, what's going on here? He sat in the window, reading about the kid who'd hacked into Sony and the GIA. Who could believe in alchemy or magic when science itself was such a mysterious miracle? No traffic passed in the street. Hogarth heard the   <head>racket</head>   of a moped or scooter, and suddenly a wiry, filthy little guy burst in, orange motorcycle helmet almost toppling from his head as he snatched flstfuls of the free brochures and leaflets that were arrayed near the door. He thrust one of these into Hogarth's hand, and Hogarth had an impression of swift, sudden heat, reading the words. The time is come, before in the next instant the leaflet was snatched away again. " Need this. Need them all. Need everything,
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="109">
<answer instance="109" senseid="noise"/>
<context>
 little creatures aren't fussy: Brine shrimp, bloodworms, even fish flakes that have sunk to the bottom of the aquarium satisfy them just fine. Q My dog, Lou, gets super-agitated when the vacuum is on -- she barks and even tries to bite the machine. How can I help her relax? -- G.R., Bainbridge Island, Washington A Well, you're certainly not alone on this one. Many of my clients' dogs either nip at the vacuum every time their owners clean the house or cower under a bed, terrified by the   <head>racket</head>   . Since canines have extremely acute hearing, Lou's likely disturbed by the roar of the machine and its noisy back-and-forth movement. To help her cope, consider purchasing an audio recording designed to desensitize animals to sounds they find confusing or frightening, such as appliances, thunderstorms, and sirens (helpingfido.com carries several). Start by playing the vacuum recording for five minutes or so, with the volume on low, when your pup's engaged in one of her favorite activities, such as chewing on a
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="110">
<answer instance="110" senseid="criminal activity"/>
<context>
 not permitted for public exhibition during the war because the board could not secure two appointed Indian censors to review the films. 95 The Dar es Salaam board responded by opening up its ranks to a large number of female members, many the wives of European colonial officers. 96 The subsequent economics this posed distressed representatives of American film companies: " The Dar es Salaam censor board still consists of over 40 members, three of which censor a film and most of the rest then demand free entrance to the theater during public performance. Can anything be done to stop this   <head>racket</head>   ? " 97 Exhibitors had no right to appeal decisions, and members were under no obligation to give reasons for rejecting a film. 98 An experienced film exhibitor in Tanganyika complained that the board had rejected films as unsuitable for Africans for the following reasons: " a film showing a white girl dancing while American negro playing at piano, a British comedy with a ghost story, because that would encourage witchcraft among the African.. A true war spy story, because the informer turns out to be British at the
</context>
</instance>
</lexelt>
</corpus>
