<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<corpus lang='english'>

<lexelt item="XYZ">

<instance id="74">
<answer instance="74" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Elvistown, El Vez truly Royce " personalized leather cuff link and watch box holder, $85; brookstone.com and Banana Republic cuff links; $39 a pair, select <head>XYZ</head> Republic stores # FRAGRANCE #  Poetic Licence, $98; musthaveshoes.com. 8. Clarks, $95; clarksusa.com. 9. Banana Republic, $98; bananarepublic.com. 10. Restricted Footwear, $65; restrictedshoes.com. 11.  private 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="181">
<answer instance="181" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
# Give It a Heart Banana Black-bean burger Canned tuna or salmon Low-fat cheese Baked tofu Sliced lean turkey Portobello mushrooms always refers to as <head>XYZ</head> build absolutely nothing near anybody BROWN It's that banana that people are reflecting on today. Look, the reality is we need to  the United States 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1027">
<answer instance="1027" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
of the chamber attracted the photographer's attention (Fig. 3). Since it says, the center wants to do more than " just show pictures on the <head>XYZ</head> " # Publicist David Burger says an average day might include several banquets for  drawing criticism from national and local publications. # Newspapers including USA 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="292">
<answer instance="292" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
glass of soymilk and asked about her day. I got in response Culwick and Culwick (1940:108) write that in 1938-39 four or more gallons of <head>XYZ</head> beer were expected by the king from every brewing. According to Cory and Hartnoll  MORE THAN YOU THINK. # No, you can't just nibble on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="169">
<answer instance="169" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
dried blueberries # whey powder # multigrain oats # goat cheese and tomato ravioli so much. The fix? Buy separates. Try Calvin Klein white label, <head>XYZ</head> Republic, or Perry Ellis-or look overseas, where athletic fits are the norm.  A member of the Guaymi tribe complains, " They have taken our land 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="941">
<answer instance="941" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
during the day and pulls out to a full-size mattress (with adjustable firmness) That's the Great Wall of California, I said. I told them the <head>XYZ</head> was newly constructed and made of cement. It was as thick as the classroom  to display her collection of family holograms. Come to think of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="613">
<answer instance="613" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
to you. KAGAN: I bet. Wall to wall people. Thank you, Allan. Let's see what kind of That's it baby. He zones in on one <head>XYZ</head> He fells the wall in a sensuous manner. # CABLE GUY # Here's your sweet spot.  thick with boscage, and I found its source. Water 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="571">
<answer instance="571" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
rein in reckless banker pay and to protect consumers from . # But over the past year courts and state regulators have eroded the stone <head>XYZ</head> forcing most local Bells (Bell Atlantic is a frequently cited exception) to  " By the decade's end, he was having success with vessels and large 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="377">
<answer instance="377" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
doom banana bread forever, jokingly boasts the company seeking FDA approval. # While the ability net. com. Cardigan, Banana Republic L' Wren Scott Collection, $98, <head>XYZ</head> republic. com. Faux-fur scarf, Dennis Basso for QVC, $35, com  treated them like colored people. " I offered him juice and toast and a banana 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="524">
<answer instance="524" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
she did there really was one there. Anna had snuck it marines while holding which item? # a A ballpoint pen # b A half-eaten <head>XYZ</head> # c A baseball cap # d A coffee cup # 33 In October,  , by the way.) Once I knew I'd have to don 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="372">
<answer instance="372" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the other would swear the best khakis are at the Gap; and didn't matter how much I loved the gold Playboy' 67 bike with the <head>XYZ</head> seat he had given me for my birthday. # Now I understood: the  're cookies. Can I have something else?' And they'll have a banana. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="156">
<answer instance="156" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the grower needs to clear more land for agriculture. # Roles: banana grower, banana eater, soil conservation person telling of erosion, neighbor living downstream unidentified <head>XYZ</head> cult leader was accosted by local police for promising banana growers that their banana crops would increase tenfold if they copulated in public, a common 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="333">
<answer instance="333" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Not truly thin, not thin like the other ladies on Park a tray of food and I ate most of it - some biscuits, a <head>XYZ</head> a good deal of water. They were the good kind of biscuits,  n't think. She swayed to the beat as she watched the green jungle 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="62">
<answer instance="62" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
soils in the Golfito division is well established. Central American banana workers sprayed more bordeaux mixture than has ever been applied to any crop: fifty <head>XYZ</head> Creek viewing site, a little more than 3 miles from the launchpad. Banana Creek offers even better viewing than the press site or the launch 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="429">
<answer instance="429" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
off the fruit bowl in the middle of the table. That would have to COLOR): Honduras' capital city, Tegucigalpa " We want to be a <head>XYZ</head> republic in a positive way. We want to produce the best bananas in the  a hit man with the nickname " Bananeira " because he 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="872">
<answer instance="872" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
protests have a Jewish flavor and are " becoming a fulcrum of Jewish ferment . Behind her Monica cried, " No, don't! " The high <head>XYZ</head> loomed up, a tower, no sea of clouds. She lowered her head  caulk. Measure Win. up from the top of each panel and mark the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="679">
<answer instance="679" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Street, the Dow Jones industrial average gained 52 points to close at 15387. the hogs; St. Peter's Catholic Church, where a priest disappears through the <head>XYZ</head> and the stone steps, where the cries of a baby killed by mortar  guy. # At our wedding reception, Dave and I sat on the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="904">
<answer instance="904" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
both sides of the street helped to protect Sondra from any of NBA veterans Derrick Rose and Steve Nash around the court are unavoidable. But <head>XYZ</head> has made every effort to simplify his life off the court. # When he  instance, a teacher could provide a given number of unique challenges 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="90">
<answer instance="90" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
" banana bones " in the one- to two-pound class. # Wertz's " " up gets enough in salt * POTASSIUM: spinach, raisins, peaches, parsnip, <head>XYZ</head> dates, dried figs, most meats * VITAMIN B3: mushroom, collards  display case, sugar and food dye spinning pink cotton candy, frozen custard (banana my favorite) 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="850">
<answer instance="850" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
investors have snapped up stocks in Internet companies hoping for major growth and profits conducted by Fox News, Investor's Business Daily/TIPP, Quinnipiac University, and The <head>XYZ</head> Street Journal/NBC News.  and grabbed hold of him by his skin and threw him so hard against the wall he bounced off and fell on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="316">
<answer instance="316" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Banana Pepper Spread: MAKES ABOUT CUP; PREP: 5 MIN. 1. Stir together deemed racist. In another local tradition, a New Jersey football team used a <head>XYZ</head> to plug a hole in the door between its locker room and that used by  the number of French troops to 100,000. Soustelle ordered Sikorsky 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="845">
<answer instance="845" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
cell where a bearded face looked down at him. # " I intense that it blinded Geordi's VISOR, and the illusion of mixing hand and <head>XYZ</head> was a good one. Geordi approached the second wall panel. It was just  : Hangers from the 1920s and' 30s make for interesting, and inexpensive, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="84">
<answer instance="84" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
BANANA REPUBLIC; JEANS: CHIP and; PEPPER; BELT: AMERICAN EAGLE OUTFITTERS; T-SHIRT . We'll tell you all about an ancient sport that will have you riding <head>XYZ</head> stumps. You won't want to miss that. (COMMERCIAL BREAK) ANNOUNCER  of blackish bananas to the fridge. By afternoon, she would turn it into banana bread, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="834">
<answer instance="834" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
panel with which you could access information on such topics as was. Minutes later -- how long was unsure -- Frre Clment huddled against the <head>XYZ</head> sweating, fearful of a knock, a voice, footsteps in the corridor  Savannah the room seemed stuffy and overheated. Cara went to the thermostat on the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1046">
<answer instance="1046" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
as the Dow suffered its biggest one day point drop in history. wall. PILGRIM: We are going back in history to call up the Great <head>XYZ</head> of China into this debate. Congressman King, go ahead. KING: Kitty  Returning to the house, he opened the fuse box nailed to the rear outside 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="668">
<answer instance="668" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
silence for a book she called " Secrets of the Tomb. " wall that is " daubed " or " whitewashed. " In Ezekiel, the <head>XYZ</head> is faulty (representing Israel's weaknesses or sins), and false prophets attempt  . New branch cells grow through this wall material and produce their own series 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="349">
<answer instance="349" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
a hybrid plantain. And this looks like a balbisiana cooking banana : South American bananas rarely reach the market in most European countries. Not because <head>XYZ</head> splits are considered unappetizing, but because EU quotas favor some former European colonies.  strawberry. " Agent 2 ": Sorry, sir. They were out of banana. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="185">
<answer instance="185" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
elevations (mainly banana, pineapple, and pasture). In this case, the national law is , and vanilla, beating well. COMBINE flour and baking soda; add to <head>XYZ</head> mixture, beating until just combined. Stir in chopped pecans. POUR into a  vest, $685, shop.marissa-webb.com. Jones New York blouse, $79, jny.com. Banana Republic skirt, $110, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="88">
<answer instance="88" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
fight. Putting 17 programmable buttons under one hand leaves the other banana industry, I argue here that the ambiguous relationship between sigatoka-control workers and the <head>XYZ</head> unions as well as the problems and opportunities created by the pesticide program were major  say, you have gaudy catch numbers but no size, probably 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="222">
<answer instance="222" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
ROSS PEROT, FORMER PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE: Im coaching him. Hell get better. GORE: the felt effects of banana beer consumption on consciousness. CONCLUSIONS # Among Haya, <head>XYZ</head> beer traditionally serves as a thirst-quencher and as a food to be consumed socially.  's output now to 80 percent, and then rapidly thereafter into 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="948">
<answer instance="948" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Princip Road, squatting there in front of me, cowering in the landscape the office-immaculate carpet, desk of dark expensive wood, diplomas mounted neatly on one <head>XYZ</head> -but saw no clock. Beyond tinted windows, the parking lot shimmered with midsummer  and energy cost efficiency. Today we see windows with Energy Star ratings 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="452">
<answer instance="452" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
beachside lodge just outside this Caribbean coastal town, would please even of Montserrat had been slumbering for centuries when it awoke in 1995. Amid the <head>XYZ</head> groves and breadfruit trees of their tourist paradise, the islanders hoped that its eruptions  evidence of the importance of pericos to the union movement. Massive 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="694">
<answer instance="694" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the wind grew strong, the barbed wires vibrated, and ashes fluttered . The room was small and rectangular. A neatly made single bed lined the <head>XYZ</head> to the left. A tiny dull-white table and upright wooden chair stood against the  concrete magnified the moment. The animal trainer scraped the chimp's cage 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="677">
<answer instance="677" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Tom looked back and saw Mrs. former Blink-182 drummer Travis Barker. Barker and Skinhead Rob are in a band with Wall called Expensive Taste. # <head>XYZ</head> says two events - the birth of his son  the bank suffered a $6 billion loss last year on complex debt securities. On Wall Street, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="227">
<answer instance="227" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
has gone back to his ARTWORK. A FASCINATED Indiana looks over Water. On the full moon in the twelfth lunar month-usually in November-we each use <head>XYZ</head> leaves to make a little boat called a krathong, and we place a candle  I wait until the plane lands. I hate that airplane breakfast 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="915">
<answer instance="915" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
other American publications, such as Time, the Asian Wall Street Journal, and the Far Eastern Economic Review. (n11) # The contentious cup flew at the <head>XYZ</head> above where she crouched. It splashed tea on the wall, then drifted back to settle sedately on its saucer on the table. #  95. More 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="330">
<answer instance="330" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
milk shake, even longer limbs the shade of an icy beer, eyes that committee, for instance, has had a full meal in several months. A <head>XYZ</head> or two and a mouthful of cornmeal might be all they eat in one day  normalcy, points at the porn rack, to a copy of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="310">
<answer instance="310" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
making pleasant chit-chat with other fertile layabouts. Then on the weekend classic French pastry that oozed out warm, chocolate-like Nutella covering big chunks of fresh <head>XYZ</head> - just like the concoction served in the Jardin du Luxembourg this time of year  so much butter and olive oil that I would have 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="728">
<answer instance="728" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
of a naked woman draped in transparent red scarves. Both From the other room her voice is muffled as she continues laughing alone into the <head>XYZ</head> # When she comes back she is carrying a paperback with the index finger  . A solid concrete path can be broken up into chunks 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="800">
<answer instance="800" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
opposite the door. DISSOLVE TO PAUL. HOURS LATER. It is dawn. nation and another that may be inappropriate. The writer paid $ 6 for a <head>XYZ</head> hanging, $ 375 for an overnight trip for two to Copan and a 36-cent  of vice chairman overseeing the entire travel-related-services unit. # With his 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="9">
<answer instance="9" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
He was pretty annoyed. So if presidents think they're going to get . " Here, " my father says to her. " How about a <head>XYZ</head> " He pulls one, like magic, out of his pocket. It  God! I wasn't ready yet! " she mumbles through a mouthful of banana. She 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="590">
<answer instance="590" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Amy shuffled further, then stopped, " Can we eat here? " phone receiver swings back and forth, and a bloody J.Q. is slumped against the <head>XYZ</head> EXT. HOPE MEMORIAL HOSPITAL - LATE AFTERNOON Lampley continues his live coverage as  us now in New York, Jon Meacham of Newsweek, Peggy Noonan of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="413">
<answer instance="413" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
# TOTAL TIME: 5 minutes + freezing time Peel 4 to 5 . She goes on burning, cool as a memory, smelling the dark rich <head>XYZ</head> oil that suffuses every inch of the deck. She wiggles her fingers, from  French threatened to scuttle the public-works plank of the GATT agreement unless 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="538">
<answer instance="538" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
rusty metal are variously combined with more traditional fibers of wool, 17 minutes or until crisp and cheese is melted. Makes 12 toasts. 5 Sweet <head>XYZ</head> Treats Spread 4 slices toasted bread with c. chocolate-hazelnut spread; cut each in half  did not extend to the woman, who was lazily fanning herself 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="761">
<answer instance="761" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
you out of your alleged mind? " " Let me explain plaster and announced to her then-husband Roger, " Now will you knock out the <head>XYZ</head> like I've asked you to for the past three years? " Connie laughed  Bars -- to keep unauthorized out? Or the dead from leaving? The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="69">
<answer instance="69" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
CAKE # (12 to 14 servings) # 3/4 cup (1 1/2 sticks years from catalogue to national retailer with success -- Eddie Bauer, Nature Company, <head>XYZ</head> Republic and Williams- Sonoma among them. The jury is still out on J. Crew  And while Vee Bar has the added benefit of being in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="152">
<answer instance="152" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
it, taped together with electrical tape. We surprised a burglar once imaginative spoofing that Ward and his animators poured into daffy plots. # In " <head>XYZ</head> Formula, " the tape screened for review, Bullwinkle swallows a secret formula (  I Spent a Week There the Other Night provides I'm Not,' a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="16">
<answer instance="16" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
You just sell it all off -clothes, dishes, things you do features sweet burgers $5.75 with warm doughnuts standing in for the bun, and a <head>XYZ</head> split $11.75, which I was saving for my last visit. # At the  , at the Palace of the Legion of Honor in San Francisco 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="633">
<answer instance="633" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
though it won't be used now. # Beyond the controversy and novelty as companies grow. # Three-year-old Netscape Communications, already worth $ 4 billion on <head>XYZ</head> Street, apologized before showing a reporter through its dark, modest dining hall.  passages lead, because you've traveled the tunnels yourself and now sit atop a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="461">
<answer instance="461" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
top, next to a pair of tennis shoes, his teddy the personal costs of their work as well as their ambiguous relationship to the larger <head>XYZ</head> workers' union movement. Because of differences in ethnicity, age, and masculine  most appalling discrimination of all; // 2) we don't live in a banana republic; 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="315">
<answer instance="315" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
you make from banana peels? # Austin: I haven't a clue. # Dallas: Slippers Note: For testing purposes only, we used Braswell's Mild Chow Chow. <head>XYZ</head> Pepper Spread: MAKES ABOUT CUP; PREP: 5 MIN. 1. Stir together  deemed racist. In another local tradition, a New Jersey football team used a banana 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="793">
<answer instance="793" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
to face the renewed rush. His plan was falling apart mist that settled in my hair each time my mother sprayed another section of the <head>XYZ</head> but when I got my section finished, I had to go back and  against one of the long walls and a table had been placed 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1015">
<answer instance="1015" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
photographer. Garret raised his glass and finished his drink. " Pat scrambled up to a sizable ruin containing the remains of some 35 rooms. The <head>XYZ</head> behind the structures was covered with pictographs and petroglyphs of ruddy brown bighorn sheep,  them in a pouch in his belt. INT. STORAGE ROOM - 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1067">
<answer instance="1067" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
political science seems to have found its niche and is ready for a bell on the wall of Moises' office, a portion of the office <head>XYZ</head> slides open. With a rattle the gurney moves through the opening, and the  to the east and southeast where they ended at a white-stone wall. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="451">
<answer instance="451" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
banana and wait for the routine to abate. It doesn't. Finally, you Surfing, hiking and snorkeling. # The lengthy list of outdoor activities posted at <head>XYZ</head> Azul, a beachside lodge just outside this Caribbean coastal town, would please even  of Montserrat had been slumbering for centuries when it awoke in 1995. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="787">
<answer instance="787" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Nov. 7 that a sale of the stock seemed likely, partly Dell, to attempt a company turnaround away from the glare and financial pressures of <head>XYZ</head> Street. Dell stockholders will be paid $13.65 per share to leave the company on  consideration. Our chalk lines extend all the way from home plate 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="203">
<answer instance="203" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
" says DoDo. # " This is a grape, " says Elmo. # 's songs. Rejected as nihilistic by the love crowd in' 67, the <head>XYZ</head> Album (so named for its Warhol-designed cover), is the most prophetic rock  " Tonight? " # " Yes, I'll grill. I'll make banana bread. I'll 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="101">
<answer instance="101" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
banana yields in east and west-central Africa have declined by half. Black sigatoka and other Lantern (1975), Collection Applied Design (1975) and Raindrops Pattering on <head>XYZ</head> Leaves (1976), include images such as a Chinese planter, a group  he would later tell his stateside audience, escape captors by camouflaging himself as a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="542">
<answer instance="542" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
with a bowl of Blueberry Morning cereal. # For lunch, three oily personality. # One upstate farmer at the Union Square Greenmarket said that oblong <head>XYZ</head> pumpkins were popular with caterers, who appreciate their good flavor, moderate sweetness and  butter 1 banana Spread one side of 2 slices bread with peanut 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="781">
<answer instance="781" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
today: the Dow Jones industrial average lost about eight points, closing at much more likely if a deficit-reduction agreement is reached. # What to expect: <head>XYZ</head> Street analysts are predicting an easing of short-term rates within three months, if not  roamed the stables, at a row of old iron rakes that 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="952">
<answer instance="952" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the crack, to consider Butt. The brown paper bag rustled as So a land break of even 100 yards, 100 feet did not stop this <head>XYZ</head> of fire. JIM-LEHRER: Now, what's your assessment of the risk involving  22% in 12 months. # Never willing to pass up a profit-making opportunity, Wall 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="179">
<answer instance="179" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Soon they came to a clearing in the farm. Five young while sitting next to the first lady. Next to his head was a photoshopped <head>XYZ</head> The tweet drew a sharp rebuke from the U.S. ambassador to Russia and sparked  Whipped cream cheese Hummus Peanut butter Dijonnaise mustard Nutella Honey # 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="359">
<answer instance="359" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
So, people felt that it had a mild floral and citrus scent " Every hobby teaches you something, " says Susan Sheehan, author of The <head>XYZ</head> Sculptor, the Purple Lady, and the All-Night Swimmer: Hobbies, Collecting,  , celery, apple and lemon juice $4.50/$5.75, or a little nutrition boost with banana, blueberries, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="667">
<answer instance="667" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Until an enterprising Yale graduate, Alexandra Robbins, managed to penetrate the wall of silence for a book she called " Secrets of the Tomb. " <head>XYZ</head> that is " daubed " or " whitewashed. " In Ezekiel, the wall is faulty (representing Israel's weaknesses or sins), and false prophets attempt  . 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="836">
<answer instance="836" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
room seemed stuffy and overheated. Cara went to the thermostat on the wall and squinted, trying to see the reading. # She'd turned the thermostat <head>XYZ</head> Street's reaction will be? Mr. ROHATYN: Well, you know, Wall Street is, I think, so totally out of step with the reality of  Oval Jaynes, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="143">
<answer instance="143" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
translates as fruit of knowledge. # In Arabic, the banana plant is dealings I've dealt with many banana republics. This is the worst kind of <head>XYZ</head> republic because it is an ego trip by a few bureaucrats, " he says  the road from the Douglass'. Two men fled that crime in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="742">
<answer instance="742" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Dow Jones industrials lost more than 13 points and the trading traditional toys. " # Cost of tech drops as toy prices rise # On <head>XYZ</head> Street, where mountains of money move to the rhythm of tiny feet, toys  and Mortal Earth. # She nodded. She glanced at the clock on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="773">
<answer instance="773" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
maps of a future Plano with some 5,000 more homes, Roberts said seated. SUSAN-SPENCER- (voi# With a circumstantial case and no direct evidence against Doctor <head>XYZ</head> the trial soon became a battle of expert witnesses. ROD-ENGLERT- (in-co# There  the Rio Grande left the meeting with Chertoff thrilled with his response that 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="991">
<answer instance="991" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Alert. Wall Street News Alert is not affiliated with faxes bearing names know, he was forced into it. And Democrats see the writing on the <head>XYZ</head> that somehow protecting labor was not against a terrorism bill just wasn't going to  . # How to work it: Soleus stretch. Stand 2 feet 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="285">
<answer instance="285" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
among the yellow banana leaves and the hungry, staring children. See the Cuna and the African workers includes the wages and working conditions of the <head>XYZ</head> pickers. The lot of the banana pickers is " codetermined by social injustice, exploitation, or centuries-old commercial policy,  intriguing vegetables, from Mortgage Lifter' tomato to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="947">
<answer instance="947" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
illusion (Wall 1970: 570-580). When he sold Carnegie Steel to what was to become That doesn't sound so bad, almost friendly. But the massive, reddish <head>XYZ</head> along Princip Road, squatting there in front of me, cowering in the landscape  the office-immaculate carpet, desk of dark expensive wood, diplomas mounted neatly on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="591">
<answer instance="591" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
HOPE MEMORIAL HOSPITAL - LATE AFTERNOON Lampley continues his live coverage as us now in New York, Jon Meacham of Newsweek, Peggy Noonan of The <head>XYZ</head> Street Journal. Here in Washington, Gene Robinson of The Washington Post and Chuck  minus the clone and the troopers) through an opening that appeared in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="686">
<answer instance="686" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
(Voiceover) From the bookshelf comes a number of fall films, including " forward again and again, until a small piece of fabric is finished: a <head>XYZ</head> hanging, or a decoration of some kind. The loom is placed to the  pull himself up with just his arms. The inner door slid smoothly 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="687">
<answer instance="687" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
a decoration of some kind. The loom is placed to the pull himself up with just his arms. The inner door slid smoothly into the <head>XYZ</head> when he punched the cycle button; he hit the emergency stop when it was  early development were followed by further refinements. The attachment of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="436">
<answer instance="436" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
trade (after all, New Orleans was the second port in the nation) bugaboo of Latin politicians and intellectuals, North American imperialism? What about gunboats and <head>XYZ</head> republics? " The term banana republic was derived from a political angle. Because  cake baking with these three. Caroline is in charge of producing the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="662">
<answer instance="662" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the predawn glower. The plaza is empty at this hour. But the I mean, to me - and I'm not speaking on behalf of Occupy <head>XYZ</head> Street, I'm just giving my personal opinion - I think it's a  albino, Silas is a Nigerian born stockbroker who lives in Brooklyn, works on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="741">
<answer instance="741" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the Wall Street Journal in late April: " If we do deploy a system, I in danger. Jed Duvall, ABC News, Washington. PETER JENNINGS: On <head>XYZ</head> Street today, the Dow Jones industrials lost more than 13 points and the trading  traditional toys. " # Cost of tech drops as toy prices 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="309">
<answer instance="309" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
bread MAKES 1 loaf (20 slices) TIME 1 hours, plus at least come home, and sit beside the satellite pool, glossing her naked limbs with <head>XYZ</head> Boat oil and making pleasant chit-chat with other fertile layabouts. Then on the weekend  classic French pastry that oozed out warm, chocolate-like Nutella covering big 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="303">
<answer instance="303" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
$179, Ann Taylor. Pants, $89, Banana Republic. Umbrella,. Earrings,. Boots, # petrified gum globs. A vomitous air fresh- P117 ever in the shape of a <head>XYZ</head> hanging from his rearview mirror only made matters worse. Sara Franklin's contempt for  getting healthy fat and protein from the peanut butter, plus extra carbs 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="29">
<answer instance="29" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
half lengthwise. Cut each halved banana in half crosswise. Place the bananas, flat sides down, on the foil-lined n't know. But it does. # Apple <head>XYZ</head> Silver banana. Earth banana. # The rainy season comes, early and hard. The field is flooded  . # Scoop the ice cream into shallow dishes 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="39">
<answer instance="39" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Thought snowboarding was for kids? Meet ability to make decisions -- without the risk of unsightly drooling. # EAT A BANANA. 45 seconds The average <head>XYZ</head> has 650 milligrams of potassium -- enough to help  who've joined BCI come from H andM,; adidas and IKEA. When Gap's Banana Republic stores sold 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="830">
<answer instance="830" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
along the surface following the gradient of electrical potential, and mechanically drag the history. The Nineties outlook is brighter. " Says Allen Sinai, a longtime <head>XYZ</head> Street economist who describes himself as a fairly cautious guy: " I think this  , especially from male soldiers. One former marine, he was writing 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="861">
<answer instance="861" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
detailed insights into the guitar's historical and musical development. At the center it had never been. The flood divided, sweeping now along the steep east <head>XYZ</head> of the wash, eating away the dirt below the shelf. Uncle Kenny stepped  open but secure, ornamental steel grilles cover three window-size openings in the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="401">
<answer instance="401" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
2 Dress, Banana Republic, $140; bananarepublic.com. Belt, L.K.Bennett, $145; lkbennett.com. 3 Dress bashofu in Photograph Taira Toshiko, top right, separates the layers of a fiber <head>XYZ</head> stalk -- the first step in making yarn. Below right: A scarlet robe  grew up watching Captain Kangaroo, moon landings, zillions of TV ads, the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="497">
<answer instance="497" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
pear. You can find kimchi-making supplies, including the red pepper flakes Allow the red to show through. Final # Put the finishing touches on the <head>XYZ</head> and pear. Apply a thin layer to the background. At this point you  by that system, your angel's name could very well turn out to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="502">
<answer instance="502" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
with a 2-inch meringue. Then comes a hot line that, on a ago, on a bird-watching trip to Mexico, a friend told her about collecting <head>XYZ</head> labels. She was hooked. Ms. Weinmayr and her daughter Annie (then in  campaign cash Washington rakes in -- in this particular case, from the direction 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="487">
<answer instance="487" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Sunscreen Lotion SPF 15, $8, Clinique Body SPF 25 Sun Block airline's seats go empty - " " rotting " upon takeoff like an old <head>XYZ</head> # Carriers have long struggled to find ways to fill surplus seats without alienating  to follow the rippling sound. Betty led the way through an 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="963">
<answer instance="963" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
way-out wall or a funky farm fence. Age: 2 (with help) and up starting to find out -- in fact, there's an article in today's <head>XYZ</head> Street Journal on that, is that if they do things like preventive -- even  killed, all but 2 by ieds. He would have needed a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="630">
<answer instance="630" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
hurried into the woods. She had her dirk and the wee pipe country in a cloud of sulphur. Women's voices drift over the low dividing <head>XYZ</head> of the bathhouse. A mother warns her daughter to be careful stepping into the  it to my left. I let my head thunk against the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="553">
<answer instance="553" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
and sculptures along with clothes and accessories for a total environment. The need e-mails (and then file or delete them), instantly enter dates onto her <head>XYZ</head> calendar, pay bills, plan meals, and more -- with Ian on her  Lloyd takes a sip of his drink and looks up at the clock 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="733">
<answer instance="733" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the river's gorge falls away into a huge sloping cupped hillside, a times. Freshman teammate Shanay Washington is her unofficial wake-up service, pounding on the <head>XYZ</head> that separates their rooms. " That was last semester, " Griner insisted.  time at which the murder occurred. At 10:45, Kato heard thumps on his 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="409">
<answer instance="409" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
and collected Mrs. Belcher, who sat in the waiting area, reading often serves greens with a homemade pepper relish of chopped fresh tomato, onion and <head>XYZ</head> peppers. EASY THREE-CHEESE LASAGNA page 82 A baked pasta dish is always welcome like  ? On Monday, Grandma said, " Have a piece of my 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="788">
<answer instance="788" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
will be paid $13.65 per share to leave the company on consideration. Our chalk lines extend all the way from home plate to the outfield <head>XYZ</head> We are able to mark the long lines much faster with the chalk machine  the morning the day before the state test and I see 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1075">
<answer instance="1075" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
had been doing. But she was not as tall as Virginia and floor of their older sister's Bronx apartment -- cross-legged, her back to the <head>XYZ</head> -- as the household's other children played around her. It was, the  Prince salespeople, many tennis shops gave Prince's " peg " space -- the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="463">
<answer instance="463" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
banana republic; and 3) by continuing the race, Clinton is ensuring the voting Village: the old Hawaii, no electricity only a compressor, where the best <head>XYZ</head> bread on the planet is made by a true native of the islands juliasbanana bread.com  # Cupcakes: # 3/4 cup granulated sugar, divided # 1/2 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="228">
<answer instance="228" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
a little boat called a krathong, and we place a candle I wait until the plane lands. I hate that airplane breakfast of an ice-cold <head>XYZ</head> a children's snack pack of Cheerios and a recess box of milk.  accompanied by crisp fresh vegetables and mashed pumpkin. Dessert went deliciously native -- 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1044">
<answer instance="1044" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
nitre. Before I was aware of what was happening, Montresor had back to CROSSFIRE. That was the Treasury secretary reacting to the wild day on <head>XYZ</head> Street, as the Dow suffered its biggest one day point drop in history.  wall. PILGRIM: We are going back in history to call up the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="766">
<answer instance="766" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
of a house, as far as the crew had gotten the " Across the vast interior of the warehouse, all the way to the far <head>XYZ</head> were parked machines and vehicles of all shapes and size, some larger than  roof terrace with a solar-heated pool and a bar. # " We 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="263">
<answer instance="263" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the tangled jungle with exotic highlights of pink and blue. They in Paris in the mid-1980s. The chef there amazed his apprentice by adding a <head>XYZ</head> to a lamb shank curry. " He said,' You won't even  . Add orange juice, rum, if using, and nutmeg. Fold in banana slices. Remove 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="198">
<answer instance="198" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
sector of the Queensland east coast trawl fishery, and occurs mostly with tapioca. It has only half the banana content of plain -- a plain <head>XYZ</head> product. Ms-HURLEY: The wrong side dishes can ruin a perfectly healthy meal.  three meals combined: # Several chocolate chip cookies with milk; two bowls of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="950">
<answer instance="950" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Products and appliances that have Energy Star ratings may qualify for and a lot of Republicans agree with you, but that approach was working until <head>XYZ</head> Street melted down. MR-BROOKS: Well... MR-BROKAW: Andrea, I want to  cheap wig store: pageboys, falls, extensions. I squatted down against the wall to consider the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="579">
<answer instance="579" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the shell and backfilling, you can add more room for decking or plants years older than you. When you're 50, TlI be an oltl peeled <head>XYZ</head> Don't tell me that isn't the truth about me because it is  barreled into the scrawny man I chased. He stood motionless, staring at a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="98">
<answer instance="98" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
how to put a condom on a banana, like you did in homeroom after Kristi got pregnant, Ms. Freedman. Except 13779 Rice cereal or mashed <head>XYZ</head> Finger food or chunky applesauce? Make it easy on yourself with our age-by-age  (Emas 1998). (n14) Chiquita and Dole also set up nonunion banana operations 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="971">
<answer instance="971" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
and fell to the ground. An area about fifteen feet in diameter. It didn't, " Weis said. " Rather than beat your head against the <head>XYZ</head> with a guy who disrupts a lot of teams with his penetration, we figured  past him, he pivoted, his swinging tail ripping several sinks out 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="317">
<answer instance="317" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
in the door between its locker room and that used by the number of French troops to 100,000. Soustelle ordered Sikorsky H-2 1 " Flying <head>XYZ</head> " and other helicopters from the United States. General Cherrire was relieved of duty  ! But as a mother of a 1 1/2-year-old who has 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="772">
<answer instance="772" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
sheer face that rises 1,650 feet. This basalt formation extends for nearly influx of children, he said. # The plans on his " war room <head>XYZ</head> " show maps of a future Plano with some 5,000 more homes, Roberts said  seated. SUSAN-SPENCER- (voi# With a circumstantial case and no direct evidence 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="280">
<answer instance="280" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
of the healthiest things you could add to your diet, " says so young. Maria said she was only thirteen. The Weasel picked a fat <head>XYZ</head> from one of several plants in his yard. At this time of year he  . Eric was going to have nuts and syrup, but he 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="878">
<answer instance="878" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
indicating Arkham Asylum. EXT. ARKHAM ASYLUM - CONTINUOUS The headlights cast light of a tremendous building effort, " adds McGuire. Whereas Lewis and McGuire joined <head>XYZ</head> Street firms after graduate school, E. Stanley O'Neal worked for General Motors for many  the gradual darkening of the eye, the gradual fading of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="357">
<answer instance="357" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
cloth (bashofu), patterned with a geometric float weave, made for Ryukyuan wonderfully prepared vegetarian food inside a small, pleasant restaurant and at outdoor tables under <head>XYZ</head> palm, and evergreen trees. Author Affiliation Wayne Curtis is a frequent contributor  talk about them individually. RUSS-MITCHELL: Let's start with this one. DR-KAVITA-MARIWALL: The Banana 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="913">
<answer instance="913" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
fire, just flames and heat and it was like there was nothing left the window, Mr. Wiggins.' Get back in that corner and face the <head>XYZ</head> and stay there. One more word out of you and you'll spend the  and brought libel suits against other American publications, such as Time, the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="248">
<answer instance="248" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
peels, a tack to put under every one of our assumptions? This too quicksand, jump in a river, swim from crocodiles, climb the baboons " <head>XYZ</head> tree, swing on vines, land on an elephant, charge through the jungle  from Joe and parents when junior wants the lifesize replica, Joe bath robes, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="736">
<answer instance="736" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
saw the defendant. An hour and 10 minutes sits there, turning this way and that, looking at the pictures on the wall, looking at the <head>XYZ</head> I see that he is practicing. He is  extends 26 miles around the base, earning it the nickname, " the Great Wall of Clark ". 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="361">
<answer instance="361" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
blueberries, almond butter, coconut, hemp protein and choice of milk $6 olds sitting calmly in circles-no one is crying or shouting or grabbing another child's <head>XYZ</head> or crayons-and I wonder what it is about the Japanese that makes this self-contained,  the fruit smoothie line, now comes with four ingredients: milk, juice, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="675">
<answer instance="675" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
fire filled the sky now, singeing the hair off Sentience's exposed flesh breakfast. " He shoved him away and the boy's back thumped against the <head>XYZ</head> knocking the wind clean out of him. Tom looked back and saw Mrs.  former Blink-182 drummer Travis Barker. Barker and Skinhead Rob are in a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="261">
<answer instance="261" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
one banana grower, Chiquita Brands International. # In the cases, workers claimed they were , 3 g fiber, 72 mg cholesterol, 270 mg sodium. Mom's <head>XYZ</head> Dessert Total time 15 minutes Makes 8 servings 2 c. heavy or whipping cream 2  a greenbelt. At night, neon lights lit up the swaying 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="456">
<answer instance="456" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
I craved was the kind I watched my grandmother, Nanny, put together I'd love to play with bourbon and a salted caramel shake, or a <head>XYZ</head> ice cream with a beautiful dark rum like Gosling's. Or how about dipping  # No. We didn't. Silence. # ANTHONY # We're making banana daqueris. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="241">
<answer instance="241" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
# Pelosi also said she was briefed by federal officials several years door through the porch, you know? Where I was makin a jelly and <head>XYZ</head> sandwich? I remember I had my hair in curlers cause I was goin that  Light Conditioner # PHOTO (COLOR): From left: Diesel Rabox jeans, Banana 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="125">
<answer instance="125" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
we peel the banana from the stem end, and that's usually a bit of a tussle. is eggs, chorizo (sausages), tortillas, fried plantains (from the <head>XYZ</head> family), pan dulce (sweet bread), and fresh fruit. Another  cotton shirt ($295) by Massimo Alba; suede ($140) by Banana Republic. #  29G CARB; 0MG CHOL; 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="837">
<answer instance="837" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
on the wall and squinted, trying to see the reading. # She'd turned the thermostat Wall Street's reaction will be? Mr. ROHATYN: Well, you know, <head>XYZ</head> Street is, I think, so totally out of step with the reality of  Oval Jaynes, now the athletic director at Pittsburgh. Jaynes' successor, Hindman Wall, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="109">
<answer instance="109" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
He's kissing me on his family TV set. Aw, that just on silt-trap drains reflected the need to control surplus runoff in banana fields. In <head>XYZ</head> cultivation farmers planted only in widely spaced holes, so runoff moved downhill unimpeded.  , Santa Cruz doesn't emphasize that its athletic teams' mascot, a hermaphroditic 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="817">
<answer instance="817" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
they were listening. The opera fell away to a minor-key aria and to the woodshed, grabbed a short ladder, and made her way to the <head>XYZ</head> From the highest rung, she could just see over the top, and  " Before this program, I could have been the mouse over there against 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="423">
<answer instance="423" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
BANANA REPUBLIC, OLD NAVY. GARNET HILL. L.L BEAN KIDS. HANNA ANDERSSON. FHIA-01. The Goldfinger was developed by painstakingly cross-breeding samples from the more than 350 <head>XYZ</head> types originally collected by United Fruit scientists. It is a highly versatile fruit,  signature suckling-pig confit with pumpkin and sage; lobster with baby leeks, pimiento 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="474">
<answer instance="474" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
once the hindmost part of each cylinder thus becomes the forward-facing strong resemblance to a lunar landing module, includes a two-story greenhouse with a thriving <head>XYZ</head> tree. In addition, he is experimenting with citrus, nut, and avocado  environment or the health of field workers. " Is sigatoka the end of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="381">
<answer instance="381" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
" # Did Fraser arrive in a loincloth? " No, he bowls of soup, enormous fish-shaped platters of ceviche and moist pork tamales wrapped in <head>XYZ</head> leaves are the stuff of this kitchen. # Start with a beef empanada --  the grass beyond. Too late, he notices the empty beer bottles 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="919">
<answer instance="919" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
wall. # # TOYOTA # # You see what you're doing, don't box, and an indoor grill with charcoal. A worn crucifix hung on the <head>XYZ</head> the gold paint was peeling from the figure of Christ. Everything was dull  because Warren has built her public persona in part by pushing for 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="734">
<answer instance="734" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
that separates their rooms. " That was last semester, " Griner insisted. time at which the murder occurred. At 10:45, Kato heard thumps on his <head>XYZ</head> and shortly after 11:00, he saw the defendant. An hour and 10 minutes  sits there, turning this way and that, looking at the pictures on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="319">
<answer instance="319" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
allergies, it would be great to have a few nutritious and yummy 's economy, thanks to subsidies from Great Britain. That country has bought every <head>XYZ</head> Saint Vincent can grow since 1948, paying more than the crop would bring in  to be followed by what may be viewed as counter-prestations that 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="214">
<answer instance="214" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
is no doubt that the European corporations do pay high wages that grew in green clusters between the bricks. I could see the shadows of <head>XYZ</head> trees moving on the window screens, the humidity condensing and threading along the fronds  alternative to pain and cursing: Replenish your magnesium and potassium immediately 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="801">
<answer instance="801" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
for an overnight trip for two to Copan and a 36-cent of vice chairman overseeing the entire travel-related-services unit. # With his outgoing nature and <head>XYZ</head> Street polish, Mr. Chenault strikes some as a throwback to the era of the  241	2000	ACAD	IBMRandD	A	B	C	  left at the original 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1068">
<answer instance="1068" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
wall slides open. With a rattle the gurney moves through the opening, and the to the east and southeast where they ended at a white-stone <head>XYZ</head> Below the wall, down a rocky decline, was a small lake shaped like a lima bean  's supposed to be made of, if it's going 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="124">
<answer instance="124" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
face wearing sunglasses with the caption " Speedy Banana " next , I just like to think so -- you and me, we peel the <head>XYZ</head> from the stem end, and that's usually a bit of a tussle.  is eggs, chorizo (sausages), tortillas, fried plantains (from the banana family), pan dulce 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="388">
<answer instance="388" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
cup oil 1/2 cup honey 1 teaspoon vanilla 2 eggs 3 The bag inside had been dragged out and shredded, and bits and pieces of <head>XYZ</head> peel, coffee filters, and other assorted trash littered the concrete floor. #  back and forth on the edge of an embankment, which is littered with 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="230">
<answer instance="230" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
with homemade vanilla ice cream. A touch of the exotic With the unpredictability mission control. As we sit near the water's edge, looking across the <head>XYZ</head> River at the launch pad, we hear an announcement that catches our attention.  You can eat 1 cup of diced melon for less than 50 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="7">
<answer instance="7" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
a banana, raised his eyebrows and said, " Laura, she's our guest. area. " Israeli agriculture is incredibly mismanaged, " Bromberg says as we pass <head>XYZ</head> plantations along the Jordan River bank. " The farmers here could be planting olives  Teddy Roosevelt said: I could carve a judge with more backbone 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="113">
<answer instance="113" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
A touch of cinnamon and nutmeg gives these sweet treats an early plants has lowered the price: In the spring, Home Depot was selling one-gallon <head>XYZ</head> plants for $9.99. Garden-variety dahlias can be found for less than $5, but  was making all sorts of boasts. He seems to have folded like 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="15">
<answer instance="15" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Bea was on the floor playing with Bear. " I want Jell-O, I used to packrat things. Hell, I had six exhaust valves from a <head>XYZ</head> boat. You just sell it all off -clothes, dishes, things you do  features sweet burgers $5.75 with warm doughnuts standing in for the bun, and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="406">
<answer instance="406" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
contains 21 g protein, 19 g fiber and only 12 g fat 's development of Mexigold' squash is more typical. He started by crossing Mexican <head>XYZ</head> a blue-green banana squash, with the orange, heart-shaped Golden Delicious'  she said, forcing a smile. She left the break room, leaving the banana behind, and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="268">
<answer instance="268" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Clinton. The second banana must have been Speaker-designate Mr. Livingston, who resigned for obvious reasons, thanks to Haan shoes ($330), colehaan.com; Banana Republic bracelet ($35), <head>XYZ</head> republic.com; On her (right): Calvin Klein dress ($130),  tsp. each baking powder and cinnamon 1 tsp. baking soda 1 cup chopped walnuts cup banana chips, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="41">
<answer instance="41" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
sold a hemp blend skirt or fragrances in certified sustainable wood boxes, So base your wardrobe on simple but good pieces. Look at J. Crew, <head>XYZ</head> Republic, H andM,; Club Monaco. They have great and varying sensibilities and they  diced fresh mango (or any tropical fruit, such as papaya, pineapple or 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="400">
<answer instance="400" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
or banana leaves are the more traditional wrappers. # ufninfoNutrition Information (per serving, including . " # 1 Dress, Taylor Dress, $128; Belk. 2 Dress, <head>XYZ</head> Republic, $140; bananarepublic.com. Belt, L.K.Bennett, $145; lkbennett.com. 3 Dress  bashofu in Photograph Taira Toshiko, top right, separates the layers of a fiber banana stalk -- 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1028">
<answer instance="1028" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
David Burger says an average day might include several banquets for drawing criticism from national and local publications. # Newspapers including USA Today and The <head>XYZ</head> Street Journal are joining forces with Phoenix-area rivals the East Valley Tribune and The Arizona  phone calls -- if they come -- will come (today). 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="115">
<answer instance="115" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
like a wet banana. What's happening? Gen. SCHWARZKOPF: Well, again, I think he (cooked or chopped raw) 4 c. vegetable or fruit juice medium apple, <head>XYZ</head> or orange 2 c. fruit (chopped, cooked, frozen or canned) tbsp.  Show, a weekly 90-minute extravaganza emceed by Talullah Bankhead, with Allen as second banana. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="470">
<answer instance="470" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
a great gavel. Of the hard, wheeling lights above, my cup nonfat milk or soymilk cup plain nonfat yogurt 2 Tbs. vegetable oil 1 firm <head>XYZ</head> diced 3 Tbs. shredded coconut 1. Put buckwheat flour, all-purpose flour,  'm real hungry, " Joe said. # " Guess I'll have the banana, " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="532">
<answer instance="532" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
plantation; a large, airy cavern, its volume has been nearly doubled by it up. ELIZABETH-VARGAS-# (Off-camera) Where do you get these jeans? DAN-PERES-1EDITOR# These are <head>XYZ</head> Republic. ELIZABETH-VARGAS-# (Off-camera) Banana Republic. DAN-PERES-1EDITOR# Yeah. CHRIS-CUOMO-1ABC-# (Off-camera) And that beautiful  , and expensive. " (n61) # When labor costs rose during the banana 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="638">
<answer instance="638" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Wall Street's largest white-shoe firms again? # " Yes, it's fascinating to had telephoned from France, or if Jinx hadn't driven her car into a <head>XYZ</head> the storm would have blown over in a day or two. As it  90 minutes. That's almost impossible to do. The other thing is " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="165">
<answer instance="165" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Ocean to Africa? As you might have predicted, the answer of that day and a part of the next as Potts learned to pilot the <head>XYZ</head> with efficiency. Truth told, I never thought he'd learn. Thought the  Hungarian peppers -- from Whole Foods or summer farmers markets -- or substitute 2 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="884">
<answer instance="884" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
reimagined Saul's transformation into Paul as a night scene in which photo of a young Clinton posing behind the county judge's desk hung on the <head>XYZ</head> As they walked toward the bank to greet folks inside, Laverty reminded Pryor  polls, many media polls that come out, the Pew poll, the " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1039">
<answer instance="1039" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
to be the heaviest. Barring an unlikely last-minute change, he will deserve to die. " I noticed a cross-stitched picture of Jesus hanging on the <head>XYZ</head> and I liked how small and per fect the stitches were. " Some  They are your allies in this war against human suffering. Sincerely, James 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="812">
<answer instance="812" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
doing' The Wall,'' Walking Against the Wind.' I was fascinated. I'd her head and looked around. Watery sunlight filtered in through the hole in the <head>XYZ</head> though it did nothing to lift the chill from her fur. In the  and the Republican Party is changing, too, just more slowly. " A 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="681">
<answer instance="681" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
to the Unitarian church, watching Charlie dance with our mother. We were garden, revealing and concealing views. # The most common device used is the <head>XYZ</head> that encloses the garden space. With an enclosed garden entered through gates, the  called, and at the sound of that familiar, long-forgotten voice, a false 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="229">
<answer instance="229" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
children's snack pack of Cheerios and a recess box of milk. accompanied by crisp fresh vegetables and mashed pumpkin. Dessert went deliciously native -- a <head>XYZ</head> tart with homemade vanilla ice cream. A touch of the exotic With the unpredictability  mission control. As we sit near the water's edge, looking across 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="639">
<answer instance="639" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the storm would have blown over in a day or two. As it 90 minutes. That's almost impossible to do. The other thing is " <head>XYZ</head> Street Journal " points this out. He was on the attack. They call  prop up a magazine against your side of the armrest. You'll create 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="226">
<answer instance="226" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
commercials, died Friday of cancer. She was 64. # Valli was a # It appears that Bonzo is attracted to Miss Tuffet's Derfume... Eau De <head>XYZ</head> Peel. Tyki has gone back to his ARTWORK. A FASCINATED Indiana looks over  Water. On the full moon in the twelfth lunar month-usually in November-we 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1041">
<answer instance="1041" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
allies in this war against human suffering. Sincerely, James M. Wall # , goes down. Newhouse gets hit in the chest, slams back against the <head>XYZ</head> As Newhouse lays dying on the floor his fingers reach for the dog tag  kitchen, and you see Kid Number One has been scribbling with 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="67">
<answer instance="67" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
yellow zoot suit complete with a snap brim fedora. That's the ticket! twenty of Bert's renowned apricot tarts. Jimmy will bring them to the Pink <head>XYZ</head> Club on Fiftysecond Street, where the tarts will be devoured for free by any  of any variety 2 cups finely shredded green cabbage leaves 1. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="224">
<answer instance="224" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
We are accumulating a massive debt. We owe about half choice but to replant their vast plantations with Cavendish and to overhaul the system of <head>XYZ</head> mass production that United Fruit (now Chiquita Brands International) had invented around the  variety shows from the 1950s through the 1970s and provided the voice 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="493">
<answer instance="493" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
skin. And the money? " It was a little burned around the edges accuracy is this club' s real forte; good job limiting dispersion; no <head>XYZ</head> balls with the # FEEL: Many testers get a good sense of where  This is what some people do,' and pretended to stab her with 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="192">
<answer instance="192" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
banana. But tomatoes, a lot of people, may not know, heavy for the problem of representation itself. Wanjohi Nyamu, an artist who worked not at <head>XYZ</head> Hill but at the informal studio outside the National Museum sponsored by Kuona Trust,  's attention at least. So he went on. " We'd be 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="503">
<answer instance="503" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
She was hooked. Ms. Weinmayr and her daughter Annie (then in campaign cash Washington rakes in -- in this particular case, from the direction of <head>XYZ</head> magnate Carl Lindner. Barlett and Steele, who spent 27 years at the Philadelphia  460	2003	FIC	Scholastic Scope	A	B	C	  a hopeful grin and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="455">
<answer instance="455" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
place into them. This is the holiday dinner set. During New Year fully intend to make both these decadent puddings. Just not right now. The <head>XYZ</head> pudding I craved was the kind I watched my grandmother, Nanny, put together  I'd love to play with bourbon and a salted caramel shake, or 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="891">
<answer instance="891" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
wall, memorializes the Reverend George Dana Boardman (18011831), who, with his moisture is absorbed from the soil. You can dig a trench next to the <head>XYZ</head> of a mission and it'll be perfectly dry, but just the moisture in  ? Mr. BESCHLOSS: Well, the newsreel we just saw - Kennedy at 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="266">
<answer instance="266" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
banana slices. Remove from heat, and let cool slightly. 3. Divide warm burlesque show is the first banana. And that was Bill Clinton. The second <head>XYZ</head> must have been Speaker-designate Mr. Livingston, who resigned for obvious reasons, thanks to  Haan shoes ($330), colehaan.com; Banana Republic bracelet ($35), banana republic.com; On her 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="157">
<answer instance="157" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Roles: banana grower, banana eater, soil conservation person telling of erosion, neighbor living downstream unidentified banana cult leader was accosted by local police for promising <head>XYZ</head> growers that their banana crops would increase tenfold if they copulated in public, a common practice in the  see the silvery glint of a dime 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="448">
<answer instance="448" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
10 medium washed, hulled strawberries; cup plain low-fat yogurt; 2 tablespoons nation with a healthy middle class and small business sector, not the simplistic " <head>XYZ</head> republic " portrayed. The income might be low in dollar terms, but that  all or part of 27 magazine articles; and the Cincinnati Enquirer apologized 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="283">
<answer instance="283" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Dominica's export-based banana industry. Roberto Valentin, president of Puerto Rico Container, said his company is other crops. Other crops, such as maize, rice, sorghum, and <head>XYZ</head> will receive breeding support from AGRA, as well. For maize and sorghum  has done here. It's a day by train. Walk among the yellow banana 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="732">
<answer instance="732" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
strength to strength. # The US had had its own the history of the world is a place near the town of George where one <head>XYZ</head> of the river's gorge falls away into a huge sloping cupped hillside, a  times. Freshman teammate Shanay Washington is her unofficial wake-up service, pounding on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="415">
<answer instance="415" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
The Germans refused, insisting on their right to import bananas at will cultivation farmers planted only in widely spaced holes, so runoff moved downhill unimpeded. <head>XYZ</head> farmers used large amounts of synthetic fertilizers in their fields, and silt-trap drains limited  have just finished a dinner of chicken and fried plantains, the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1037">
<answer instance="1037" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
a wall, but I'm getting pretty fuckin' sick of this! Get it? I don't want it. George YELLS as he lands the hammer into the <head>XYZ</head> again. Sam is alarmed by his father's blatant rage. # GEORGE #  game into a damaging deal frenzy. # The punishment for the biggest name 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="874">
<answer instance="874" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
wall. Spot the top of the next panel on this mark. Sidebar Where the proper stress control. The Dogbone allows for proper termination from double <head>XYZ</head> to single wall while maintaining system pressure rating. In addition, the Dogbone helps control thermal expansion  into the darkness overhead. It marks the end of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="649">
<answer instance="649" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
down until I was crouching against it. # In the distance now pronounce that you are husband and wife. A clock clicks noiselessly on the <head>XYZ</head> behind them. It has no face. Colin, you may kiss your bride  , Brit. BRIT-HUME-FOX-NEW: Hi, Bret. Our sister publication, " The Wall Street Journal 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="888">
<answer instance="888" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
USA Today # Sacramento Bee # San Francisco Examiner 49951 # On Time. This picture was not even framed. It was simply tacked on the <head>XYZ</head> and it had obviously been torn -- rather carelessly, perhaps hurriedly -- from  McConnell is calling a Sunday session, ahead of a midnight deadline. GWEN-IFILL# 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="128">
<answer instance="128" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
pervade parts of Kauai damaged by Hurricane Iwa in 1982, Asquith says for one dress to multipurpose, you can find inexpensive ones online at Target, <head>XYZ</head> Republic and even Wal-Mart. # It was a simple challenge between colleagues. Wear one  no-melt? DAVE-PISTORINO: Four flavors. CHRIS-WRAGGE: Just four? DAVE-PISTORINO: Yep. Banana, chocolate, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="154">
<answer instance="154" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
banana'' -album-flavored tribal stomp that features former VU drummer Moe (Maureen) Tucker farm means the grower needs to clear more land for agriculture. # Roles: <head>XYZ</head> grower, banana eater, soil conservation person telling of erosion, neighbor living downstream  unidentified banana cult leader was accosted by local police for promising banana growers 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="267">
<answer instance="267" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
And that was Bill Clinton. The second banana must have been Speaker-designate Mr. Livingston, who resigned for obvious reasons, thanks to Haan shoes ($330), colehaan.com; <head>XYZ</head> Republic bracelet ($35), banana republic.com; On her (right): Calvin Klein dress ($130),  tsp. each baking powder and cinnamon 1 tsp. baking soda 1 cup chopped 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="973">
<answer instance="973" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
around his side and managed to dislodge one of his scales with " Is that what men like? " Lily was studying the kitchen, one <head>XYZ</head> at a time. # " I think it had little to do with the  stand, along the wall in an auditorium at Merrill Lynch and; 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="313">
<answer instance="313" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
legumes, Kava and ornamentals are also affected by CMV. CMV is heard myself as someone else. # " You might wan na munch on a <head>XYZ</head> or something, " Spinelli said. " You're pale as shit. "  Rockville, Md. # Dallas: What kind of shoes can you make from banana peels? 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="974">
<answer instance="974" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
" Lily was studying the kitchen, one wall at a time. # " I think it had little to do with the stand, along the <head>XYZ</head> in an auditorium at Merrill Lynch and; Co.' s Wall Street headquarters, wondering whether my boss's determination will pay off or do us  cat chase 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1054">
<answer instance="1054" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
banking industry. But the idea made some sense. It was to avoid the minority than we do in the House. They don't have this iron <head>XYZ</head> of resistance that is evident in the House of Representatives. But, you know  # " NOW with Bill Moyers " will begin Jan. 18, airing 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="120">
<answer instance="120" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the Chiquita banana factory. Can't wait what comes out of that story. LITTLEFORD: It's sundae, describe it for me. Mr-GREG-RANDALL-1: Hot cherries, hot fudge, big <head>XYZ</head> (Audience-reaction) Mr-RANDALL:... and you could drive me nuts. (Audience-reaction) RIVERA:  and over, sometimes on the same wall so it seems to swarm; a banana transformed 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="213">
<answer instance="213" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Festival: It'll be celebrated June 9-10 in Wilmington, where the ice-cream -- especially of Latin America and the Caribbean? I say this because of the <head>XYZ</head> wars, and there is no doubt that the European corporations do pay high wages  that grew in green clusters between the bricks. I could see 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="45">
<answer instance="45" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
flesh tastes like a mix of papaya, pineapple, and banana. ## " Everyone told us,' you can't make money off cherimoyas, the tip of the <head>XYZ</head> " # As mentioned, the Cavendish is the banana mainstream America knows best. But Quick says so many other varieties are out there  (where there 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="804">
<answer instance="804" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
with a lot of lights. Text on the bottom of Marie-Santana had swum round and round within inches of where he was clinging to the <head>XYZ</head> and when her face came out of the water for air and her mouth  the Great rebuilt the second Temple in Jerusalem 2,000 years ago; 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="855">
<answer instance="855" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
fast do you think it's going? " I don't know her -- I think it was her third birthday -- a castle that was a <head>XYZ</head> unit. And there was all different rooms in it. So we had to  .. but... a bit dangerous? Christina set her summer fire against the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="96">
<answer instance="96" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
equally - the 150 calories in a banana are more useful to the body, and less likely to add weight, than 33546 Picadillo-Stuffed Peppers Island <head>XYZ</head> Bread Cuban Black Beans with Mango Relish Brown Rice, Peas and Pine Nuts Eating  and tell people about AIDS and show them how to put 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="586">
<answer instance="586" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
of Calla-Lily directors charged behind Ruth toward the elevator bank. Preston might not take it after all. It is a bit too close to the <head>XYZ</head> she said to me. Do you think we will be all right here  probably made their next trades even more aggressive.) And when Cisco had 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="936">
<answer instance="936" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
where Joe Connor's father, Frank Connor, was calling for the check. the federal budget to appear larger than it otherwise would. The solution is to <head>XYZ</head> off the savings that Social Security accrues by introducing a system of individually owned investment  when he went into the next room, which had dull 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="569">
<answer instance="569" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
thick foliage. Once again he ignored her comment. " Stay close, lot of the field on the backstretch and turning for home, there was a <head>XYZ</head> of four horses in front of him. I debated whether to go around,  with growing public fury about a $700 billion bailout, Washington cracked down 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="996">
<answer instance="996" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Wall Street realized. Its new-product cupboard was bare. Separate divisions called on the same wall': the stones (that is the antecedent events) which compose the <head>XYZ</head> (that is the subsequent event) are joined and held together, not by  Ministry Inc. is raising money to pay for its new building by making 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="710">
<answer instance="710" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
ship, casting a shifting got a wine glass or something. And you put the glass up to the wall, and you can hear through the <head>XYZ</head> a little bit more of the song   2108585 WALL STREET TAKES NO PRISONERS THESE DAYS, which James D. Robinson III, chairman for  than, you know, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="324">
<answer instance="324" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
to a decline in the use of grass barriers. Peasants devoted of these. The reason is the natural oils actually put -- well they put <head>XYZ</head> all over your shoe for one thing, so you can buff it off.  bagels while driving to the start. At the first rest stop I 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="153">
<answer instance="153" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Formula, " the tape screened for review, Bullwinkle swallows a secret formula ( I Spent a Week There the Other Night provides I'm Not,' a <head>XYZ</head> -album-flavored tribal stomp that features former VU drummer Moe (Maureen) Tucker  farm means the grower needs to clear more land for agriculture. # Roles: banana 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="302">
<answer instance="302" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
pizza burgers, and a banana split waiting. You goofballs want to at least pretend you're working? " $178, Boden. Sweater, $179, Ann Taylor. Pants, $89, <head>XYZ</head> Republic. Umbrella,. Earrings,. Boots, #  petrified gum globs. A vomitous air fresh- P117 ever in the shape of a banana hanging from his rearview mirror 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="53">
<answer instance="53" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
a dessert Eva whips up on the spot. She whirls a keep electrolytes in balance, healthcare professionals often advise those on diuretics to eat a <head>XYZ</head> every day to replenish potassium stores. Taking a daily multivitamin is a good idea  in my backyard to what the " Wall Street Journal " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="234">
<answer instance="234" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
maquila workers, and others persist in demanding representation. In concert with more comfortable to it. And -- and this is a look that is from <head>XYZ</head> Republic. And it -- on this one, the jacket's about 290,  . The land was also protected from erosion by the large amounts of trash 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="917">
<answer instance="917" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
drifted back to settle sedately on its saucer on the table. # 95. More delays would push back an expected gravy train. # That has <head>XYZ</head> Street on edge; traders are tuned to every hint of delay. # Microsoft  . Tour # buses. Blind people feeling around # for bullet holes 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="684">
<answer instance="684" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
with the wall. Its molecules seem suddenly active, the wood grain suddenly animate. Layers begin either, are you? Ms-SHANKLE: No. Dr-McGRAW: I mean, because that <head>XYZ</head> you don't just put that up in December. It's up all  we are legion -- this is a big event. (Excerpt-from- " Wall BOWEN: (Voiceover) 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="926">
<answer instance="926" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
# Impressed by the company's red-hot sales, he accumulated 12,000 sure space was saved for a row of appliance garages below the cabinets on one <head>XYZ</head> This way, the storage units don't take up much-needed counterspace; the  walked around the bed. Fold after fold of needlepoint canvas was piled along the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="656">
<answer instance="656" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
She turned to the mass of Buruden and addressed their a nail from between his lips and began to hammer a hole in the black <head>XYZ</head> where he was planning to hang his 3-D " found objects " portrait of Bill  door and flings it open. INT. ELEVATOR Gina hits the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="471">
<answer instance="471" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
firm banana, diced 3 Tbs. shredded coconut 1. Put buckwheat flour, all-purpose flour, 'm real hungry, " Joe said. # " Guess I'll have the <head>XYZ</head> " he said to Casey. # " Try the carrot sticks, "  carp lurking in schools under bridges in swiftly-moving concrete bayous... Korean-run Mexican bakeries... 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="173">
<answer instance="173" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
" BRATT Ingredients BANANA: (ONE MEDIUM-SIZED, PEELED) Calories: 85 Protein: 1.5 grams Carbohydrates online. Rochesterclothing.com is a good place to start, along with Jack Victor, <head>XYZ</head> Republic, J.Crew, and the Gap. I have a decent black belt that  opens her hand and the banana is still there, but now it's mushed 
</context>
</instance>
