<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<corpus lang='english'>

<lexelt item="p_c">

<instance id="538">
<answer instance="538" senseid="car"/>
<context>
we could do. DONNIE (off pigeon) Did you know there used to be falcons in New York? # LEFTY ! Ace jumps out of his <head>p_c</head> and starts skipping around the park with the pigeon held high over his head. He looks insane. ACE (CONT'D)    from the waist gamble at cards 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="722">
<answer instance="722" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Galya said. " He talks French, not Moscow. Like you and rough cloth straps help the players get into positions like the can opener or <head>p_c</head> To get into the pigeon, the players, while seated on the basement    I encourage you to make the spice mix if you can. You can 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="769">
<answer instance="769" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
imprint and recall bank. Both neutral. Unless the occupant had been on in Napier Terrace eight years ago when Staff Foster caught it. " Shad's <head>p_c</head> suit looked at me for a beat then nodded. " Fitness reports and other    out. As she shifted his shoulders to spare his face from 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="648">
<answer instance="648" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
caught the white pigeon! Ace jumps out of his car and starts possible. Germ cells develop into sperm or eggs, which will produce a passenger-like <head>p_c</head> in the next generation. # STATUS: Scientists have so far sequenced DNA from  snooping neither. Just you should know Teague and his boys are lurking 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="770">
<answer instance="770" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
me for a beat then nodded. " Fitness reports and other out. As she shifted his shoulders to spare his face from resting in the <head>p_c</head> droppings, his eyes fluttered open and his arms twitched at his side. She    ended late. Like firecrackers, or thunder. On Labor Day there was the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="254">
<answer instance="254" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
by carrier pigeon during the Allies' Normandy invasion in World War II. # Or for trying sperm to inseminate band-tailed pigeons, creating hybrids (half band-tailed <head>p_c</head> half passenger pigeon). Artificial insemination is used extensively in modern poultry, with a high rate    hear, " Walter said. # " I shouldn't? " # 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="483">
<answer instance="483" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
as the meat of any animal with spotted or striped skin broad fields of wheat and corn at our backs, as well as a towering <head>p_c</head> house of mud, ancient, partially demolished, and untenanted. Facing us was    to pocket. All gone now. The manufacturing floor smells like stale urine and pigeon 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1239">
<answer instance="1239" senseid="car"/>
<context>
on the passenger side and brushed at his suit jacket. " Well, officer this... " He shook his head darkly. # We were in Dick's <head>p_c</head> He was taking me to my hotel. After we'd buried Doc,    . Later, shaken but safe, he assessed the damage: a badly battered car, a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="90">
<answer instance="90" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
wandered into the Angels' bullpen, as you see there, during a game stood up and got a bottle of vodkafromthe freezer. Ruth's heart was a <head>p_c</head> in her chest. He puUed her bottom lip open with his good thumb and    flutter at the corner of the high ceiling and Frendon looked 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="735">
<answer instance="735" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
-- Irving Tessler, President. These birds get to take it easy today Figure 3. Variation in the abundance of an exotic bird species, the rock <head>p_c</head> (Columba livia), at random sites in Baltimore. (a) The    . # PHOTO (COLOR): An unusual feature of several fort complexes are pigeon towers, which may 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="386">
<answer instance="386" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
for its Italian-Jewish owner, Joey Scott, said he learned much of traits. # 3 Swap those bits of DNA for the corresponding bits in rock <head>p_c</head> stem cells, thus creating passenger pigeon stem cells. # 4 Convert the stem    and he learned he'd lost his position as President of the Society. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="330">
<answer instance="330" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon peas instead. He also advises waiting until the rainy season ends in mid-October to , pumpkin and squash seeds, dried beans, millet, sesame, a, <head>p_c</head> peas, sunflower seeds, sorghum syrup, dark rye, wild rice, sunchokes    size of a quarter, with his pinkie, beginning to rock faster. The pigeon barely had 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="495">
<answer instance="495" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
its belly swollen by the gases of putrefaction. Crooked feathers pointed in all this year's side-by-side litter. 203-256-3860; ruger.com USER-FRIENDLY AMMO Shooters of side-by-sides fancy <head>p_c</head> loads -- those 12-gauge, 11/4-ounce, 1220-fps loads that hit birds hard without kicking    . Through the rearview mirror I watched as a cloud of smoke 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="563">
<answer instance="563" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the plucking. But in six weeks, the pigeon had begun to no answer but the owl hooting in the night, the mourning coo of the <head>p_c</head> at dawn. # At first light, Apalura saw that her worst fear was  bath, so some kid understands what happened to a friggin' Puppy and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="390">
<answer instance="390" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
was warned of legal maneuvers by creditors. A pigeon, and , the Philadelphia Eagles mascot eagle walks up to get a drink and shoos the <head>p_c</head> away. Ace is furious. ACE You idiot! Do you know what you   the gamekeeper of the mansion-house property, a limber-legged fellow who could pick off 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="882">
<answer instance="882" senseid="car"/>
<context>
and he needed a ride from Oklahoma City to Kansas. # for a certain distance at a certain minimum speed and other arcane stuff. Your <head>p_c</head> readiness monitors hadn't completed, just idling in line; this may take  , she revved it up a few times before putting it in reverse. The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="878">
<answer instance="878" senseid="car"/>
<context>
fast nose-dive for the bottom and in a frenzy of terror, she Henry said. He took another look out of their hiding place. The white <head>p_c</head> was still moving slowly down the road. # " Okay, we're in    Alan did on their cars, or perhaps not. More likely they sold their 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="811">
<answer instance="811" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
volcano-scarred cliffs, dense forests, and a 120-foot-high waterfall aptly called environmental movement into high gear was a small blue-gray headed game bird called the passenger <head>p_c</head> In the 1870s, a commission in Ohio investigated the open hunting of the    fine day, indeed. What do you say we take a look at 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="580">
<answer instance="580" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
and cormorants will be nesting around the deck, while seagulls will nest on equally possible, though, that Saatchi is the new Schragis -- Spy's latest <head>p_c</head> One can almost picture Carter and Andersen, oozing Anglophilia, sidling up to    of prey or to escape predators. Confuciusornis sanctus, about the size of a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="475">
<answer instance="475" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
produced a sound. They could hear the ill cooing of the pigeon. " Okay, " Owen repeated, as if to break the spell. living passenger <head>p_c</head> genome. # Phase 3: Genome creation. Goal: synthesizing passenger's DNA regions identified as significant in phase 1 and integrating these into band-tailed bird cells    Almighty 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="131">
<answer instance="131" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
there used to be falcons in New York? # LEFTY ! Ace jumps out of his car and starts skipping around the park with the <head>p_c</head> held high over his head. He looks insane. ACE (CONT'D)    from the waist gamble at cards or mahjong. # Homes, sometimes called " pigeon coops 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="839">
<answer instance="839" senseid="car"/>
<context>
growing crowd. LIEUTENANT FRANK GRIMES bails out before the car stops, smoothing out the wrinkles in his rumpled suit. He reacts with surprise left the <head>p_c</head> in reverse while she danced inside, flinging her hair. The car rolled down the hill, through a rickety fence, and into a scrubby pasture   RICK 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1052">
<answer instance="1052" senseid="car"/>
<context>
him with his hand and gave him a knowing, confidential look me for having an active imagination, and when they took me to school the <head>p_c</head> would be long and dark blue and very warm, because it would snow all    consists of the most expensive cargo, everything from designer clothing and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="151">
<answer instance="151" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
tough-talking law enforcement ranger who ran away from Manhattan to join original caption explained, the hawk had been trapped in the nooses of a lure <head>p_c</head> The falconer banded and released the bird immediately. #  town drunk six months ago, Cal had proven himself a steady friend. Sea Pigeon was tied 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="938">
<answer instance="938" senseid="car"/>
<context>
them, the skeleton is carefully pulled free from the ground. WE he talks to Jesus - a Jesus whom viewers will see riding in Daniel's <head>p_c</head> sitting in his house, conferring on the street. # Last fall,     6156 Atlanta once dreamed big and prospered. Few envisioned that an abandoned race car 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="764">
<answer instance="764" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
are very tender, remove the curry leaves and mash the mixture in the sport, and landlords also cracked down because gentrifiers did not like the <head>p_c</head> mess. Dr. Jerolmack estimates there are no more than 300 pigeon fliers left in    lending his experience in developing a care plan for captive breeding 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="141">
<answer instance="141" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in the world. (Both the Zenaida dove and the city, or rock Bus!' At this event he will announce the full title of his latest <head>p_c</head> volume, now known only as' The bird Wants a...' (Hyperion    . He stood at the drawing room window and shuddered at the sight of a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1282">
<answer instance="1282" senseid="car"/>
<context>
same old thing. " " I was hanging with kids that were thing. " Do you ever miss Detroit? " I asked her in the <head>p_c</head> on the way there, " because sometimes I wish we lived there with Grandma    seems skeptical. # " Other than drafting, Buddy's not been in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="140">
<answer instance="140" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
to be cowering in a corner of the room, hands clasped of bread, this plump little dove appears at first to behave like any city <head>p_c</head> in the world. (Both the Zenaida dove and the city, or rock    Bus!' At this event he will announce the full title of his latest 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1162">
<answer instance="1162" senseid="car"/>
<context>
I said, " Can we try to push-start it? " anyway . She remembered how much fun it was, as she sat fidgeting in her <head>p_c</head> on this hot night. # He didn't smell anymore. He hadn't    change the mechanical composition of a car that was rented. This is not a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="739">
<answer instance="739" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
sesame, a, pigeon peas, sunflower seeds, sorghum syrup, dark rye, wild rice, sunchokes size of a quarter, with his pinkie, beginning to rock faster. The <head>p_c</head> barely had its eyes open, but then it turned its head back and looked    . We descended until we were next to it. The corpse 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="581">
<answer instance="581" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
One can almost picture Carter and Andersen, oozing Anglophilia, sidling up to of prey or to escape predators. Confuciusornis sanctus, about the size of a <head>p_c</head> is the first bird known to have a beak with no teeth. //    a souffle dish. She also made delicious pies, such as rabbit pie 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1310">
<answer instance="1310" senseid="car"/>
<context>
she walked to the bridge and jumped off. RIVERA: Oh, one few hours till all the hydrogen left in the tank has vented. Push the <head>p_c</head> outdoors to keep your house from exploding, then call the dealer to tow it    She hated it so much that she never went outside except 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1170">
<answer instance="1170" senseid="car"/>
<context>
hit by a car at the age of 93, and that was just about a year ago, Scooter as a puppy. He was driving Anne's <head>p_c</head> when he saw another car hit the small dog. He watched the other car slow down, then speed   . COLIN is not visible among them. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1307">
<answer instance="1307" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Security. Just like on TV, the man shielded her head from bats this season. # Sports administrators likened the rulings and the memorandum to a <head>p_c</head> manufacturer recalling a model because it's unsafe but waiting a year before starting the    nothing else to think: The Browns were dead. Had to be. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="23">
<answer instance="23" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
most numerous bird on earth, so prolific its flocks hid the New York, where peregrine falcons roost atop the buildings and rain fine drops of <head>p_c</head> blood down on the hot dog vendors below, what we have here is rare    When he tried to volunteer for the Marines to serve in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="545">
<answer instance="545" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
whenever the windows were opened because of heat or paint fumes has messenger birds. Or that the Amyrlin will see any message I send by <head>p_c</head> It is a long journey, and hard. I would not send you    symptoms is usually HRT. All these presenting symptoms are lumped together into the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1250">
<answer instance="1250" senseid="car"/>
<context>
backfiring. I heard it, dismissed it, and went back to sleep. But never the human heart. # Joe reached the elevator first and pushed the <head>p_c</head> call button. We gathered behind him, quietly talking with Marsha's friends,    the girl's T-shirt. She shrieked. Urine dribbled down the side of the car door 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="19">
<answer instance="19" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Military veterans from across the country come to the mountain town the entire area of the courtyard below. In the middle of the net a <head>p_c</head> is trapped fast, its wings askew, its feet splayed, almost as if    to these guys and continue some level of parity so you would not 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1083">
<answer instance="1083" senseid="car"/>
<context>
less than 15 seconds, put the vehicle in park, turned off the -- or " previously owned " -- vehicle, ask yourself: " Are new <head>p_c</head> values better at certain times of the year than others? " # This used    of clarity, another hundred metres of onrushing progress. # And as 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="544">
<answer instance="544" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
proper management, market values can sometimes act to increase the probability floor, and the art teachers and their students were bothered by the stench of <head>p_c</head> droppings on the ledge whenever the windows were opened because of heat or paint fumes   has messenger birds. Or that the Amyrlin will see any 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1193">
<answer instance="1193" senseid="car"/>
<context>
" I'm not going to talk to the reporters, " he said comes to visit with his wife, Amy. I see them sitting in the <head>p_c</head> before coming in. They're arguing. Or Ben's arguing and Amy is    , Dec. 12 New York Yankee Alex Rodriguez does a quick wardrobe change behind 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="759">
<answer instance="759" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
speak pigeon to, you know, the use of the Hawaiian language theyre very, very act again, collapsed, grabbed at a shingle. Laughing to himself. A <head>p_c</head> skittered sideways. Fatima swooning, hooting Andy! Oh Andy! The other nuns    . To this day, there are those who defiantly write their return addresses as 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1098">
<answer instance="1098" senseid="car"/>
<context>
you might observe it and rubber neck because you don't engine repair traveling through the southwest with an old Indian man whose people likened a <head>p_c</head> to a human body: wheels as legs, distributor cap as a heart,    American automobile market. In 1970, U.S. automakers had eighty-six percent of the domestic 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="84">
<answer instance="84" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
real fun begins. # The idea behind sporting clays is that through the earpieces. " That rat must have done something pretty bad to that <head>p_c</head> to make it keep on like that. " # " Doubtless, " I  the day; her elegant, slender frame was far from that of a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="41">
<answer instance="41" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
a day, and tell them who it is for - do that, and I am, that she is a chimera, too. I was born a <head>p_c</head> she says, laughing. But then she says, not really. I    sixteen. " You know the one about Georgiana, my m other's pet pigeon? " " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="787">
<answer instance="787" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
and only then does he begin to slow up. Gripping the handles in modern poultry, with a high rate of success. By introducing the passenger <head>p_c</head> sperm again to the first hybrid generation, we decrease the number of alleles descended   realization makes Jake smile. Then a FLAPPING SOUND spins him around 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="252">
<answer instance="252" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon de-extinction campaign are encouraged to visit the Great Comeback page on Facebook. # " The bird), brown teal, bellbird, native robin, scaup, weka and <head>p_c</head> as well as reptiles like the rare tuatara lizard, have been reintroduced.  teapot, and Arabella distributed the fragrant libation with a practiced hand. # " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="636">
<answer instance="636" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
its labeled wooden cage, along with dozens of other birds, her fellow . Well, Nick thought it was adorable. Darla said it sounded like a <head>p_c</head> getting the Heimlich. The gerbil, whose name was Porlock, had come with    instrument which will produce an intemal variant. The butterfly has a genome, the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="718">
<answer instance="718" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Pigeon River. Is that a place? Cold Mountain? The Doctor shrugs, not , and it will just stand there, pacing nervously, oblivious to information a <head>p_c</head> would use to open its own food dish. Give the territorial dove a trained    slides from her chair and walks to the kitchen with the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="239">
<answer instance="239" senseid="car"/>
<context>
position within Marino. ACE I did it! I did it! I caught the white pigeon! I caught the white pigeon! Ace jumps out of his <head>p_c</head> and starts    possible. Germ cells develop into sperm or eggs, which will produce a passenger-like pigeon in the next generation. # STATUS: Scientists have so 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="168">
<answer instance="168" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the two birds as kin. Rock doves wheel in flocks around bare through a washhouse and a paved area containing a coal shed, pump, and <head>p_c</head> cote. I gave a sigh of relief as we arrived in the warm,  had carried her tea to her workroom and was halfway through the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="576">
<answer instance="576" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the two birds as kin. Rock doves wheel in flocks around bare through a washhouse and a paved area containing a coal shed, pump, and <head>p_c</head> cote. I gave a sigh of relief as we arrived in the warm,  had carried her tea to her workroom and was halfway through the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="459">
<answer instance="459" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
decline, the forests it depended upon shrinking, and its numbers am even more impatient for tomorrow to arrive so that I can tell the other <head>p_c</head> " VALERIAN'S DISPOSITION, as he continued pacing the length of his study    Some experts argue that their numbers constitute as big a public health hazard 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="610">
<answer instance="610" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in fact there is nowhere in particular to hang my toothbrush anymore. hawk spotted soaring down the ridge, it's time to " flash " the <head>p_c</head> Tommy pulls on a string attached to the vest the pigeon wears, lifting    and crawl, crumbs of wallpaper catching on her sweater. She could hear 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1054">
<answer instance="1054" senseid="car"/>
<context>
and mobile phones. Freight is often transported in large pallets, which are the editor at the time, and so hotels. I put off approaching the <head>p_c</head> Otherwise he might have shot I tried Grace's cell phone number again,   drew Julianne from her state of shock. She pushed the button to lower 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1277">
<answer instance="1277" senseid="car"/>
<context>
comes with the interior d'elegaaaance. " So, of course, being Italian, of cars going uphill was slow and wiggly. A man leaning out of his <head>p_c</head> window, flicking cigarette ash, smiled at two teenaged girls who walked with their    orbits around here. I have asked myself why many times. Why solar 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="400">
<answer instance="400" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Recaito is a cilantro cooking base that can be purchased at be safe to say that his concern would be exactly that, not to be <head>p_c</head> holed, not to be stereotyped, but to be judged on his ability.    third part of the trinity when Ms. Maud Johnson flew in like a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="784">
<answer instance="784" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
MILES # Excuse me? # GANGSTER # Who do you want me . Its pocked concrete and slick, hot tar spring into sharp relief. A <head>p_c</head> nips at a mite under its wing. I pull my eye away to get    , " even spending the better part of a year painstakingly 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1122">
<answer instance="1122" senseid="car"/>
<context>
arrive to and leave from your destination without incident. John had heard a man had been arrested who had a load of dynamite in his <head>p_c</head> It turned out that he had nothing to do with it. He was    Force. " It's almost like this cult following where they get in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1107">
<answer instance="1107" senseid="car"/>
<context>
abundant, efficiently generated electric power, in a much lighter package, that find out that he rented a car, and that the mileage on the rental <head>p_c</head> was dead on from Burbank to the murder scene and back. To me and    In both cases, a firm, steady application of the brake will 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="183">
<answer instance="183" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
# Q WHAT EXTINCT SPECIES WOULD YOU BRING BACK? # 1. The passenger pigeon, because it must have been # 2. Anything but the passenger <head>p_c</head>    by an entourage that includes the ghost of the Marquess of Queensberry and a hard-drinking pigeon (Norm MacDonald). (Adult Swim, Oct. 27, 10: 30    Democrats 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="449">
<answer instance="449" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
a day, and tell them who it is for - do that, and I am, that she is a chimera, too. I was born a <head>p_c</head> she says, laughing. But then she says, not really. I    sixteen. " You know the one about Georgiana, my m other's pet pigeon? " " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="594">
<answer instance="594" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Mountain: Pigeon John, Grayskul, Crew 54, Curbside Jones Hotel Vegas: (expletive) -- exhale on the way up and inhale on the way down. Do not <head>p_c</head> poke your head forward. Curl up as slowly and smoothly as possible. The    junk exception, and then the rest of your investments have to fit 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="510">
<answer instance="510" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
I caught the white? Ace slows down and begins to look around warily air like the full moon, you know. " PGPH singing Well, the <head>p_c</head> woman told me she was God's wife. I said, " Is that    : Absolutely. Noah's dove was actually a pigeon. In fact, a pigge and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="259">
<answer instance="259" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
different kinds of arguments regarding why he should be allowed to drive. # his liking, although the sounds in his ears -- dove, cuckoo, green <head>p_c</head> parrot, sparrow, flamingo, duck, and quail -- destroyed any illusions   a pigeon. " # I say, " The weird thing was that the pigeon kept 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1212">
<answer instance="1212" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Dust rolled in the open windows and stuck to our faces. " Very When an attack finally came, it wasn't a mortar. It was a <head>p_c</head> bomb positioned near the hotel checkpoint that missed the Australian ambassador, but killed a    in her stroller. Other infants will only quiet down with a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="382">
<answer instance="382" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
con artists pretend to find a stash of money in an envelope have premarital sex, smoke publicly, and walk with toes out -- rather than <head>p_c</head> toed as in the feminine posture of kimono clad women displaying chastity -- Japanese men    terms with that emotion? -- he hands me, without smiling, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="368">
<answer instance="368" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
blood), tickling my nose? So that I sneeze &; topple to the which I had discovered I particularly liked. There were also jelled duck eggs, <head>p_c</head> eggs in sauce, shrimps with chicken and peas, chicken and scallops with ginger    to this drill is a popper-style target with an attachment that will 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="476">
<answer instance="476" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in phase 1 and integrating these into band-tailed bird cells Almighty was unable to find a single Sicilian household where he could send in his <head>p_c</head> without the bird being attacked by the girl's mother and a gang of her    better suited to the short story form. It is also the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="54">
<answer instance="54" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
roofing lead, most particularly from churches, which earned him his Some birds have been taken out of their cages and are being expertly examined by <head>p_c</head> fanciers. The birds are lightly pinched between two fingers, the length of their    about 150 birds, and we fly them from Las Vegas to Montana. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="534">
<answer instance="534" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
He has a legion of men with him, many more than before. on the boat and, at the Tower, the throngs of visitors and the <head>p_c</head> droppings. # If I could just find a copy of the Times, I    . And it takes a while. Sometimes too long, as the extinct 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="527">
<answer instance="527" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
gone from the skies. I've made it my life's work to , and for flute, he picks the long whistles of the white-bellied green imperial <head>p_c</head> and the descending run of short notes uttered by the strawberry finch. He elects    actually like birds. One is Mo Willems, author of books like' 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="971">
<answer instance="971" senseid="car"/>
<context>
TV. # Reminders such as wearing a bracelet that jingles when your I don't give a damn about the Blue Book. I know what the <head>p_c</head> is worth. " Just then Jordan, the kid, came up to the    occupations involved with transporting these drugs such as truck drivers, export-importers, and used 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="193">
<answer instance="193" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
for their dad's drinking bouts when he came home late, stumbling Of those wayward days he says: " You become the human equivalent of a <head>p_c</head> or a seagull. People see us without seeing us, sometimes they give us    , long wait before we went out to the yard to the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="917">
<answer instance="917" senseid="car"/>
<context>
car. She could imagine cutting the cord, but in the crunch, she could I was fine but at the same time I am driving a <head>p_c</head> and the car had drugs in it, so technically I have to go to jail for it    Trump, make a million dollars and buy me 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="659">
<answer instance="659" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Tenn. 1- 800-251-9100 or www.pigeonforge.tn.us. World Chicken Festival. Sept. 21-24. permission from the Web site **33;244;TOOLONG # Readers who are interested in joining the passenger <head>p_c</head> de-extinction campaign are encouraged to visit the Great Comeback page on Facebook. # " The    bird), brown teal, bellbird, native robin, scaup, weka and pigeon, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="952">
<answer instance="952" senseid="car"/>
<context>
a shuttle bus to the Canton cotton mill from Free Home # STARKS falters slightly as he walks. JACKIE helps him make it to the <head>p_c</head> much like before... # # STARKS # Thanks. # INT. JACKIE    rising fuel efficiency of gasoline-powered vehicles will make incremental mileage more affordable to consumers. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1332">
<answer instance="1332" senseid="car"/>
<context>
get somewhere. We should respect that. KELLERMAN: Yes. And that . People need to see she was more than the suspect that was driving the <head>p_c</head> COOPER# Does any of this make sense to you, Amy? CAREY-JONES# No    The warning shots are difficult to see, almost impossible to hear in a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="870">
<answer instance="870" senseid="car"/>
<context>
the Swiss government refunds 50 percent of this cost. The gas produced by class. It's a kind of every person category. Anybody can drive their <head>p_c</head> off the street and run the quarter-mile. There's not a lot of money    thick through the middle. He was glad when Stevie let herself out 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="555">
<answer instance="555" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
delivered word of the first Olympics. Is that true? Mr-BLECHMAN: Yeah, five broods a year are possible -- and has a convenient length of gestation: <head>p_c</head> eggs hatch in 18 days, the young fledge five weeks later and are sexually    one asks to " see one. " Upon this command, a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1003">
<answer instance="1003" senseid="car"/>
<context>
in Canada or Alabama. After weighing the pros and cons, you decide a Mercedes 300 SL roadster. To this day, that Mercedes remains his favorite <head>p_c</head> # The museum houses a wide variety of vehicles, including many exotic Ferraris    the power in me didn't like it one bit. It told me 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="683">
<answer instance="683" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
would write out a tiny note, attaching it to the bird risk of indulging in a cheap metaphor, I must tell you that one dead <head>p_c</head> was floating in the river. # Charlie reads the paper. He complained about  dress that winter, and on Easter she wore it to the First 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="362">
<answer instance="362" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
me for a beat then nodded. " Fitness reports and other out. As she shifted his shoulders to spare his face from resting in the <head>p_c</head> droppings, his eyes fluttered open and his arms twitched at his side. She    ended late. Like firecrackers, or thunder. On Labor Day there was the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1100">
<answer instance="1100" senseid="car"/>
<context>
and the Japanese had three percent. Today, Japan has forty percent is barely beginning to drizzle, the little raindrops muddying up the dust on the <head>p_c</head> windshield. She drives slowly on the gravel, getting them well off the forest  toward the house. # Driver was up, over and on him as 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1245">
<answer instance="1245" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Jackson says. # Long distances often scare off potential bike commuters, , and Dan would sign the waiver so the episode could air. But the <head>p_c</head> kept going steadily forward. We turned onto Sunset Boulevard and suddenly, even at    be forbidden, that theyre free to do, and what their passengers in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="414">
<answer instance="414" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon; cockatoo feathers; red paint; white paint; pots; garden baskets ( the grillwork and dropped to the ground. # In the bubbling cooing of the <head>p_c</head> house, she thought and she wrote. Rufina thought about Eugenio waiting for her    PHOTOGRAPHS: DAMIAN RUSSELL Photograph: The Alfred Dunhill flagship store. Photograph: Roasted pigeon 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="102">
<answer instance="102" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
I caught the white? Ace slows down and begins to look around warily air like the full moon, you know. " PGPH singing Well, the <head>p_c</head> woman told me she was God's wife. I said, " Is that    : Absolutely. Noah's dove was actually a pigeon. In fact, a pigge and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1278">
<answer instance="1278" senseid="car"/>
<context>
flicking cigarette ash, smiled at two teenaged girls who walked with their orbits around here. I have asked myself why many times. Why solar noon <head>p_c</head> Why Paublo van? But I have also stopped and asked people to translate    of the complaint, that a police officer said she's in somebody else's 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1129">
<answer instance="1129" senseid="car"/>
<context>
sports car to run on nonpolluting lemur urine. Congratulations, Americans. You've wised up driver Dale Earnhardt, Sr.. Earnhardt died on February 18, 2001 after his <head>p_c</head> was hit by another and slid into the wall on the last turn of the    less and less useful to me with each issue. I 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="146">
<answer instance="146" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
" # " That's a relief. I'd really hate to have (Voiceover) He points out that the birds have an important place in history. A <head>p_c</head> delivered word of the first Olympics. Is that true? Mr-BLECHMAN: Yeah,    five broods a year are possible -- and has a convenient length of gestation: 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="562">
<answer instance="562" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
had it, Georges to the days of Babylon. Kuwait, after all, had been a fat bird ready for the plucking. But in six weeks, the <head>p_c</head> had begun to    no answer but the owl hooting in the night, the mourning coo of the pigeon at dawn. # At first light, Apalura 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="550">
<answer instance="550" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
volume, now known only as' The bird Wants a...' (Hyperion . He stood at the drawing room window and shuddered at the sight of a <head>p_c</head> flying to the coop. # He trudged through the snow and found the landed    HAMPSHIRE NEWPORT - Residents tired of cleaning up pigeon droppings have 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="52">
<answer instance="52" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
DISPOSITION, as he continued pacing the length of his study Some experts argue that their numbers constitute as big a public health hazard as their <head>p_c</head> relatives. Only a glut of Vulture Medicae can account for the creation of such  bones and his fingers lost their nimbleness. He took to " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1121">
<answer instance="1121" senseid="car"/>
<context>
back into her lane. Screw this, she thought, her heart thudding. or treks back and forth to summer camp and baseball practice, having a well-maintained <head>p_c</head> can ensure that you arrive to and leave from your destination without incident. John    had heard a man had been arrested who had a load 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="987">
<answer instance="987" senseid="car"/>
<context>
car, but as of Tuesday evening, the gunman had eluded capture. was impounded late Tuesday from the parking lot at the Logan airport. The rental <head>p_c</head> evidently came under suspicion because it had been recorded several times on surveillance cameras at    sky was purple. Mr. Smith stood in his yard and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1242">
<answer instance="1242" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Ford LTD, feeling whatever modicum of triumph had seemed his evaporating which one of them their uncle might be in. But their father parked the <head>p_c</head> and walked them straight there. Now that the boys had been let out they    . Graham, slumbering with the help of pills, takes a 26-minute, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="872">
<answer instance="872" senseid="car"/>
<context>
the elevator. The doors were open. As soon as she opposition leader was apparently the target of an assassination attempt last year in a suspicious <head>p_c</head> accident. So why was he sitting alone and unguarded in his holiday home late    -- besides design and production expenses. The Italian auto industry -- 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1262">
<answer instance="1262" senseid="car"/>
<context>
drove all night across the country. Matthew was barely conscious when he arrived Channel 4 TV. LARSON: (Voiceover) Next, KNBC's investigative reporter revisited the second <head>p_c</head> wash where our worker was paid only in tips, about 80 cents an hour    His eyes widen in surprise. # TOM # I'll meet you 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1158">
<answer instance="1158" senseid="car"/>
<context>
seat beside him for the chisel. Where had it gone? There it was forth). AS anyone familiar with L. A. knows, you must have a <head>p_c</head> to get around. Thus I made the acquaintance of the burgeoning class of those    and construction of their model cars. For speed, students compete to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1207">
<answer instance="1207" senseid="car"/>
<context>
a halt. The pressure seals hissed as the doors opened, and , to suffer wrath behind closed doors for a day or so. # One <head>p_c</head> honked as it sped past, someone whooped from another. Then a car slowed    Congress made car manufacturers clean up their act by switching to unleaded 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1352">
<answer instance="1352" senseid="car"/>
<context>
up the pass. It was two long traverses to the slate quarry -- enough, though totally inaccurate. The voice is gorgeous and alluring. Were a <head>p_c</head> salesman to have the voice of Frank Bascombe, he could probably persuade me to    to do with the drive itself, particularly since it was nighttime 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1222">
<answer instance="1222" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Subaru WRX -- anywhere he wants. He also skis so perfectly all the way down, so all there was was silent shooting and long quiet <head>p_c</head> chases; it all seemed so peaceful, so faraway. It was what I    says. " I had a nice job, a beautiful girlfriend, a nice car, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="992">
<answer instance="992" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Lindsay and her older sister first arrived, they both felt said that talking to their teens about allowance was more stressful than haggling with a <head>p_c</head> salesman. But experts say we need to be clear and upfront if our kids    . " I can't eat it either. " # They're in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="663">
<answer instance="663" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
during the Allies' Normandy invasion in World War II. # Or for trying sperm to inseminate band-tailed pigeons, creating hybrids (half band-tailed pigeon, half passenger <head>p_c</head> Artificial insemination is used extensively in modern poultry, with a high rate    hear, " Walter said. # " I shouldn't? " # " Pigeon, you 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="774">
<answer instance="774" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
cousin. # 2 Identify and synthesize mutations that distinguish the passenger take a vacation or pay for hospital bills, and it never occurs to the <head>p_c</head> that he's part of the con. " # The shill in Mr. Molina    on the futon to reshelve the mag &; I sniff the feather 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1123">
<answer instance="1123" senseid="car"/>
<context>
turned out that he had nothing to do with it. He was Force. " It's almost like this cult following where they get in the <head>p_c</head> and come down here. " The task force identified 213 victims of human trafficking    relationship with the family of Dana Spencer, the 16-year-old girl who 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="42">
<answer instance="42" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
born a pigeon, she says, laughing. But then she says, not really. I sixteen. " You know the one about Georgiana, my m other's pet <head>p_c</head> " " Yeah, " Brian said. Mickey said. " How about    last night. Ms-ARIANNE-AMBERT: (Voiceover) He's my pet. SPENCER: (Voiceover) The pigeon doctors tried so 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="954">
<answer instance="954" senseid="car"/>
<context>
take him to the hospital. But Quan just ignored him and dentist as well as the front desk attendant, I watched as she entered her <head>p_c</head> a top-of-the-line new Mercedes with the temporary license plates StUl visible. In seeing   around a hairpin turn, and say, " Uh... Sid's car. " " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="117">
<answer instance="117" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in and shipped from a garage in a blue-collar part of a Hollywood character. When Shane met him he was doing street-corner cons-green-goods hustles and <head>p_c</head> drops. Shane had first busted him when he was still a rookie working vice    decades of a brutal brand of communism, benefits from U.S. aid. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="574">
<answer instance="574" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
leg. Melissa tugs on the harness and the bird walks away project and cold-called asking to participate; he has since gone on to lead the <head>p_c</head> resurrection initiative out of a lab in California. # " We always joke that    Nevada Barr (Avon, $ 5). The fourth book in the Anna 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1208">
<answer instance="1208" senseid="car"/>
<context>
to suffer wrath behind closed doors for a day or so. # One car honked as it sped past, someone whooped from another. Then a <head>p_c</head> slowed    Congress made car manufacturers clean up their act by switching to unleaded gas. The car companies screamed bloody murder, claiming their products would be 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1093">
<answer instance="1093" senseid="car"/>
<context>
wheel of a new 520 -- horsepower Chevy Monte Carlo, Casey any gang members nearby with bloodier ideas on their tiny minds. Calvin parked the <head>p_c</head> half a block up from the store and hopped out, taking the riot gun    record, I have walked, taken Muni, ridden my bike and driven 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="45">
<answer instance="45" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
painted from reference photographs lent to me by the New Only a few domestic animals produce as wide a range of physical types as the <head>p_c</head> the dog, the chicken and (icthyologists suggest) the goldfish. The    we can not afford to teach children such lessons in cruelty. # As the pigeon 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="256">
<answer instance="256" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
you shouldn't hear a story like this, " he said. He , but only three forest birds became extinct -- the carolina parakeet, the passenger <head>p_c</head> and the ivory-billed woodpecker. Moreover, habitat loss probably did not play the major    Killed By an errant shot off the foot of an Argentine soccer 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="423">
<answer instance="423" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
then on to a strange little pavilion with an asymmetrical facade, and " We have listened, Sister Scald. Gaunt and Bone sent warning by carrier <head>p_c</head> that they would seek a king's tear this night, unaware we'd knowingly    else. # Henri-Franois brings us the news as we're sitting down to some 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="829">
<answer instance="829" senseid="car"/>
<context>
a thumbs-up, and the lights flashed at me. Ranger was listening to the his wife, Melanie, " bless her heart, " on trips to European <head>p_c</head> factories -- Danny jumped in. He'd gone to Ireland, where his parents    # n Age: 30 # n Hometown: Pittsboro, Ind. # n Car: Chevrolet 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="628">
<answer instance="628" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon poop. Could the droppings, they wondered, be responsible for the background noise pigeon's leg. # 1906 # Edward developed a near-phobia of pigeons. A <head>p_c</head> returned to his coop, and he learned he'd lost his position as President    above all others, a grouse and duck hunter, a Lab trainer, a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1288">
<answer instance="1288" senseid="car"/>
<context>
the' Two all-beef patties' mantra into a McDonald's drive-through speaker box , like an apple falling from a tree, like a rock falling through a <head>p_c</head> window. For the rest of the night, whenever she slips a scaloppine    a full-size car. " So the salesman asked if we wanted to order 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="749">
<answer instance="749" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
he discovered that his pigeon had escaped the cage. His pigeon also knew where to go. . And it got better. Everyday he'd watch the <head>p_c</head> Everyday the pigeon would watch him. I saw him learn. Learn that there was one more    ingredients (though always the best provenance). Some recipes aren't 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="217">
<answer instance="217" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
I caught the white pigeon, I caught the white? Ace slows down fly level, I heard the deep percussive blast of the shotgun, and the <head>p_c</head> jerked back, propelled by the impact, and fell like a limp dishrag from    ground movement. 4. Evaluate nearly a mile of pipe on steep slopes 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="309">
<answer instance="309" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
GSU School of Business / JAMES SMALLWOOD / Staff 42480 # Decatur drift in slowly, with their lips slightly parted, to discover a solitary white <head>p_c</head> wheeling about freely inside the enormous domed chamber. In the near-dark, its ghostly  ramble. Names of loved ones. MRS. MORGAN (listening to Inman) Pigeon River. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="795">
<answer instance="795" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
said he learned much of traits. # 3 Swap those bits of DNA for the corresponding bits in rock pigeon stem cells, thus creating passenger <head>p_c</head> stem cells. # 4 Convert the stem    and he learned he'd lost his position as President of the Society. A pigeon, and he was warned 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="17">
<answer instance="17" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
to some pigeon, red currants, apricots, and wine: the Tribunal, according to the my vision. I turn, ready to throw. Someone is holding the white <head>p_c</head> above his head, its wings spread between his fingertips. He lets it go    aka Doux Papa, c. 1937 # PHOTO (BLACK &; WHITE): Hubert Pigeon, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1105">
<answer instance="1105" senseid="car"/>
<context>
" The smile froze on her face. Jaine hated wasting a of all new cars will have them by 2010. These units will supply the <head>p_c</head> with abundant, efficiently generated electric power, in a much lighter package, that    find out that he rented a car, and that the mileage on the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="661">
<answer instance="661" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
such an odd nickname! " Belinda mused, tipping a little scalding tea in photographic transmission, he's best known for sending his photo film by carrier <head>p_c</head> during the Allies' Normandy invasion in World War II. # Or for trying    sperm to inseminate band-tailed pigeons, creating hybrids (half band-tailed pigeon, half passenger 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="813">
<answer instance="813" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
this essay were adapted with permission from the Web site **33;244;TOOLONG thing that was all over their fancy horn-shaped antenna yet didn't change was the <head>p_c</head> poop. So they cleaned it out, and sure enough, the noise dropped    live bands and children's rides. 843-871-9622, ext. 119, flowertownfestival.org. TENNESSEE Pigeon Forge --- 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1231">
<answer instance="1231" senseid="car"/>
<context>
on the way to the hotel, this time parked on a street in my car. Mercury Sable. Don't know why I said it was her <head>p_c</head> It was mine. She was on her way to her rehearsal dinner.    and cold, but feeling really mellow. Monty fell asleep as soon as the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="313">
<answer instance="313" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Strongly condemning the adoration of military culture that seems so prevalent in lip between her teeth, the way her husband used to do. " Silly <head>p_c</head> " Galya said. " He talks French, not Moscow. Like you    and rough cloth straps help the players get into positions like the can opener 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="431">
<answer instance="431" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
most numerous bird on earth, so prolific its flocks hid the New York, where peregrine falcons roost atop the buildings and rain fine drops of <head>p_c</head> blood down on the hot dog vendors below, what we have here is rare    When he tried to volunteer for the Marines to serve in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="357">
<answer instance="357" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in the sport, and landlords also cracked down because gentrifiers did not like the pigeon mess. Dr. Jerolmack estimates there are no more than 300 <head>p_c</head> fliers left in    lending his experience in developing a care plan for captive breeding of the new passenger pigeon. Advanced Cell Technology Inc., under the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="717">
<answer instance="717" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
GSU School of Business / JAMES SMALLWOOD / Staff 42480 # Decatur drift in slowly, with their lips slightly parted, to discover a solitary white <head>p_c</head> wheeling about freely inside the enormous domed chamber. In the near-dark, its ghostly  ramble. Names of loved ones. MRS. MORGAN (listening to Inman) Pigeon River. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1234">
<answer instance="1234" senseid="car"/>
<context>
show up, red lights spinning. He walked around the X3 and looked has more. (Begin-VT) JIM-AXELROD: Known for a reputation as shiny as the new <head>p_c</head> in one of its showroom, Toyota is now scrambling to fix deadly accelerator pedals    cells do not respond well to insulin. Imagine that you try 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1266">
<answer instance="1266" senseid="car"/>
<context>
retirement security and family vacations. # " moves come straight out of The Oprah Winfrey Show. (" You get a car! And you get a <head>p_c</head> Everybody gets a car! ") #    than a glance in this land of dark. And on both sides of the car, the dead brush at 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="848">
<answer instance="848" senseid="car"/>
<context>
his car broken into, he wants someone to go down. ! UNIDENTIFIED-MALE: " Crown backed down then and, without another word, stormed off to his <head>p_c</head> Cade watched him until he drove away, then breathed a frustrated sigh and    's new hero looked back at the blown riders in amazement. When 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1271">
<answer instance="1271" senseid="car"/>
<context>
It shouldn't take me more than forty minutes once I land, so ? Why don't you call your folks to come out here, get their <head>p_c</head> and drive you home. " " SEE, THAT'S YOUR PROBLEM,    false imprisonment and said Wednesday that was based on the fact that he turned the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1333">
<answer instance="1333" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Does any of this make sense to you, Amy? CAREY-JONES# No The warning shots are difficult to see, almost impossible to hear in a speeding <head>p_c</head> at a long distance. Usually the last resort for us was attempting to fire    , some guy is wearing your head for a hat. Lucy 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="647">
<answer instance="647" senseid="car"/>
<context>
position within Marino. ACE I did it! I did it! I caught the white pigeon! I caught the white pigeon! Ace jumps out of his <head>p_c</head> and starts    possible. Germ cells develop into sperm or eggs, which will produce a passenger-like pigeon in the next generation. # STATUS: Scientists have so 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="487">
<answer instance="487" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
" That son of a bitch lives around here, " Owen announced the bris, " Meir said, " where do you want to have the <head>p_c</head> hopping? " " The what? " " The pidyon haben. " He    no questions. How much single malt you think it takes to warm up 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="85">
<answer instance="85" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
make it keep on like that. " # " Doubtless, " I the day; her elegant, slender frame was far from that of a pouter <head>p_c</head> and she liked to think hers was a lean and intelligent face that would    Snowball, an innovative pig Napoleon, a tyrant pig Clover, a forgetful 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="128">
<answer instance="128" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Consider the progression of excess which finally led to the with a sweep of other interested scientists to fully assemble the genome of the passenger <head>p_c</head> and explore its natural history in a way that historical accounts have never afforded before  n't a crystal ball big enough for what we could 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="557">
<answer instance="557" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
to allow the squad to sight in their guns. After the practice " " Can they? " said Larker dubiously. " Blithe Spirit has the <head>p_c</head> homing instinct, yet the shape, airspeed, and control of a fast-flying bird    aisles. # I notice a mourning dove -- the classy cousin of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="949">
<answer instance="949" senseid="car"/>
<context>
production car in 1996 that was a plug-in electric car had to do as a team was teach him how to drive the top fuel <head>p_c</head> successfully. We took an approach that we would never put him in a situation    's glad to see him in the race. " I'd vote 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="791">
<answer instance="791" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in the feminine posture of kimono clad women displaying chastity -- Japanese men terms with that emotion? -- he hands me, without smiling, the carrier <head>p_c</head> he is holding. # Its feathers feel slightly damp -- like satin. The    all meals and climbing equipment. Cost: NZ$695. Contact: www.alpinerecreation.com KAYAK CAMPING PIGEON 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="812">
<answer instance="812" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
you say we take a look at the Pigeon River? " # . At that point, we will have success: the de-extinction of the passenger <head>p_c</head> # Portions of this essay were adapted with permission from the Web site **33;244;TOOLONG    thing that was all over their fancy horn-shaped antenna yet didn't 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1206">
<answer instance="1206" senseid="car"/>
<context>
- NIGHT 164 Hans sees a black Mercedes coming down the percent. # Doug was so deep in his thoughts that he barely noticed his <head>p_c</head> sighing to a halt. The pressure seals hissed as the doors opened, and    , to suffer wrath behind closed doors for a day or so. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="997">
<answer instance="997" senseid="car"/>
<context>
obliterated, burned beyond recognition. " Says Townsend: " The whole thing be found. She searched for days before learning that the floodwaters had carried the <head>p_c</head> several blocks away, where it jumped a fence and disappeared. Three days later    three. " What I wanted to say was, let's jump in the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="451">
<answer instance="451" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
m other's pet pigeon? " " Yeah, " Brian said. Mickey said. " How about last night. Ms-ARIANNE-AMBERT: (Voiceover) He's my pet. SPENCER: (Voiceover) The <head>p_c</head> doctors tried so hard to save last night didn't make it. Dr-ROBERTS:    to have its way with her. Pierre Puvis de Chavannes' " The Carrier 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1312">
<answer instance="1312" senseid="car"/>
<context>
She sent me to the post office and the grocery store the electric grid. But they must produce enough power to juice up an electric <head>p_c</head> # This year, Sachs is working with NYIT and MIT (where he    David Bradford needs just one more thing, his taxi. Mr-BRADFORD: Hello, car. OSGOOD: 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1044">
<answer instance="1044" senseid="car"/>
<context>
that is used by Queen Elizabeth. # MR. PIECH'S dream, loyally at gunpoint. He said he had delivered a pizza and was returning to his <head>p_c</head> when a man hit him on the back of the head with a handgun.  and dropped the man at the edge of the house. Pike 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="458">
<answer instance="458" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
of approved uses in the " R-1 Single Family Residence District likely to become extinct. Yet by the end of the century the red-breasted passenger <head>p_c</head> was in catastrophic decline, the forests it depended upon shrinking, and its numbers  am even more impatient for tomorrow to arrive so that I can 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="924">
<answer instance="924" senseid="car"/>
<context>
# Before the plant closed, Sandy Beck had started to lose . # Ian tried to bolt. # Norse slammed the boy hard into the <head>p_c</head> # " Don't, " Malone called out. " Do as he    focus really well on one thing. You can't distract me in a race car. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="148">
<answer instance="148" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
in 18 days, the young fledge five weeks later and are sexually one asks to " see one. " Upon this command, a practice clay <head>p_c</head> is released to allow the squad to sight in their guns. After the practice    " " Can they? " said Larker dubiously. " Blithe Spirit 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="300">
<answer instance="300" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
of the Pigeon Drop and the Greek Return, but Opel wasn't a man.) Threely of Paris, pointed, innumerable. Richelieu turns, and crosses to an elaborate <head>p_c</head> coop. Servants attach messages to the legs of carrier pigeons. # Rochefort steps    HOTO (BLACK &; WHITE): Members of a " stellar " team from 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1294">
<answer instance="1294" senseid="car"/>
<context>
that it was a younger man's vehicle. Although he was seventy-two, partially your electricity consumption-and bill-by 30 to 50 percent. Gasoline: Use mass transit or <head>p_c</head> pool to work, bike, and walk to local errands. Avoid buying gas-guzzling    , smoking some dope, swimming in the Poplar River outside town -- when 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="122">
<answer instance="122" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
dove gliding in a shaft of moonlight. Then it leaves the moonlight good luck. KOTB: OK. GIFFORD: I would say it's good luck for the <head>p_c</head> KOTB: Yeah, exactly. GIFFORD: He's the only one that feels better    , from itunes.apple.com # Willems, M. (2011). Don't let the pigeon run this app! 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="88">
<answer instance="88" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
12-gauge, 11/4-ounce, 1220-fps loads that hit birds hard without kicking . Through the rearview mirror I watched as a cloud of smoke the color of <head>p_c</head> feathers lifted in a single piece up above the black scribble of trees. My    Los Angeles Angels' pitcher Dane De La Rosa. Thursday night in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="886">
<answer instance="886" senseid="car"/>
<context>
up, packed to the gills with stolen, looted appliances. # REDNECK other few bus passengers had vanished. Repeat signs warned me away from parking a <head>p_c</head> from lingering, loitering, or gathering. I hadn't consulted a guidebook    returns to the one town she's been running from. Announcer: (On car radio) 104.9, KKRV, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="221">
<answer instance="221" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
returned to his coop, and he learned he'd lost his position as President above all others, a grouse and duck hunter, a Lab trainer, a <head>p_c</head> shooter, and an occasional big-game hunter. No outdoor writer has had a more    Captive breeding. Goal: using altered cells from phase 3 to create rock 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="633">
<answer instance="633" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
set in a complicated circle of dark antique gold " (9) she cut the fat gland off the end of a chicken, and killed a <head>p_c</head> quietly without breaking its tiny bones. She showed him how to add pimento pepper   I'd gotten to the point where I didn't mind being a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1243">
<answer instance="1243" senseid="car"/>
<context>
walked them straight there. Now that the boys had been let out they . Graham, slumbering with the help of pills, takes a 26-minute, backseat <head>p_c</head> ride across Vancouver. A second exercise in the representation of inner and outer states    n't hear that he ran a red light and pulled out 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1110">
<answer instance="1110" senseid="car"/>
<context>
car. She leaned into the back seat, brought out paper, books, and 1988 graduation from Evergreen High School, eight of Evergreen's teenagers were killed in <head>p_c</head> accidents. The common factor in all of these deaths was not drinking or reckless    up because I knew that Joanne and the two children were 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1169">
<answer instance="1169" senseid="car"/>
<context>
realize his error or stop or consult his map.9 He continued was calling to remember Sister Rosemary Lynch, who died after being hit by a <head>p_c</head> at the age of 93, and that was just about a year ago,    Scooter as a puppy. He was driving Anne's car when he saw 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="951">
<answer instance="951" senseid="car"/>
<context>
I'd vote for Renee Ellmers, " he cracks. # The next There weren't too many places to go to and the family had just one <head>p_c</head> Her father drove a shuttle bus to the Canton cotton mill from Free Home   # STARKS falters slightly as he walks. JACKIE helps him make 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1113">
<answer instance="1113" senseid="car"/>
<context>
with a date. I couldn't even compare Billy to a date. He Factory, has concerns a little closer to home. When she bought a new <head>p_c</head> recently, Gall chose a Mazda Tribute specifically for its good gas mileage, even    parade of 200 of them in Texas in 1996, " he says. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1039">
<answer instance="1039" senseid="car"/>
<context>
moments that the blood in her brain was a result of the car accident. They would also deduce that since she'd been in a single- <head>p_c</head> crash    it's probably the newest care that I've ever had, and the coolest car I ever had. I worked really hard for it. It's a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="708">
<answer instance="708" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
of the Pigeon Drop and the Greek Return, but Opel wasn't a man.) Threely of Paris, pointed, innumerable. Richelieu turns, and crosses to an elaborate <head>p_c</head> coop. Servants attach messages to the legs of carrier pigeons. # Rochefort steps    HOTO (BLACK &; WHITE): Members of a " stellar " team from 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1223">
<answer instance="1223" senseid="car"/>
<context>
car chases; it all seemed so peaceful, so faraway. It was what I says. " I had a nice job, a beautiful girlfriend, a nice <head>p_c</head> I owned my own house. As far as the world was concerned,    Versatility Performance Workhorse Fuel Efficiency Design Luxury Technical Innovation JUST ABOUT ANYBODY CAN 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="5">
<answer instance="5" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
3: Right. Mr-BILL-JAYCOX: Pigeon fancier, we like to call ourselves. BRAVER: bird fancier. Mr-JAYCOX: Yeah Yams; pigs; tobacco; dyed rattan; bird-of-paradise plumes; crests of Goura <head>p_c</head> cockatoo feathers; red paint; white paint; pots; garden baskets (    the grillwork and dropped to the ground. # In the bubbling cooing of the pigeon 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1309">
<answer instance="1309" senseid="car"/>
<context>
car had ducked a bumper, gone end over end, rolled a few times ejecting after her. You just don't know. EDWARD: He was at his <head>p_c</head> and she walked to the bridge and jumped off. RIVERA: Oh, one    few hours till all the hydrogen left in the tank has vented. Push 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="181">
<answer instance="181" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
but all we can hope to do with the sea-going forms . # I don't look forward to returning to the bonfire and the clay <head>p_c</head> massacre, but I can't just hang out by the kennel making small talk    # Q WHAT EXTINCT SPECIES WOULD YOU BRING BACK? # 1. The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="807">
<answer instance="807" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Now we shall have to eat rabbit pie and cold beef with fresh tomatoes, red onion and avocado slices and a side of rice with <head>p_c</head> peas. Note: Recaito is a cilantro cooking base that can be purchased at    be safe to say that his concern would be exactly that, not 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="676">
<answer instance="676" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
unimpeded from the streets, the media, and popular culture generally armistice now swept the ranks with the same ex citement brought on by the dead <head>p_c</head> Thoughts of home were very close today. Birch chatted on about the mudhole    . You may not even need another gun. In the years I 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="950">
<answer instance="950" senseid="car"/>
<context>
took an approach that we would never put him in a situation 's glad to see him in the race. " I'd vote for my <head>p_c</head> before I'd vote for Renee Ellmers, " he cracks. # The next    There weren't too many places to go to and the family had just 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1265">
<answer instance="1265" senseid="car"/>
<context>
education for children, health and retirement security and family vacations. # " moves come straight out of The Oprah Winfrey Show. (" You get a <head>p_c</head> And you get a car! Everybody gets a car! ") #    than a glance in this land of dark. And on both sides of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="160">
<answer instance="160" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
dishes, arroz con gandulas - rice with pigeon peas - and blood sausages known as morcilla. Come the weekend, salsa and make do with white <head>p_c</head> feathers that I could collect from behind my uncle's coop. Only once did I find a tail-feather from a golden pheasant. I    in various locations 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="180">
<answer instance="180" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Forge, a few miles from her birth site. Many people who are raised wrote. People had driven the dodo, the Carolina parakeet, and the passenger <head>p_c</head> to extinction, " but all we can hope to do with the sea-going forms    . # I don't look forward to returning to the bonfire 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="336">
<answer instance="336" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
pigeon infection was deep. And never cured. In recent years, as I came so unfair! " she whined. # " No, unfair is being a <head>p_c</head> in Newark, New Jersey with only one leg. What happened to you is   picks them up. DONNIE'S POV Photos of Lefty's rooftop. As the PIGEON 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="993">
<answer instance="993" senseid="car"/>
<context>
But experts say we need to be clear and upfront if our kids . " I can't eat it either. " # They're in the <head>p_c</head> now. He furtively turns on the Game Boy. He knows enough not to    , his fist dug into his cheek. In one hand he clutches 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1030">
<answer instance="1030" senseid="car"/>
<context>
he smiled, thinking of her and remembering the night they had met. the fog-shrouded highway, the slowed circuits of his brain, only she saw the <head>p_c</head> Karl its echo. She grips his arm protectively. " There's really  . The decoy team leaves the hotel, entering a waiting Mercedes sedan. The car 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="255">
<answer instance="255" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
during the Allies' Normandy invasion in World War II. # Or for trying sperm to inseminate band-tailed pigeons, creating hybrids (half band-tailed pigeon, half passenger <head>p_c</head> Artificial insemination is used extensively in modern poultry, with a high rate    hear, " Walter said. # " I shouldn't? " # " Pigeon, you 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="996">
<answer instance="996" senseid="car"/>
<context>
which he won't sleep. The goggles must have fallen off the bed of the car were scattered everywhere, " says onlooker Jenna Gulley. " The <head>p_c</head> was obliterated, burned beyond recognition. " Says Townsend: " The whole thing    be found. She searched for days before learning that the floodwaters had carried 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="742">
<answer instance="742" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the most efficient predicted route, but potentially the most difficult. Stem . She lay on her bed and looked through the skylight, listening to a <head>p_c</head> hurl itself against the wall, sirens approaching and receding. She had never slept    hawks. # For some years I was absorbed by hawks. But my 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="417">
<answer instance="417" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
" Its bios is cheap when you get " em by the thousand A whole lot of homing birds, hmm? " he asked. He saw <head>p_c</head> shit raining from the sky. " That's very interesting. Actually, though    the Great Comeback page on Facebook. # " The ability to synthesize sequences of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1199">
<answer instance="1199" senseid="car"/>
<context>
also should have a guaranteed hotel reservation so you can arrive late ( lot of miles. (Footage-of-McCanns) VAN-SANT: (Voiceover) Once their transportation, the McCanns rental <head>p_c</head> has reportedly become a key part of the case against them. Numerous press accounts    Waltrip, 9.6. Before 2002 Gordon won once every five times he 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="790">
<answer instance="790" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
con artists pretend to find a stash of money in an envelope have premarital sex, smoke publicly, and walk with toes out -- rather than <head>p_c</head> toed as in the feminine posture of kimono clad women displaying chastity -- Japanese men    terms with that emotion? -- he hands me, without smiling, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="847">
<answer instance="847" senseid="car"/>
<context>
of the car thing, " he says. He's selling the Ferrari 355. There is ? ! UNIDENTIFIED-MALE: He just wants revenge, he s had his <head>p_c</head> broken into, he wants someone to go down. ! UNIDENTIFIED-MALE:  " Crown backed down then and, without another word, stormed off to his car. Cade 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="880">
<answer instance="880" senseid="car"/>
<context>
Alan did on their cars, or perhaps not. More likely they sold their car when it didn't do exactly what the driver wanted. Or the <head>p_c</head> dealers    before April 16, 1995, when his former Army buddy called to say his car had broken down and he needed a ride from Oklahoma 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="95">
<answer instance="95" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
wood- pigeon (Columba palumbus). Charismatic species for the United Kingdom, such as the servant, Hannah, was frying johnnycakes on a pan over a fire, popping <head>p_c</head> peas into her mouth. Everything smelled of fried fish, blistered peppers, and    the Fare to Fowl dinners, Canales and his staff turned out platters of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="301">
<answer instance="301" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Design Challenge solution at the opening ceremony of Space Day result in the biggest decimation of a natural population since the extinction of the passenger <head>p_c</head> But while the passenger pigeon was only one avian species out of 10,000,  They'd eaten peanut-butter-and-honey sandwiches and shared a Yoo-hoo. There'd been a dead 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1111">
<answer instance="1111" senseid="car"/>
<context>
factor in all of these deaths was not drinking or reckless up because I knew that Joanne and the two children were coming, in the <head>p_c</head> coming to the embassy for a medical examination for the children. School was starting    The hard floor wasn't so bad-it was definitely better than doing 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1190">
<answer instance="1190" senseid="car"/>
<context>
new Chevy Vega, whose presence suddenly seemed to him much more revolver at Luke's head as he and Rosita reluctantly left the familiarity of the <head>p_c</head> He gave the weapon a quick twirl. " I watched reruns of The    comes to buying or selling cars. If you have the time, sell 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="62">
<answer instance="62" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
the air. A second beore Gorbachev pulls the trigger, I see embryos before scientists can access the nucleus. So U.S. researchers plan to inject band-tailed <head>p_c</head> embryos with primordial germ cells, edited to be as passenger like as possible.  of weary clapboard buildings. A bronze statue of a Union soldier, covered 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="570">
<answer instance="570" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
and squared shoulders. She looks at once robotically durable and mysteriously frail. taunts from above, something seemed to burst loose in his chest, like a <head>p_c</head> fluttering free from a cage. Alis rope was still taut in the water next    bass into an easy-to-digest primer. To slow things down for the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="391">
<answer instance="391" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Ace is furious. ACE You idiot! Do you know what you the gamekeeper of the mansion-house property, a limber-legged fellow who could pick off a <head>p_c</head> hawk or good piece of gossip at a hundred yards. The gamekeeper told Claude    , it is simultaneously dropping in price. " # Ben J. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="369">
<answer instance="369" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
shrimps with chicken and peas, chicken and scallops with ginger to this drill is a popper-style target with an attachment that will launch a clay <head>p_c</head> when it falls. I used the smaller US Popper from MGM targets (mgmtargets    for the after-party, Future Pigeon's second album, The Echodelic Sounds of Future 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="367">
<answer instance="367" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
he's part of the con. " # The shill in Mr. Molina on the futon to reshelve the mag &; I sniff the feather (ooh; <head>p_c</head> blood), tickling my nose? So that I sneeze &; topple to the    which I had discovered I particularly liked. There were also jelled duck eggs, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="642">
<answer instance="642" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
dog that had eaten a Pound Puppy, among others) and shabby leather overcoat sitting on the other side of me leaned over and indicating the <head>p_c</head> said, " White death. " I nodded and grinned. I had the    in October. But if all goes as planned, the falcon soon notices the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="245">
<answer instance="245" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
tourism chief for the Smoky Mountain Visitors Bureau there's even a phrase for it: kabootarbaazi. The literal translation is " pigeon hunting, " with the <head>p_c</head> viewed as a weak and gullible person. Recruiters  the dregs of capitalist societies, " Mandelstam observed, smiling blandly at the stool pigeon over the heads 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="152">
<answer instance="152" senseid="pigeon"/>
<context>
Springfest continues through June 10, Dollywood's KidsFest is June 15-Aug. 5. 1-800-365-5996 stasis bed recorded Flanagan's death at eight minutes to five this evening. The <head>p_c</head> bio died eleven seconds later. Unless Flanagan managed to bust up his own     , clapper rail, Caribbean coot, least tern, piping plover, and white-crowned pigeon. 
</context>
</instance>
