<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<corpus lang='english'>

<lexelt item="XYZ">

<instance id="848">
<answer instance="848" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
bicycle traffic (predominantly students at the University of Minnesota). Likewise, in Toronto, the Prince Edward Viaduct has five lanes of motor traffic, bicycle lanes, and <head>XYZ</head> on its upper deck; and a pair of tracks for the Bloor–Danforth subway line on its lower deck. The western span of the San Francisco–Oakland 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1136">
<answer instance="1136" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
road crosses Wyandotte Street (which roughly parallels the Detroit River). Windsor's Department of Parks and Recreation maintains of green space, 180 parks, of trails, of <head>XYZ</head> 60 parking lots, vacant lands, natural areas and forest cover within the city of Windsor. The largest park is Mic Mac Park, which can accommodate 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1169">
<answer instance="1169" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
their coats bulging like balloons. All up and down the Calle Grande they went, sowing the sharp burrs carefully in the sand, along the narrow <head>XYZ</head> in every foot of grass between the silent houses. And then they took the side streets and by-ways, missing none. No place where the foot 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="519">
<answer instance="519" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
pig iron was referred to as "hot metal". The hot metal was then poured into a steelmaking vessel to produce steel, typically an electric arc <head>XYZ</head> induction furnace or basic oxygen furnace, where the excess carbon is burned off and the alloy composition controlled. Earlier processes for this included the finery 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="252">
<answer instance="252" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
Besides material characterization, the material scientist/engineer also deals with the extraction of materials and their conversion into useful forms. Thus ingot casting, foundry techniques, blast <head>XYZ</head> extraction, and electrolytic extraction are all part of the required knowledge of a materials engineer. Often the presence, absence or variation of minute quantities of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="908">
<answer instance="908" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
ed path, trail or footpath that is not next to a road, for example, a path through a park. The term <head>XYZ</head> is usually preferred in North America, along with many other countries worldwide that are not members of the Commonwealth of Nations. The term pavement is 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1118">
<answer instance="1118" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
of cob webs and spiders, and are very important for that reason. Hard brooms are made for the harder job of actually sweeping dirt off <head>XYZ</head> The word "broom" derives from the name of certain thorny shrubs ("Genista" and others) used for sweeping. The name of the shrubs began to be 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="277">
<answer instance="277" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
condensation are a current topic of architecture. High humidity can often have a negative effect on the capacity of chemical plants and refineries that use <head>XYZ</head> as part of the process (e.g. steam reforming, wet sulfuric acid process). The humidity will reduce the oxygen concentration, and the flue gas fans have 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="980">
<answer instance="980" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
working anonymously, had either been killed or disappeared. He sporadically sent out dispatches and stories; he wrote about the mood in Havana, the crowded city <head>XYZ</head> and other topics, but he was soon desperate for money again. Taylor, left alone in England, was also penniless. She became frantic with worry over 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1171">
<answer instance="1171" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
side streets. It was all done in so quiet and gentlemanly a manner that not one of the grown-up spectators who had gathered on the <head>XYZ</head> thought of interfering. Big Hans, however, who had intended to see something of the city before starting for the West, was so discouraged at the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="478">
<answer instance="478" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
Gt). One estimate for resources is 18,000 Gt. When coal is used for electricity generation, it is usually pulverized and then combusted (burned) in a <head>XYZ</head> with a boiler. The furnace heat converts boiler water to steam, which is then used to spin turbines which turn generators and create electricity. The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="777">
<answer instance="777" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
in an abrupt, trembling voice. # " There isn't anything we can do, " the receptionist said. " They can't come onto the property. The <head>XYZ</head>    's free, you know. " Her voice was cool. # " I thought there were escorts. " # " The volunteers usually come Tuesdays, that's 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1059">
<answer instance="1059" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
Fame, Volume One, 1929–1964" anthology in 1970. The story is set in the near future, when "roadtowns" (wide rapidly moving passenger platforms similar to moving <head>XYZ</head> but reaching speeds of 100 mph) have replaced highways and railways as the dominant transportation method in the United States. Heinlein's themes are technological change 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="38">
<answer instance="38" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnace"/>
<context>
This point is east-southeast of Mount Whitney, the highest point in the contiguous United States with an elevation of 14,505 feet (4,421 m). Death Valley's <head>XYZ</head> Creek holds the record for the highest reliably recorded air temperature in the world, 134 °F (56.7 °C) on July 10, 1913. This has been contested by 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="665">
<answer instance="665" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
oil-free and nonacnegenic, sells for $ 16.50 at department-store cosmetics counters. 56905 # SITGES, Spain - The road, followed far enough, slopes onto a cobblestone <head>XYZ</head>    , then a sandy beach replete with volleyball players and finally a breathtakingly expanse of Mediterranean blue. From where we stood, though, outside a tidy 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1120">
<answer instance="1120" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
for walking and bicycling connect to Montpelier: the Cross Vermont Trail and the Central Vermont Regional Path. Montpelier's downtown is relatively compact and pedestrian-friendly, with <head>XYZ</head> and crosswalks throughout the downtown area. The Vermont Mountaineers of the New England Collegiate Baseball League play at the Montpelier Recreation Field. The city has 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="954">
<answer instance="954" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
urs of 9:00 p.m. and 6:30 a.m. The compromise plan permits the homeless to sleep on the <head>XYZ</head> provided they are not "within 10 feet of any business or residential entrance" and only between these hours. One of the motivations for the compromise 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="513">
<answer instance="513" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
by an evaporator coil for air conditioning. The air supply is normally filtered through air cleaners to remove dust and pollen particles. The use of <head>XYZ</head> space heaters, and boilers as a method of indoor heating could result in incomplete combustion and the emission of carbon monoxide, nitrogen oxides, formaldehyde, volatile 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1163">
<answer instance="1163" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
 The lower floor communicated by two doorways with the narrow, rock-paved <head>XYZ</head> The _pulperia_--or drinking shop--of the proprietress, Madama Timotea Ortiz, occupied the ground floor. On the bottles of brandy, _anisada_, Scotch "smoke" and inexpensive wines behind 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="844">
<answer instance="844" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
with the Chicago Roller Skate Company to produce sets of skate wheels, which they attached to square wooden boards. Accordingly, skateboarding was originally denoted " <head>XYZ</head> surfing" and early skaters emulated surfing style and maneuvers, and performed barefoot. By the 1960s a small number of surfing manufacturers in Southern California such 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="537">
<answer instance="537" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
. You could love great art but have no desire to live in a museum . He noticed a damaged sprinkler head where lawn met <head>XYZ</head>   . He   got   his   tools   from   the   truck   and   knelt   on   the   grass   ,   taking   a   break   from   the   impatiens   . His   cell   phone   rang   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="171">
<answer instance="171" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
China. However the cementation process was not abandoned and as late as the early 19th century there are descriptions of solid-state cementation in a domed <head>XYZ</head> at around 900–950 °C and lasting up to 10 hours. The European brass industry continued to flourish into the post medieval period buoyed by innovations such 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="895">
<answer instance="895" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
After finishing a recording for the armed services, Davis took a break outside the club. As he was escorting an attractive blonde woman across the <head>XYZ</head> to a taxi, Davis was told by a patrolman to "move on." Davis explained that he worked at the nightclub and refused to move. The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="395">
<answer instance="395" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnace"/>
<context>
terrified of the whites and their wheeled wagons and huge buffalo, none of which the Shoshone had ever seen before when they came wandering down <head>XYZ</head> Creek Wash in December 1849. In 1940, when Bah-vanda was around 100 years old, JC Boyles, a Panamint Shoshone who had become educated, came back 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="913">
<answer instance="913" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
here cyclists are also able to use the same section of path as pedestrians. There is evidence that <head>XYZ</head> were built in ancient times. It was claimed that the Greek city of Corinth was paved by the 4th-century, and the Romans were particularly prolific 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1050">
<answer instance="1050" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
falls in love with another girl. Joan Blondell tells her roommate, who tries to steal Cagney away from her, that as long as there are <head>XYZ</head> the roommate will have a job. In the Shanghai Lil number, it is clear that Lil and all the other girls are prostitutes working the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="636">
<answer instance="636" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
And tell yourself you can stop at that point if you want. Yes, you might quit in 10 minutes. But once you're out on the <head>XYZ</head>    , you'll probably keep walking. NEXT TIME Buddy up " If you have an exercise partner, it's easier to stay committed, " says Dr. Wyatt. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="841">
<answer instance="841" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
photographing the club's remarkably nondescript entrance -- and Scot Pressley's one-man march. # Pressley didn't need city permission to walk back and forth on the <head>XYZ</head>    across from the club Monday, holding a sloppy hand-made sign that is more of a stream-of-consciousness rant than a focused protest message. # " Voice 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="405">
<answer instance="405" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
Rosas to make net sinkers, plumb bobs, and small figurines. Copper was the most important metal for toolmaking in ancient Egypt and was smelted in <head>XYZ</head> from malachite ore mined in the Sinai. Workers collected gold by washing the nuggets out of sediment in alluvial deposits, or by the more labor-intensive 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="82">
<answer instance="82" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
17th century was called pale ale. In 1709 Abraham Darby I established a coke-fired blast furnace to produce cast iron. Coke's superior crushing strength allowed blast <head>XYZ</head> to become taller and larger. The ensuing availability of inexpensive iron was one of the factors leading to the Industrial Revolution. Before this time, iron-making 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1016">
<answer instance="1016" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
Frog Jubilee, featuring a frog-jumping contest, to celebrate the association with Twain's story. Each year's winner is commemorated with a brass plaque mounted in the <head>XYZ</head> of downtown Historic Angels Camp and this feature is known as the Frog Hop of Fame. The California red-legged frog, feared extinct in the county 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="775">
<answer instance="775" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
iii New York actively target bladers. They hate our guts. Often, in the early days of learning the sport, I was forced up onto the <head>XYZ</head>    to save my life, which made me a pedestrian. After I'd done some improving, learning how to anticipate the buses before they came after me, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="729">
<answer instance="729" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
had relocated to Texas. She missed her terribly. # The sun was just peeking over the barren hills to the east as she left the <head>XYZ</head>    and headed into the wooded trail that looped behind the houses. Within moments, pale winter sunlight flickered, illuminating the bare trees and the snow-splotched fields 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="995">
<answer instance="995" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
filmed at the American Embassy at 2 Avenue Gabriel, and the Canadian Embassy at 35 Avenue Montaigne. The scene where Luc throws money on the <head>XYZ</head> was filmed at the corner of rue Paul Albert and rue Feutrier in Montmartre. Driving scenes in Paris were filmed in front of the Louvre 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="976">
<answer instance="976" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
Frank (age 33) were well attended. About 300 people joined in the procession to Boot Hill and as many as two thousand watched from the <head>XYZ</head> Both McLaurys were buried in the same grave, and Billy Clanton was buried nearby. The story was widely printed in newspapers across the United States. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="575">
<answer instance="575" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
Takhar , near the border with Tajikistan . Mahathir clamps down on Islamic groups 19-10-2001 Sahimah sells Islamic books , tapes and headscarves from her <head>XYZ</head>   kiosk   here   . But   pride   of   place   is   reserved   for   a   new   arrival   :   T-shirts   emblazoned   with   Osama   bin   Laden   's   face   and   the   phrase   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="164">
<answer instance="164" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
natural flake graphite can be made from steelmaking kish. Kish is a large-volume near-molten waste skimmed from the molten iron feed to a basic oxygen <head>XYZ</head> and consists of a mix of graphite (precipitated out of the supersaturated iron), l
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="306">
<answer instance="306" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
s called the Hall-Heroult process. Héroult's second most important contribution is the first commercially successful electric arc furnace (EAF) for steel in 1900. The Héroult <head>XYZ</head> gradually replaced the giant smelters for the production of a variety of steels. In 1905, Paul Héroult was invited to the United States as a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="209">
<answer instance="209" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
repeated his demand once, but Muhammad once again refused. Then, he (the Bedouin) left Medina. Muhammad said, "Madinah is like a pair of bellows ( <head>XYZ</head> it expels its impurities and brightens and clear its good." In this narration, there was no evidence demonstrating that Muhammad ordered the execution of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="8">
<answer instance="8" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
fire with sand or magnesium foundry flux to remove its air source. Magnesium compounds, primarily magnesium oxide (MgO), are used as a refractory material in <head>XYZ</head> linings for producing iron, steel, nonferrous metals, glass, and cement. Magnesium oxide and other magnesium compounds are also used in the agricultural, chemical, and construction 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="226">
<answer instance="226" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
H.F. Bruner & Sons. From about 1854 to 1900, an industrial complex existed in and around Columbia, Marietta and Wrightsville that included 11 anthracite iron <head>XYZ</head> and related structures, as well as canal and railroad facilities servicing them. By 1887, that number had grown to 13 blast furnaces, all operating within 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="29">
<answer instance="29" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
the Seminole Group Colombia CI, SAS. Tin is produced by carbothermic reduction of the oxide ore with carbon or coke. Both reverberatory furnace and electric <head>XYZ</head> can be used. The ten largest companies produced most of the world's tin in 2007. It is not clear which of these companies include tin 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="520">
<answer instance="520" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
was referred to as "hot metal". The hot metal was then poured into a steelmaking vessel to produce steel, typically an electric arc furnace, induction <head>XYZ</head> or basic oxygen furnace, where the excess carbon is burned off and the alloy composition controlled. Earlier processes for this included the finery forge, the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="444">
<answer instance="444" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
In 1828, he became a partner with James Beaumont Neilson in a firm to exploit the latter's patent for the hot blast blowing of blast <head>XYZ</head> which saved considerably on their fuel consumption. Macintosh married, in 1790, Mary Fisher, daughter of Alexander Fisher a merchant of Glasgow. They had one son, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1026">
<answer instance="1026" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
irresistible cornucopia of escapist ingredients." On 24 March 1941, Carmen Miranda became one of the first Latinas to leave her hand and footprints in the <head>XYZ</head> of Grauman's Chinese Theater. His next film, "Week-End in Havana" was directed by Walter Lang with William LeBaron as producer. The cast included Alice Faye, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="384">
<answer instance="384" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
roasting iron pyrite in converting sulphide to oxide in sulfur used in gunpowder compositions— illustrating how ore was piled up with coal briquettes in an earthen <head>XYZ</head> with a still-head that sent over sulfur as vapor that would solidify and crystallize —and the use of gunpowder weapons such as a naval mine ignited 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="229">
<answer instance="229" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
coal, anthracite-fired <head>XYZ</head> using locally available iron ores were built throughout eastern Pennsylvania, helping to make the state a leader in iron production in the latter half of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="12">
<answer instance="12" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
material for the manufacture of containers for foodstuffs and most chemicals. Following the glass batch preparation and mixing, the raw materials are transported to the <head>XYZ</head> Soda-lime glass for mass production is melted in gas fired units. Smaller scale furnaces for specialty glasses include electric melters, pot furnaces, and day tanks. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="411">
<answer instance="411" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
the waste, and de-nitrate the fission products to assist the stability of the glass produced. The 'calcine' generated is fed continuously into an induction heated <head>XYZ</head> with fragmented glass. The resulting glass is a new substance in which the waste products are bonded into the glass matrix when it solidifies. As 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="112">
<answer instance="112" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
low. The binding of oxygen is affected by molecules such as carbon monoxide (CO) (for example, from tobacco smoking, car exhaust, and incomplete combustion in <head>XYZ</head> CO competes with oxygen at the heme binding site. Hemoglobin binding affinity for CO is 250 times greater than its affinity for oxygen, meaning that 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="631">
<answer instance="631" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
the west slope . Our first birds of the trip , seen from our taxi , were a pair of Eared Doves foraging on the <head>XYZ</head>   . We   arrived   in   Mindo   around   10:30   a.m.   and   on   the   short   stroll   to   Bird-watcher   's   House   we   picked   up   our   first   4   species   ,   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1164">
<answer instance="1164" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
 As the exceptional yachtsman was making his way down the precarious <head>XYZ</head> of the Street of the Holy Sepulchre, the solitary permanent guest of that decaying hotel sat at its door, enjoying the breeze from the sea.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="585">
<answer instance="585" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
a playful aesthetic of focused , corporate modernization ( Berman , 1982 , 16 ) . Its legendary congestion prompted a battle over street and <head>XYZ</head>   that   spoke   to   ideas   of   urbanism   that   transcended   the   significance   of   individual   buildings   constructed   along   The   Great   White   Way   .
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="953">
<answer instance="953" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
Enforcement of section 41.18(d) 24 hours a day against persons who have nowhere else to sit, lie, or sleep, other than on public streets and <head>XYZ</head> is breaking these amendments. The Court said that the anti-camping ordinance is "one of the most restrictive municipal laws regulating public spaces in the United 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="831">
<answer instance="831" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
own test. I jumped up and down on the panel. It felt like an ordinary road. An approaching transit-mix truck sent me scurrying to the <head>XYZ</head>    . Braking a few feet from where I was standing, the truck's rear wheels pivoted on the glass panel as it turned into a driveway. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="297">
<answer instance="297" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
an array of plane mirrors to gather sunlight, reflecting it onto a larger curved mirror. The ancient Greek / Latin term "heliocaminus" literally means "solar <head>XYZ</head> and refers to a glass-enclosed sunroom intentionally designed to become hotter than the outside air temperature. During the Second Punic War (218 - 202 BC), 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="531">
<answer instance="531" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
from his first trip by plane . Revell finds this violent man , so capable within his circumscribed life , in tears on a moving <head>XYZ</head>   ,   unable   to   read   the   monitors   and   in   desperate   need   of   rescue   . Suddenly   ,   the   young   poet   can   "   think   of   poetry   not   as   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="744">
<answer instance="744" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
as he gave himself to the opening scene, a montage of Left Bank vignettes. The camera zoomed in on a beautiful young woman at a <head>XYZ</head>    cafe. She lifted an infant from a sack on her back, unbuttoned her blouse and began to nurse what must have been a symbolic papoose 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="495">
<answer instance="495" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
inspection of printed copies well into the 1940s show "dord" still present). The non-word "dord" was excised, and the definition of the adjacent entry "Doré <head>XYZ</head> was expanded from "A furnace for refining dore bullion" to "a furnace in which dore bullion is refined" to close up the space. Gove wrote 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="650">
<answer instance="650" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
you first saw or heard one of the forbidden words? I'll never forget the first time I did. It was written in chalk on a <head>XYZ</head>    about two blocks from where we lived. For a moment, my entire world whirled. Someone had actually written that word for all the world to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="615">
<answer instance="615" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
" In his neighborhood there was a sidewalk with perfectly regular slabs all the same size . He noticed that when he walked along this <head>XYZ</head>   he   always   got   the   following   repeating   pattern   where   "   *   "   stands   for   "   Boing   ! "   121231231212312312*121231231212312312*121231231212312312*121231....et   c.   How   far   apart   ,   in   inches   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="238">
<answer instance="238" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
resulting metal are still significant; these are mostly contaminants of arsenic, antimony, bismuth, zinc, copper, silver, and gold. The melt is treated in a reverberatory <head>XYZ</head> with air, steam, and sulfur, which oxidizes the contaminants except silver, gold, and bismuth. The oxidized contaminants are removed by drossing, where they float to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="981">
<answer instance="981" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
surfaced. There were, however, 115 publicly maintained street crossings at intersections to keep pedestrians from having to wade through a sea of mud between wooden <head>XYZ</head> As an experiment, Washington Street was once paved with wooden blocks. This proved to be the source of much local amusement when they buckled and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="808">
<answer instance="808" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
the night and disturb your neighbors. Similarly, you can maybe take a picture of naked people. It doesn't mean you can go to a public <head>XYZ</head>    in a residential community and do it any time of day or night. So we have to have some sort of rules here. And I 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="672">
<answer instance="672" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
we saw the bus pulling away as we approached. We ran after it, but my heel got stuck in one of the grooves on the <head>XYZ</head>    , and down I went. As I fell, a strap on my dress ripped, and I exposed my boob to everyone. " -- Alex, 22 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="711">
<answer instance="711" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
- DAY Looking over his shoulder as he runs down the street, Sal slows as he realizes he's not been pursued. The vendors on the <head>XYZ</head>    bargain vigorously in Yiddish, Italian, and English. Sal stops as an ITALIAN LABORER, standing in front of a roulette wheel, shouts in triumph. The slick-haired 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="776">
<answer instance="776" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
learning how to anticipate the buses before they came after me, I was definitely a car, using any lane I chose and staying off the <head>XYZ</head> most of the time. Still, I never had a parking problem, which gave me a touch of the pecks trian. I have now passed beyond 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="643">
<answer instance="643" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
crowded in the main dining room. " 228 BY THE TIME MY brother and I arrived at Donabedian's Market, our mother was waiting on the <head>XYZ</head>    outside the shop, having commandeered the grocer's wooden handcart, which was loaded with gunnysacks of bulgur, net bags of onions, liter tins of olive oil, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1135">
<answer instance="1135" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
to include a three-level structure with 44 airline gates and similar amenities to Concourse B. The concourse plan includes a dedicated mezzanine corridor with moving <head>XYZ</head> to serve international passengers. The design and construction of the new C/D concourse has not been scheduled. When built, it is planned that both terminals 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="569">
<answer instance="569" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
doubles , twists . You notice how nimbly the body itself has learned to assess the relation between the board , pedestrians , and immediate <head>XYZ</head>   . Emblem   . Emblem   of   fashion   . Wearing   dirty   white   in   dishevelment   as   delicate   as   the   falling   draperies   on   a   dandyish   Renaissance   saint   . Chain   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="689">
<answer instance="689" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
the sidewalk, listening and staring in shock. # MOTHER # Mornin', Mayor. Jack smiles, a bit embarrassed. Jack notices a group of HUNTERS on the <head>XYZ</head>    , looking and pointing at something up in the sky. He looks up to see a small meteor plummeting toward earth. EXT. HIGH SCHOOL -- 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1007">
<answer instance="1007" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
as local industries declined. The lumber industry eventually disappeared as surrounding woodlands became depleted. As Chestnut Hill iron ores became scarce as well, the iron <head>XYZ</head> shut down. Eventually, the steel rolling mills also ceased operation. In 1906, the Pennsylvania Railroad opened a new facility in Enola, across the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="546">
<answer instance="546" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
Vegas Review-Journal had carried daily updates on the unrest in Seattle . USA Today sported a photo of bodies under a large tarpaulin on the <head>XYZ</head>   outside   the   Z   Club   ,   and   it   was   because   of   those   bodies   that   last   Friday   and   Saturday   night   African-   American   youth   rioted   in   Seattle   in   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="857">
<answer instance="857" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
St. Leonard and Solomons was completed in 1988. In 2009, a portion of Route 2-4 in Prince Frederick was expanded to 3 lines, along with <head>XYZ</head> added. Other major roadways in Calvert County include: The Census Bureau recognizes the following census-designated places in the county: Dunkirk, Huntingtown, Lusby, Owings, Prince Frederick, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="506">
<answer instance="506" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
pyroelectric materials are also piezoelectric. These materials can be used to inter convert between thermal, mechanical, or electrical energy; for instance, after synthesis in a <head>XYZ</head> a pyroelectric crystal allowed to cool under no applied stress generally builds up a static charge of thousands of volts. Such materials are used in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="280">
<answer instance="280" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
the RAF to attack targets in the Ruhr, including oil plants and other civilian industrial targets which aided the German war effort, such as blast <head>XYZ</head> that at night were self-illuminating. After the Butt Report (released in September 1941) proved the inadequacy of RAF Bomber Command training methods and equipment, the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="20">
<answer instance="20" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
the need for collective action to overcome environmental challenges such as irrigation, are all thought to have played a role. Continuing improvements led to the <head>XYZ</head> and bellows and provided the ability to smelt and forge native metals (naturally occurring in relatively pure form). Gold, copper, silver, and lead, were such 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1158">
<answer instance="1158" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
 He raised his stick to the driver, in event of him being free--and stepped out from the <head>XYZ</head>
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="644">
<answer instance="644" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
Last week, as two men gathered scrap metal from the burned house and loaded it into a pickup, next-door neighbor Linda Phillips stood on the <head>XYZ</head>    and applauded this hint of progress. # " You think you live in a nice neighborhood, and you have to tell people,' I live next 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="800">
<answer instance="800" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
steps was locked so the dogs wouldn't barge out through it. # Oh, the hell with it. Back in Manhattan, half the pedestrians on the <head>XYZ</head>    were pushier than this guy. Scraper in hand, she advanced on him. # His hands went up in a conciliatory gesture. " Okay, I get 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="445">
<answer instance="445" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
ignition properties change as the cylinder empties. For these reasons, the liquid is often withdrawn using a dip tube. Propane is used as fuel in <head>XYZ</head> for heat, in cooking, as an energy source for water heaters, laundry dryers, barbecues, portable stoves, and motor vehicles. Commercially available "propane" fuel, or LPG, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="41">
<answer instance="41" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnace"/>
<context>
super-heated air blow through the valley creating extremely high temperatures. The hottest air temperature ever recorded in Death Valley was on July 10, 1913, at <head>XYZ</head> Creek, which is the hottest atmospheric temperature ever recorded on earth. During the heat wave that peaked with that record, five consecutive days reached or 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="403">
<answer instance="403" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
He purchased a cornet from a fellow band member and spent every free minute practicing it. He worked on a "shovel brigade" at the McNabb <head>XYZ</head> and described the music made by the workers as they beat shovels, altering the tone while thrusting and withdrawing the metal part against the iron 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="867">
<answer instance="867" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
sense their physical environment to grow, including the sensing of light, and physical barriers. Over time, roots can crack foundations, snap water lines, and lift <head>XYZ</head> The correct environment of air, mineral nutrients and water directs plant roots to grow in any direction to meet the plant's needs. Roots will shy 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1034">
<answer instance="1034" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
city organizations, began revitalization and preservation efforts in its historic downtown area. The Downtown Yakima Futures Initiative was created to make strategic public investments in <head>XYZ</head> lighting and landscaping to encourage further development. As a result, local businesses featuring regional produce, wines, and beers, among other products, have returned to the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="125">
<answer instance="125" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
a completely different, cheaper material that mimics the standard type over a reduced temperature range. Thermocouples are often used at high temperatures and in reactive <head>XYZ</head> atmospheres. In this case, the practical lifetime is limited by thermocouple aging. The thermoelectric coefficients of the wires in a thermocouple that is used to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="539">
<answer instance="539" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
the backyards and mini - satellite dishes on every roof , and each driveway was a smooth carpet of blacktop and there was n't a <head>XYZ</head>   crack   to   trip   over   because   there   were   no   sidewalks   ,   and   each   house   had   a   garage   that   was   so   oversized   it   could   have   been   its   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="660">
<answer instance="660" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
out, and shoves it in his pocket. Then he decides to rip some more pages out. He steps from the phone-booth and sits on the <head>XYZ</head>    , takes off his shoes. He folds the pages, stuffs them into his shoes to plug the holes, then puts his shoes back on. Now 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1028">
<answer instance="1028" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
private vehicles. In 2006, the Segway scooter was approved for use on sidewalks and other pedestrian designated locations, as well as roads that have no <head>XYZ</head> obstructed sidewalks or sidewalks lacking curb cuts. The user must be over 16 years old. No license is required. The maximum allowed speed is , 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="813">
<answer instance="813" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
swarming with police cars, dozens of them parked on block after block, as officers conducted their investigation and neighbors came out and stood on the <head>XYZ</head>    , watching. # On nearby 73rd Avenue, a man who declined to give his name said he was working in his backyard when he heard 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="194">
<answer instance="194" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnace"/>
<context>
entitled "Prima Voce: The Spirit of Christmas Past". A Brunswick/American Decca LP entitled "Readings from the Bible" featured Laughton reading Garden of Eden, The Fiery <head>XYZ</head> Noah's Ark, and David and Goliath. It was released in 1958. Laughton had previously included several Bible readings when he played the title role in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="510">
<answer instance="510" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
relatively little sediment comes down the Rhine from Lake Constance. The north side of the falls is a millsite. In the 17th century, a blast <head>XYZ</head> for smelting iron ore found in the limestone was built. It was in operation until the first half of the 19th century. In 1887 the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="574">
<answer instance="574" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
to bed in my undergarments . As I walk with crutches or wheel down the street , I spot a $ 10 bill on the <head>XYZ</head>   . I   am   too   tired   to   pick   it   up   . I   spend   time   teaching   the   cat   how   to   use   a   can   opener   so   it   can   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="948">
<answer instance="948" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
quantities of Portland cement were first imported to the United States in the 1880s, its principal use was in the construction of sidewalks. Today, most <head>XYZ</head> ribbons are constructed with cross-lying strain-relief grooves placed or sawn at regular intervals typically apart. This partitioning, an improvement over the continuous slab, was patented 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="324">
<answer instance="324" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
coke. The process also contains a flux such as limestone, which is used to remove silicaceous minerals in the ore, which would otherwise clog the <head>XYZ</head> The coke and limestone are fed into the top of the furnace, while a massive blast of air heated to 900 °C, about 4 tons per 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="630">
<answer instance="630" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
others unspecified ) and the event was cancelled. { pull quote } the presumption was that if you were in the street or on the <head>XYZ</head>   in   the   downtown   area   of   miami   ,   you   were   an   activist   ,   and   therefore   a   criminal.   activists   ,   once   defined   as   criminals   ,   were   then   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="482">
<answer instance="482" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
function applied to the mould before casting. Sea coal can be mixed with the clay lining (the "bod") used for the bottom of a cupola <head>XYZ</head> When heated, the coal decomposes and the bod becomes slightly friable, easing the process of breaking open holes for tapping the molten metal. Coal is 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1160">
<answer instance="1160" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
 They found a carryall and a span of horses standing near the <head>XYZ</head> A lady and a little girl were in the carryall.  Two gentlemen were examining one of the wheels, and several boys stood near looking on.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="977">
<answer instance="977" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
It was the most expensive Unimog, with prices starting at DM150,000. Introduction of the very small model UX100. It is designed to slip speedily over <head>XYZ</head> and by park plants. It is sold off after a few years of production to Hako who specialize in vehicles of this kind and size. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1017">
<answer instance="1017" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
John's roundabout retains perimeter cycle lanes. The roundabout at the Brown Road/202 interchange adopts a U.S.-recommended design. On-street pavement markings direct cyclists to enter the <head>XYZ</head> at the end of the bike lane. Cyclists who choose to travel on the wide sidewalk, cross roundabout arms perpendicularly, well outside the circle. A 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="248">
<answer instance="248" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
Virtually the entire city (900,000 households and 5,900 companies) is centrally heated, using residual heat from electricity generation (3,000 MW) and gas- and oil-fired heating <head>XYZ</head> total heat capacity is 4,640 MW. The heat distribution piping network is long and comprises 14,000 substations and 10,000 heated buildings. Sofia concentrates a significant 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="131">
<answer instance="131" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
Even the sheath of a magnesium oxide insulating the thermocouple does not keep the hydrogen out. Type M (82%Ni/18%Mo–99.2%Ni/0.8%Co, by weight) are used in vacuum <head>XYZ</head> for the same reasons as with type C (described below). Upper temperature is limited to 1400 °C. It is less commonly used than other types. Type 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1095">
<answer instance="1095" senseid="sense0" org_word="Sidewalk"/>
<context>
consisted of re-recording of Ramones songs, a re-recorded solo song ("Fix Yourself Up", originally from "Zonked!"/"Ain't It Fun?"), cover-songs and an unreleased new solo-song (" <head>XYZ</head> Surfin'"). In the 21st century, Dee Dee teamed up with Paul Kostabi, leader of the hardcore punk band Youth Gone Mad and former guitarist for 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="894">
<answer instance="894" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
frequently seen as a nuisance by drivers, especially when their numbers multiply in the warmer months. Cycle paths can be found alongside the majority of <head>XYZ</head> and streets, although the newer and/or renovated ones are much easier to tell apart from pavements than older ones. The cycle paths usually involve a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="263">
<answer instance="263" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
such as those built in the region by Losh, Wilson and Bell who when they opened their Port Clarence works in 1853 had 5 operating <head>XYZ</head> in the region according to Marley the Geologist, who was commissioned to look for a deep seam of ironstone near Middlesbrough by Bolckow & Vaughan, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="439">
<answer instance="439" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
became widely available in the 1870s after the process was modified to produce more uniform quality. Bessemer steel was being displaced by the open hearth <head>XYZ</head> near the end of the 19th century. This Second Industrial Revolution gradually grew to include chemicals, mainly the chemical industries, petroleum (refining and distribution), and, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="814">
<answer instance="814" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
opening, LIFE Coalition members decided to escalate their activities. They hired what they called a " problem pregnancy counselor " to organize a volunteer " <head>XYZ</head> counseling program. "    Sidewalk    counselors walked quietly, usually in twos, back and forth in front of the clinic. They approached people entering the clinic, gave 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="346">
<answer instance="346" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
city limits). This is true in many other cities around the United States Bricks in the metallurgy and glass industries are often used for lining <head>XYZ</head> in particular refractory bricks such as silica, magnesia, chamotte and neutral (chromomagnesite) refractory bricks. This type of brick must have good thermal shock resistance, refractoriness 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="567">
<answer instance="567" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
the front door . It was dark outside , the streetlamps at the corner spreading orange light over the fallen leaves on the lawn and <head>XYZ</head>   . A   strong   breeze   rustled   those   still   left   on   the   trees   ,   sending   a   few   to   spiral   down   and   around   the   crossroads   where   the   two   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="807">
<answer instance="807" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
low-flow toilet fixtures makes sense and, in fact, ought to be expanded to other kinds of home fixtures. Here in New York, wasteful practices like <head>XYZ</head>    washing ought to be rethought. The use of gray water, which is water that comes out of your sewage treatment plant for industrial purposes, is 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="106">
<answer instance="106" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
ystem is 0. Thus, it implies that the total entropy change of the <head>XYZ</head> and sink is zero, for the process to be reversible and the efficiency of the engine to be maximum. This derivation is carried out in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="31">
<answer instance="31" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
high vacuum needed for the tubes. The high melting point and oxidation resistance lead to the use of the metal in the production of vacuum <head>XYZ</head> parts. Tantalum is extremely inert and is therefore formed into a variety of corrosion resistant parts, such as thermowells, valve bodies, and tantalum fasteners. Due 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="601">
<answer instance="601" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
celebration in some of the typical districts of Madrid . From early to mid-August , these fiestas are commemorated with processions , open-air dancing and <head>XYZ</head>   concerts   in   the   park   of   the   Vistillas   and   its   vicinity   . conscience   campaigns   for   the   legal   right   for   those   who   have   a   conscientious   objection   to   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="497">
<answer instance="497" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
The non-word "dord" was excised, and the definition of the adjacent entry "Doré furnace" was expanded from "A furnace for refining dore bullion" to "a <head>XYZ</head> in which dore bullion is refined" to close up the space. Gove wrote that this was "probably too bad, for why shouldn't "dord" mean 'density'?" 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="296">
<answer instance="296" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
the focal point may reach , and this heat can be used to generate electricity, melt steel, make hydrogen fuel or nanomaterials. The largest solar <head>XYZ</head> is at Odeillo in the Pyrénées-Orientales in France, opened in 1970. It employs an array of plane mirrors to gather sunlight, reflecting it onto a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="927">
<answer instance="927" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
of sidewalks averaged 74%. Research at the University of North Carolina for the U.S. Department of Transportation found that the presence or absence of a <head>XYZ</head> and the speed limit are significant factors in the likelihood of a vehicle/pedestrian crash. Sidewalk presence had a risk ratio of 0.118, which means that 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="781">
<answer instance="781" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
neighborhood where only a few hours ago police and ambulance sirens blared and the victim of a family squabble lay bleeding and unconscious on the <head>XYZ</head>    . " That's the neighborhood, " the pastor said. " It's not uncommon here. " He is a former prison guard and knows violence well. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="598">
<answer instance="598" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
said to have taken place . The rest of your day is free to maybe shop , visit the Sistine Chapel or relax in a <head>XYZ</head>   caf?   . (   BB   )   Day   7   Rome   ? Florence   Today   begins   with   a   drive   through   the   Chianti   wine-producing   region   of   Tuscany   to   Renaissance   Florence   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="715">
<answer instance="715" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
still open. Bit how'd you know about it? " he paper isn't out until noon. " Eliot placed the pieces of the cup on the <head>XYZ</head>    and brushed his hands on his jeans. He looked even taller than his father. " I met an old friend of my father's at the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="755">
<answer instance="755" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
Oxford Street and Tottenham Court Road. People were massed in a giant semi-circle outside the entrance, spilling way over into Oxford and onto the opposite <head>XYZ</head>    . Police barricades were set up and several police cars were parked down the street. People were standing on tip-toe, looking over the heads of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="203">
<answer instance="203" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
notably tin, lead and (at a higher temperature) copper, can be recovered from their ores by simply heating the rocks in a fire or blast <head>XYZ</head> a process known as smelting. The first evidence of this extractive metallurgy dates from the 5th and 6th millennia BC and was found in the archaeological 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="231">
<answer instance="231" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
toll, in the coldest winter months some daring motorists would cross on the firmly frozen river. Later that same decade, many of the city's brick <head>XYZ</head> were converted to concrete; the bronze plaques of the concrete installers are still visible today. The start of the 20th century brought economic challenge to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="489">
<answer instance="489" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
is not used by itself, but instead as the sensors of larger electrical systems. For example, a thermocouple might be used to help ensure a <head>XYZ</head> temperature remains constant. For this reason, instrumentation engineering is often viewed as the counterpart of control engineering. Computer engineering deals with the design of computers 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="695">
<answer instance="695" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
hint at it. Mr-TSATSARONIS : Yes, I tried to show him that I wasn't going to let, you know, down so easily. ZWERDLING : Actually, <head>XYZ</head>    vendors in New York face another threat, and it's a lot bigger than unruly competition. The mayor wants to ban pushcarts from some of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="923">
<answer instance="923" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
In town and city centers (known as downtown in North America) the amount of pedestrian traffic can exceed motorized traffic, and in this case the <head>XYZ</head> can occupy more than half of the width of the road, or the whole road can be reserved for pedestrians, see Pedestrian zone. Sidewalks may 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="166">
<answer instance="166" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
of these are fly ash, a by-product of coal-fired power plants, ground granulated blast furnace slag, and silica fume, a byproduct of industrial electric arc <head>XYZ</head> The use of these materials in concrete reduces the amount of resources required, as the mineral admixtures act as a partial cement replacement. This displaces 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1043">
<answer instance="1043" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
occupy land near railroad tracks, under overpasses, and waterways. Commercial squatting is common in Thailand, where businesses temporarily seize nearby public real estate (such as <head>XYZ</head> roadsides, beaches, etc.) and roll out their enterprise, and at closing time they fold it in and lock it up, thus avoiding the extra cost 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="425">
<answer instance="425" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
lead from 1678 and to copper from 1687. It was also applied to iron foundry work in the 1690s, but in this case the reverberatory <head>XYZ</head> was known as an air furnace. The foundry cupola is a different (and later) innovation. This was 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="94">
<answer instance="94" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
and coke. A related characteristic is the Coke Strength After Reaction (CSR) index; it represents coke's ability to withstand the violent conditions inside the blast <head>XYZ</head> before turning into fine particles. The water content in coke is practically zero at the end of the coking process, but it is often water 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="309">
<answer instance="309" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
sources provide more information on the composition and function of the whole mechanism. The Wolfenbüttel manuscript in particular provides the following description: ...having built a <head>XYZ</head> right at the front of the ship, they set on it a copper vessel full of these things, having put fire underneath. And one of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="780">
<answer instance="780" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
so she could claim what she wanted more than anything in the world: the truth about her brother's last days.Officer Tommy Wynn stood on the <head>XYZ</head>    , looking up at the white wall on the side of Garcia's Pharmacy. The first rays of the sunset cast a soft red glow over 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="795">
<answer instance="795" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
a glimpse of the ten-year-old Kathy he used to know. In her face was a child's rejoinder of I did not! The boy on the <head>XYZ</head>    wisely conceded the argument and hid behind his mother's coat. A mounted policeman galloped up to Mallory and her prisoner. The cop was grinning as 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="686">
<answer instance="686" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
side. He seems excited to have survived and is very pleased with himself. EXT. NEW YORK STREET - DAY The Mugger steps out onto the <head>XYZ</head>    and hurries toward the subway. A patch of sleeve soaks up the blood from his eye. Sam starts after the man but instantly freezes. Hordes 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="914">
<answer instance="914" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
were built in ancient times. It was claimed that the Greek city of Corinth was paved by the 4th-century, and the Romans were particularly prolific <head>XYZ</head> builders – they called them "semitas". However, by the Middle Ages, narrow roads had reverted to being simultaneously used by pedestrians and wagons without any 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1013">
<answer instance="1013" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
trict with the coastal Raouche area. The street is a large concentration of shopping stores, boutiques, restaurants, banks, street vendors, <head>XYZ</head> cafes, newspaper kiosks, and a booming nightlife spurred by students from the neighboring American University of Beirut. The AUB campus is another popular visitor destination, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="879">
<answer instance="879" senseid="sense0" org_word="Sidewalk"/>
<context>
natural chalk, modern blackboard chalk is generally made from the mineral gypsum (calcium sulfate), often supplied in sticks of compressed powder about 10 cm (4 in) long. <head>XYZ</head> chalk is similar to blackboard chalk, but it is shaped into larger sticks and often colored. It is used to draw on sidewalks, streets, and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="345">
<answer instance="345" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
Baking has opened up doors to businesses such as cake shops and factories where the baking process is done with larger amounts in large, open <head>XYZ</head> The aroma and texture of baked goods as they come out of the oven are strongly appealing but is a quality that is quickly lost. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1045">
<answer instance="1045" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
on a scouting trip with Snoopy as their scout leader; Pig-Pen, the perpetually dirty boy who could raise a cloud of dust on a clean <head>XYZ</head> in a snowstorm, or inside a building; and Frieda, a girl proud of her "naturally curly hair," and who owned a cat named Faron, much 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="804">
<answer instance="804" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
of them with the same incredulity we felt two years ago, when the first person asked. Nobody ever asked during our four years on the <head>XYZ</head>    in Harlem, when we had nothing to sell except musical ferocity and an odd-couple look. People out there got used to the white boy playing 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="773">
<answer instance="773" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
on April Fool's Day when I noticed an odd caption under Sean Connery's photo. It read that he " will cement his immorality in the <head>XYZ</head>    at Mann's Chinese Theater in Hollywood. " # Prints and a signature used to suffice; now everybody's got a gimmick. # GINT SUKELIS # San 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="880">
<answer instance="880" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
(4 in) long. Sidewalk chalk is similar to blackboard chalk, but it is shaped into larger sticks and often colored. It is used to draw on <head>XYZ</head> streets, and driveways. Tailor's chalk is traditionally a hard chalk used to make temporary markings on cloth, mainly by tailors. However, it is now usually 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1084">
<answer instance="1084" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
studio setting. During the mid-1960s expansion of the house, Presley constructed a large wing on the south side of the main house that was a <head>XYZ</head> between the music room in the original one-story wing and the swimming pool area, that connected to the house by a small enclosed gallery. The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="968">
<answer instance="968" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
main reason cited by "National Geographic" in naming Atlanta a "Place of a Lifetime". The city's lush tree canopy, which filters out pollutants and cools <head>XYZ</head> and buildings, has increasingly been under assault from man and nature due to heavy rains, drought, aged forests, new pests, and urban construction. A 2001 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="740">
<answer instance="740" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
through the ground right next to fallen Val and Rhonda! They roll sideways, come up running, and sprint for Pham Van's along an old wooden <head>XYZ</head>    . 81 EXT. PHAM VAN'S STORE - DAY 81 Earl flings open the front door. Val and Rhonda race toward the porch. Right on their 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="722">
<answer instance="722" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
of the neck just where it joined her skull, a blow that would have decapitated her if he'd been swinging a sword. Blood spattered the <head>XYZ</head>    and she went down to the stoop, and Koop hit her again, this time across the top of her undefended skull, a full, merciless swing, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="893">
<answer instance="893" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
World War II, street-style craps became popular among soldiers, who often played it using an Army blanket as a shooting surface. With no backboard or <head>XYZ</head> curb to hit against, this gave rise to presumed methods of dice control, of which the best was known as the "army blanket rol
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="922">
<answer instance="922" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
not be present as the amount of traffic (pedestrian or motorized) may not be enough to justify separating the two. In suburban and urban areas, <head>XYZ</head> are more common. In town and city centers (known as downtown in North America) the amount of pedestrian traffic can exceed motorized traffic, and in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="716">
<answer instance="716" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
the avenue, as a great hearse, drawn by huge black horses, moved to the dirgelike music of a military band. The men standing on the <head>XYZ</head>    uncovered as the be-flagged coffin passed. Women wept. " Lincoln's funeral, " said T., with the authority of one who had spent many hours in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1041">
<answer instance="1041" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
It has made the riverfront accessible to the public. The area also has a new amphitheater for live performances and improved access through ramps and <head>XYZ</head> Fountains and color-changing lights have been added underneath two bridges which carry pedestrian traffic across the normally-open levee breachings. The project stretches approximately four blocks 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="434">
<answer instance="434" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
William Blake Richmond, frustrated with the pall cast by coal smoke. Although there were earlier pieces of legislation, the Public Health Act 1875 required all <head>XYZ</head> and fireplaces to consume their own smoke. It also provided for sanctions against factories that emitted large amounts of black smoke. The provisions of this 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="15">
<answer instance="15" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnace"/>
<context>
several ways to fuse many small glass canes together into a multicolored pattern, resulting in millefiori beads or chevron beads (sometimes called "trade beads"). " <head>XYZ</head> glass" beads encase a multicolored core in a transparent exterior layer which is then annealed in a furnace. More economically, millefiori beads can also be 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1005">
<answer instance="1005" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
times it was called "Ausa" by the Romans. Iberian coins bearing this name have been found there. The Visigoths called it Ausona. Sewage caps on <head>XYZ</head> around the city will also read "Vich," an old form of the name. During the 8th and 9th centuries, Vic sat in the Spanish Marches 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="637">
<answer instance="637" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
conference today with detectives and her family. The black-and-white video shows the 22-year-old Ms. Freeland-Gaither flailing in vain as a man rushes her along a <head>XYZ</head>    to a parked car. " It's devastating to watch that video. You see him pull up. He's so calm, " Keisha Gaither told the Philadelphia 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="930">
<answer instance="930" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
of 0.118, which means that the likelihood of a crash on a road with a paved sidewalk was 88.2 percent lower than one without a <head>XYZ</head> “This should not be interpreted to mean that installing sidewalks would necessaril
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="150">
<answer instance="150" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
developed in the 1950s, and other oxygen steel making methods. Basic oxygen steelmaking is superior to previous steelmaking methods because the oxygen pumped into the <head>XYZ</head> limited impurities, primarily nitrogen, that previously had entered from the air used. Today, electric arc furnaces (EAF) are a common method of reprocessing scrap metal 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="284">
<answer instance="284" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnace"/>
<context>
Pittsburghese dialect "Stillers" or "Stihllers". Founder Art Rooney was almost always referred to by the nickname "The Chief" and Three Rivers Stadium as the "Blast <head>XYZ</head> during the championship years of the 1970s. During the offseason, the Steelers have long participated in charity basketball games throughout Western Pennsylvania and neighboring areas. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1036">
<answer instance="1036" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
the residences were built between 1890 and 1920. The East Hancock neighborhood was formerly characterised by a number of deep ravines originally covered with wooden <head>XYZ</head> that were filled in by the Dakota Heights Land Company; the neighbourhood was then "subdivided into residential lots". Development in the neighborhood began in the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="364">
<answer instance="364" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnace"/>
<context>
later became the subject of books, radio programs, television series, and movies. Tourism blossomed in the 1920s, when resorts were built around Stovepipe Wells and <head>XYZ</head> Creek. Death Valley National Monument was declared in 1933 and the park was substantially expanded and became a national park in 1994. The natural environment 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="717">
<answer instance="717" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
car payments. And as each cry goes out, we see a bundle of newspapers with blaring headlines like " Rent Due! " hurled onto the <head>XYZ</head>    . " # As the sense of urgency grows, one man on the street seems to have the solution. He points at the Aflac duck, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="692">
<answer instance="692" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
odd; even today so many years later I recognize from that posture that someone blind is in the room, or coming toward me on a <head>XYZ</head>    , or walking out in front of me across a mall. That particular tilt may somehow favor hearing, I don't know. # One night I 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="640">
<answer instance="640" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
flicking his tight chin toward the roof. Wink had no idea. His head still bubbled dizzy from his back-yard play. He stood silent on the <head>XYZ</head>    beside his father's leg. He tried to see what his father saw until one hand like a vice gripped Wink's neck from behind, and tightened. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1104">
<answer instance="1104" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
and mineral water tanks for all the purposes related to water. There is no proper waste management in Kathmandu, so garbage piles up on roads, <head>XYZ</head> and in waterways. Kathmandu's urban cosmopolitan character has made it the most populous city in Nepal, recording a population of 671,846 residents living in 235,387 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="122">
<answer instance="122" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
more than of Spotsylvania County and Orange County in central Virginia. Early settlers in the area had cut down the native forests to fuel blast <head>XYZ</head> that processed the iron ore found there, leaving only a secondary growth of dense shrubs. This rough terrain, which was virtually unsettled, was nearly impenetrable 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="634">
<answer instance="634" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
turn my head back to the room Where my love and I have laid . An ' I gaze back to the street , The <head>XYZ</head>   and   the   sign   ,   And   I   '   m   one   too   many   mornings   An   '   a   thousand   miles   behind   . It   's   a   restless   hungry   feeling   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="127">
<answer instance="127" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
the parts outside the furnace. For this reason, aged thermocouples cannot be taken out of their installed location and recalibrated in a bath or test <head>XYZ</head> to determine error. This also explains why error can sometimes be observed when an aged thermocouple is pulled partly out of a furnace—as the sensor 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="457">
<answer instance="457" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
VIII's Dissolution of the Monasteries saw the confiscation of church land throughout the country. Laskill, an outstation of Rievaulx Abbey and the only medieval blast <head>XYZ</head> so far identified in Great Britain, was one of the most efficient blast furnaces of its time. Slag from contemporary furnaces contained a substantial concentration 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="797">
<answer instance="797" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
chaos of sound and color, crackled around Otto. He inhaled deeply as he crossed the busy sidewalk and leaned into his mission. He walked the <head>XYZ</head> edge, footfall after footfall landing mostly not on the broad squares of concrete, but on the thin metal border that dropped at a right angle 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1031">
<answer instance="1031" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
Russell left the Presbyterian Church to join the Congregational Church. In his youth he was known to chalk Bible verses on fence boards and city <head>XYZ</head> in an attempt to convert unbelievers; he particularly noted the punishment of hell awaiting the unfaithful. At age sixteen, a discussion with a childhood friend 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="272">
<answer instance="272" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
in the late 1990s to Davis Wire, which still produces products such as fence and nails under the CF&I brand name. The facility operated blast <head>XYZ</head> until 1982, when the steel market collapsed. The main blast furnace structures were torn down in 1989, but due to asbestos content, many of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="897">
<answer instance="897" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
the building, previously the sidewalk, now at the basement level. Most property owners used screw jacks to raise their buildings to the new grade. The <head>XYZ</head> were covered, initially by wooden sidewalks, then brick barrel vaults, and eventually replaced by concrete sidewalks. Over the years, many of these underground spaces have 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1108">
<answer instance="1108" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
surfers persevered with sidewalk surfing, which is now called skateboarding. Sidewalk surfing has a similar feel to surfing and requires only a paved road or <head>XYZ</head> To create the feel of the wave, surfers even sneak into empty backyard swimming pools to ride in, known as pool skating. Eventually, surfing made 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="475">
<answer instance="475" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
can be very high. The hydration products that produce strength are essentially the same as those produced by Portland cement. Slag-lime cements. Ground granulated blast- <head>XYZ</head> slag is not hydraulic on its own, but is "activated" by addition of alkalis, most economically using lime. They are similar to pozzolan lime cements 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="173">
<answer instance="173" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
and costume jewellery. However Champion continued to use the cheaper calamine cementation method to produce lower-zinc brass and the archaeological remains of bee-hive shaped cementation <head>XYZ</head> have been identified at his works at Warmley. By the mid-to-late 18th century developments in cheaper zinc distillation such as John-Jaques Dony's horizontal furnaces in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="898">
<answer instance="898" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
at the basement level. Most property owners used screw jacks to raise their buildings to the new grade. The sidewalks were covered, initially by wooden <head>XYZ</head> then brick barrel vaults, and eventually replaced by concrete sidewalks. Over the years, many of these underground spaces have been filled or destroyed by subsequent 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="626">
<answer instance="626" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
started again at one , and of course his counting started at one after each " Boing ! " In his neighborhood there was a <head>XYZ</head>   with   perfectly   regular   slabs   all   the   same   size   . He   noticed   that   when   he   walked   along   this   sidewalk   he   always   got   the   following   repeating   pattern   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="713">
<answer instance="713" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
then hurries off along the street, disappearing around the Macy's Building down Stockton toward Market. I run across the patch of lawn, jump to the <head>XYZ</head>    and make the corner just in time to see him cross O'Farrell, the head of the cat bumping above his shoulder. At Market he turns 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="549">
<answer instance="549" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
even start reaching for their weapons . He calmly closed the door to the van and turned away . An old lady standing on the <head>XYZ</head>   with   her   dog   about   forty   feet   away   was   looking   on   incredulously   . Henri   replaced   the   Glock   in   his   shoulder   holster   ,   then   smiled   as   he   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="663">
<answer instance="663" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
the Missionaries call sidewalk counseling. Unidentified Woman 1: This is a child -- a child that you're ripping from your womb. (Excerpt from the Missionaries' <head>XYZ</head> counseling) Woman 1: This is a child with feelings. This is a child with feelings. It's a child with brains, with nerves, with a heart 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="102">
<answer instance="102" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnaces"/>
<context>
the west of the city is located Tannehill Ironworks Historical State Park, a Civil War site which includes the well-preserved ruins of the Tannehill Iron <head>XYZ</head> and the John Wesley Hall Grist Mill. The Summit is an upscale lifestyle center with many stores and restaurants. It is located in Southeast Birmingham 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="123">
<answer instance="123" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
are produced. It occurs in stars during stellar evolution. It is responsible for the galactic abundances of elements from carbon to iron. Stars are thermonuclear <head>XYZ</head> in which H and He are fused into heavier nuclei by increasingly high temperatures as the composition of the core evolves. Of particular importance is 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="400">
<answer instance="400" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
sun is high, it is nearly perpendicular to roof-angled glass, which maximizes solar gain at the wrong time of year, and acts like a solar <head>XYZ</head> Skylights should be covered and well-insulated to reduce natural convection ( warm air rising ) heat loss on cold winter nights, and intense solar heat 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="16">
<answer instance="16" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
or chevron beads (sometimes called "trade beads"). "Furnace glass" beads encase a multicolored core in a transparent exterior layer which is then annealed in a <head>XYZ</head> More economically, millefiori beads can also be made by limiting the patterning process to long, narrow canes or rods known as murrine. Thin cross-sections, or 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="521">
<answer instance="521" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
"hot metal". The hot metal was then poured into a steelmaking vessel to produce steel, typically an electric arc furnace, induction furnace or basic oxygen <head>XYZ</head> where the excess carbon is burned off and the alloy composition controlled. Earlier processes for this included the finery forge, the puddling furnace, the Bessemer 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="486">
<answer instance="486" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
evolving conceptions appear. Notably, "A figure strode to the fissure, no more than man-high yet terror seemed to go before it. They could see the <head>XYZ</head> of its eyes from afar; its arms were very long; it had a red [?tongue]". At this writing Tolkien contemplated an edict of the Valar 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="526">
<answer instance="526" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
scene between Kane and Leland after Kane loses the election. For the final scene, a stage at the Selznick studio was equipped with a working <head>XYZ</head> and multiple takes were required to show the sled being put into the fire and the word "Rosebud" consumed. Paul Stewart recalled that on the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="447">
<answer instance="447" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnace"/>
<context>
Rover and NASA's NERVA program from 1959 through 1972 at the Nevada Test Site, designated Kiwi, Phoebus, NRX/EST, NRX/XE, Pewee, Pewee 2 and the Nuclear <head>XYZ</head> with progressively higher power densities culminating in the Pewee (1970) and Pewee 2. Tests of the improved Pewee 2 design were cancelled in 1970 in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="941">
<answer instance="941" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
ol have been shown to have better concentration. Some sidewalks may be used as social spaces with <head>XYZ</head> cafes, markets, or busking musicians, as well as for parking for a variety of vehicles including cars, motorbikes and bicycles. Contemporary sidewalks are most often 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="361">
<answer instance="361" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
a new generation of copper smelting technologies. More recent furnaces have been designed based upon bath smelting, top jetting lance smelting, flash smelting and blast <head>XYZ</head> Some examples of bath smelters include the Noranda furnace, the Isasmelt furnace, the Teniente reactor, the Vunyukov smelter and the SKS technology to name a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="393">
<answer instance="393" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnaces"/>
<context>
neocolonialism and capitalism in general, especially in Latin America, but also in a changing Quebec society. "La Hora de los hornos" ("The Hour of the <head>XYZ</head> from 1968), directed by Octavio Getino and Arnold Vincent Kudales Sr., influenced a whole generation of filmmakers. Among the many political documentaries produced in the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="161">
<answer instance="161" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
They can vary in size up to 11 feet long and 30 inches in diameter. An increasing proportion of global steel is made using electric arc <head>XYZ</head> and the electric arc furnace it
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="799">
<answer instance="799" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
to fucking watch where he's going, asshole, I'm standing up so my bike wobbles from side to side while I pedal, I'm back on the <head>XYZ</head>    where the branches scrape my hair, pumping, pumping, barely stopping at River Street, bursting past the BU Bridge where I meant to stop, gasping past 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="146">
<answer instance="146" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
wood. The ancient Sinhalese managed to extract a ton of steel for every 2 tons of soil, a remarkable feat at the time. One such <head>XYZ</head> was found in Samanalawewa and archaeologists were able to produce steel as the ancients did. Crucible steel, formed by slowly heating and cooling pure iron 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="999">
<answer instance="999" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
that the fire destroyed an area about long and averaging wide, encompassing an area of more than . Destroyed were more than of roads, of <head>XYZ</head> 2,000 lampposts, 17,500 buildings, and $222 million in property—about a third of the city's valuation (more than $4 billion in 2015 dollars). Of the 300,000 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="430">
<answer instance="430" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
between one-third using coal or two-thirds using coke; however, the efficiency gains continued as the technology improved. Hot blast also raised the operating temperature of <head>XYZ</head> increasing their capacity. Using less coal or coke meant introducing fewer impurities into the pig iron. This meant that lower quality coal or anthracite could 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="591">
<answer instance="591" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
and also against the communications ... Linda " The child was crying for more than an hour , - Zarema says , - at the <head>XYZ</head>   ,   in   several   meters   from   cafe   "   Linda   "   . -   I   entered   the   cafe   and   asked   ,   "   Whose   girl   is   crying   outside   ? 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="963">
<answer instance="963" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalks"/>
<context>
worked at revitalizing the downtown areas of Beloit, Wisconsin and Missoula, Montana. During the 1990s, the downtown area underwent a revitalization, many of the city <head>XYZ</head> were repaved with decorative brick facing, and a different mix of shops and restaurants opened up to take advantage of the area's historical appeal. On 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="287">
<answer instance="287" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnace"/>
<context>
by Friedrich Wöhler in 1862 and still familiar to students: Calcium carbide production requires extremely high temperatures, ~2000 °C, necessitating the use of an electric arc <head>XYZ</head> In the US, this process was an important part of the late-19th century revolution in chemistry enabled by the massive hydroelectric power project at Niagara 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="536">
<answer instance="536" senseid="sense0" org_word="sidewalk"/>
<context>
the shade of an Indian laurel . Although the neighborhood had been built-out only five years earlier , the big tree had already lifted the <head>XYZ</head>   . Eventually   the   insistent   roots   would   block   lawn   drains   and   invade   the   sewer   system   . The   developer   's   decision   to   save   one   hundred   dollars   by   
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="79">
<answer instance="79" senseid="sense1" org_word="furnaces"/>
<context>
from combustible oil-shale gas (the term "shale gas" can also refer to gas occurring naturally in shales). Oil shale can also be burned directly in <head>XYZ</head> as a low-grade fuel for power generation and district heating or used as a raw material in chemical and construction-materials processing. Oil shale gains attention 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="236">
<answer instance="236" senseid="sense1" org_word="Furnace"/>
<context>
the majority shares in the companies. Over the course of twenty years, Carnegie's steel properties grew to include the Edgar Thomson Steel Works, the Lucy <head>XYZ</head> Works, the Union Iron Mills, the Homestead Works, the Keystone Bridge Works, the Hartman Steel Works, the Frick Coke Company, and the Scotia ore mines 
</context>
</instance>
