<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<corpus lang='english'>

<lexelt item="XYZ">

<instance id="742">
<answer instance="742" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
turned around and went back to their table and tapped Caitlyn's Junk.Whatever he might have been, his father has made him laughable.Named him after the <head>XYZ</head> he loved so well as a baby: a dish of sweetmilk set with rennet    and co-producer of Soul Food Below, George Tillman, who wrote and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="127">
<answer instance="127" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
producers and Canadian and US officials, who agree that the diplomatic cable - which Most houses have the same number of bathtubs as they have <head>XYZ</head> sets. The television sets are used all the time, but no one except small children ever use    But who told you that it had been? 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="104">
<answer instance="104" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
center of the town square. 27 While the intellectual elite conveyed its MR-WHEELER: There was little sign of remorse in Moscow, where the newspapers and <head>XYZ</head> suppressed reports from Tblisi, including the use of gas. Only days earlier a    best has come out of a terrible situation.... I was glued to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="193">
<answer instance="193" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
not only merchandise, but information, could be ordered to fit and zapped writing for television been different from writing for film? Joss whedon: I respect <head>XYZ</head> in a way that some people who came out of film might not. Some    awoke early the next morning and turned the knobs. He had 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="344">
<answer instance="344" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
live television. Steve Brill. STEVEN BRILL, Court TV: Well, I was listening Why buy a bookstore? # John Malone, who made a fortune in cable <head>XYZ</head> is offering $1 billion for Barnes and Noble trying to jump into a company    His feisty campaign has prompted the Johnson camp to respond with 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="927">
<answer instance="927" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
brought food -- figs, olives, tomatoes, eggplant, okra and bananas -- much of Albanians. And indeed, the sight of refugees crushed into trains, deprived of <head>XYZ</head> and water, and dumped unwillingly across an international border did summon up ghosts of    they do everything big. As a team they've brought a reexamination 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="247">
<answer instance="247" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
networks, a leading Saudi cleric asked God to " terminate " the Jews and and this woman's going to walk around, go to McDonald's, watch <head>XYZ</head> have whatever life she can put together for herself, and the baby is    movie Ben Hur, one of the themes of which is violent revenge. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="215">
<answer instance="215" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
When I hear all the people of New Orleans saying . A ceiling projector was beaming Day and Night onto the 5- by 7-foot Sony <head>XYZ</head> screen that had descended with such a soft, luxurious hum from a slit in    the WB comedy " Men, Women and Dogs. " Other Blacks 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="894">
<answer instance="894" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Milk, Food, and Environmental Sanitarians. # Bryan, F.L., Anderson, H.W., Cook a breakfast buffet, he methodically lifts the lid of every tray to inspect his <head>XYZ</head> options before selecting. Tall and grave, one month Cosor's junior, he    of thousands of people in a Chinese registry finds. # Men who ate spicy 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="970">
<answer instance="970" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
their lunch bags is floating around. EXT. SHORT BUS - CONTINUOUS We affect someone and identifying ways to respond to it. # Figure 2. Using <head>XYZ</head> preparation to teach irrational numbers # Skills taught: # * Wet and dry ingredient    rival # Brussels, Belgium -- Mars Inc., the family-owned maker of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="666">
<answer instance="666" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
pressed on: " Ever been sick otherwise? Measles? Chicken pox for the intravenous form of its Cordarone heart drug because it failed to meet a <head>XYZ</head> and Drug Administration request. Wyeth wanted to delay generic competition under U.S. rules that    " pig, " a nylon bag containing eight gallons of water, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="314">
<answer instance="314" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
games and finally the Internet-has lured children indoors. In two-income and stab backs in their quest for undeserved power and wealth. # The transition from <head>XYZ</head> to film has been a slow one. Even after his performance in " Four    video involving David Haines. And I want to ask all of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="698">
<answer instance="698" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
medicine and help to build a new post-Hussein nation. # ' MURDEROUS DICTATORS the Southwest Side, and her father, Frederick Smith, share a love of <head>XYZ</head> and the pleasures of a communal table. # Their South Shore kitchen bustles with    a civil war. Projects: Help Libya rebuild after war. Or bring 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="858">
<answer instance="858" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
tasted it right off the tree, and it really was delicious. ignore a more vulnerable class of children - working kids who help harvest America's <head>XYZ</head> # Those who work in the fields receive pesticide doses many times higher than    which turned out great. We get rave reviews from all their 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="346">
<answer instance="346" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
attacking him. # Yet Ms. Johnson's huge cash advantage -- she has and Alina Cho. Welcome back. One of the stereotypes we often see in <head>XYZ</head> are Asian women portrayed as sexually submissive sex objects. And I understand you watched    action, you know. Colin Powell was talking about this the other 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1083">
<answer instance="1083" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
since he lost his sense of smell, he could never eat dry # When I met Warren, he became my security blanket. He bought me <head>XYZ</head> clothes, and eventually, shelter. My mother was love struck herself.    he had found the burlap sack that Randall always carried, filled with scraps of food 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="586">
<answer instance="586" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
get some exercise, pork patties. // Costs are up, particularly for diesel fuel needed to deliver food to pantries by truck. Nearly half of the <head>XYZ</head> banks now buy some of    -- the fried **25;391;TOOLONG cuisine (no chitlins yet) is " the kind of food a lot of us grew up 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="694">
<answer instance="694" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
well worth a detour. # Not only had we not found help break them up to be more easily washed away. Nourished by this inexhaustible <head>XYZ</head> supply, the birds breed in enormous numbers and excrete in their turn. #    , director for food and beverage marketing at Danbury, Conn. -based Praxair. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="135">
<answer instance="135" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
In this country, presidential politics. Mitt Romney is ready to run, **27;2491;TOOLONG BOX Calls for Beginners Don't be intimidated by turkey hunters you see on <head>XYZ</head> who are champs with a diaphragm mouth call. If you can't use one    of bombarding people. JR: There is more rapidity now. I've watched television 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1081">
<answer instance="1081" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
for civilians. Stop the aggression. Stop the Russian terrorists. LINDSEY-HILSUM# cleared the forest and everything washed away in the rains PYLE Trees were an important <head>XYZ</head> source, producing nuts and syrups. And without wood, the Rapa Nuis could    afternoon. It took him half an hour to finish a small can of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="265">
<answer instance="265" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
chimpanzee babies who are torn away from their mothers. Chimpanzees let -- go called the extreme games. He won his event, but more importantly, the <head>XYZ</head> exposure re-ignited interest in skateboarding. About this time, he began to try a    what the hell I'm going do ROONEY Don says if they hadn't 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="225">
<answer instance="225" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
News. MS-DONNELLY: The Ethiopian rebel umbrella group, the EPRDF, arrived at the hair in front of the FTC if they didn't stop putting smut on <head>XYZ</head> did anybody say that? LAWRENCE: No, not at all. I    about public success, but I have mixed feelings about being well-known because Im on television. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="589">
<answer instance="589" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
an excellent accompaniment to the bread. # I'm a fool for of grass. // I think I said we intended to " grow our own <head>XYZ</head> " a formulation that seems remarkably naive in retrospect, since we only grew    lump meat because our hallowed, cold-water crab doesn't swim, according to Seattle-based 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="452">
<answer instance="452" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
wanting to be associated with Trump and the horde of Mexican rapists children to ask their parents questions. 6. Ask parents to watch a specific <head>XYZ</head> program with their children and to discuss the show afterward. 7. Suggest ways for    investigative social documentaries of the 1960s and 1970s were transformed in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1114">
<answer instance="1114" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
freeing them from a constant focus on day-to-day survival. A site of the earth' s population continues to grow, the need for a readily available <head>XYZ</head> supply increases. One of the effects of the population increase is urban sprawl,    , Harris SB, Harris-Giraldo R, Hanley AJG, Zinman B. Specific patterns of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="282">
<answer instance="282" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
that the kids -- they got to get through all was with the advent of black radio that I thought black people would watch music <head>XYZ</head> programs oriented toward themselves. " # Still not enough positive black images # With    " " we don't go see a movie every day. We 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="42">
<answer instance="42" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
in the figures took place in the sixties. Mr. GOLDBERG: There was television in the sixties. Mr. HOROWITZ: It had very little to do with <head>XYZ</head>    your list of the top 10 preschool TV shows. My family watches very little television, limited to about one hour a day. We choose to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="986">
<answer instance="986" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
of the state's division of Food, Drug and Radiation Safety, said it was'' one of the more 27359 Objectives. We investigated Cambodian refugee women's past <head>XYZ</head> experiences and the relationship between those experiences and current food beliefs, dietary practices,    . But she also committed to preparing an entire vegetarian meal, along 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="598">
<answer instance="598" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
industrial agriculture. Here are a few standout responses: # My Dad started . All right. So if the Yanks win, Mat donates ten tons of <head>XYZ</head> to Philadelphias food bank. How did you come up with the idea, Mat    . # How much else are you going to get done if 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="249">
<answer instance="249" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
turned on but shows a blank screen, coaxing the viewer to picture # KHARTOUM, Sudan Sudan's president declares a three-month state of emergency and state-run <head>XYZ</head> says he's dissolving Parliament. SUDAN-POLITICS. Lead has moved. # BREST,    supply is prodigious - 15 hours a week on the radio, five half-hours on television. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="219">
<answer instance="219" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Network. Mother MARY ANGELICA, Franciscan Nun, Founder of EWTN: from tape year at the Houston convention. Day by day she is trotted out for the <head>XYZ</head> shows (" Larry King Live " and the evening news among them),    reason why the vision of social reality it projects is a conservative one. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1088">
<answer instance="1088" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
fly-fishing. What makes a great small trip is having a combination of terrific food and activities, plus a little history and gorgeous scenery. " (A <head>XYZ</head>    would take. It occurred to me that it wasn't something that would put food on the table, either, as far as I could tell. I 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1024">
<answer instance="1024" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
places the food by Grace's bed. She is sleeping. # INT. LEONARD'S HOME flavorful foods. You go, grill! Author Affiliation Melissa Clark is a freelance <head>XYZ</head> journalist and cookbook author. // #    had each paid only $360 for the barge rental and about $50 apiece for our food for the entire 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="577">
<answer instance="577" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Citarella and then have waiters come in black tie and pass community, where many of the retired veterans live in substandard housing and depend on <head>XYZ</head> bank programs to supplement Social Security checks totaling less than $1,000 a month. #    and the harvest are both heating up; consider sharing your bounty 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="189">
<answer instance="189" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
WAGNER You know, that came about by Mr. Lou Wasserman (ph) Community acted on Yugoslavia yesterday. We have a report from Lindsay Taylor of Independent <head>XYZ</head> News. MR-TAYLOR: It was in the early hours of this morning after a    -- USA Government is Nazi -- world need peace. " The Chinese 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="653">
<answer instance="653" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
for the Register. She also writes CathyThomasCooks.com, a website for food lovers a preservative) and nitrate-containing processed meats and fish. Head it off Keeping a <head>XYZ</head> diary can be helpful in identifying potential headache triggers. Once you suspect a food    ve lost them before you had a chance. The three-part strategy 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="780">
<answer instance="780" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
to children referred imprecisely to the work of the Children hypothesized that 2 important environmental influences on diet are the availability of food retail and <head>XYZ</head> service establishments. 1-7 # Previous research has examined the relationship between the availability of    rocket launches and a lot of different aspects of their nuclear 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="222">
<answer instance="222" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
He left that post in September and most recently worked as chief executive With the best foot. That's right. TAMRON-HALL# We saw you all over <head>XYZ</head> NATALIE-MORALES# All over. TAMRON-HALL# All over. All over Instagram, Rose Bowl    trees to Isabelle. When Isabelle slept, Mary studied her science textbooks or watched television, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1098">
<answer instance="1098" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
My parents both grew up on farms. They wanted me to mild indigestion in June 2007, the then 47-year-old chalked it up to the Cuban <head>XYZ</head> she'd eaten on vacation. Two months later, while she was visiting the    New Zealand and the United States. # He says Americans consume the most 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="973">
<answer instance="973" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
example, it will pay up to $250 for haul-out fees, towing, food and lodging expenses. And there is no sizable deductible. Author Affiliation Tim Banse <head>XYZ</head> web. # . # KRILL: These small shrimp-like crustaceans are a staple food for a tremendous array of marine creatures, including rockfish, salmon, baleen whales    
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="939">
<answer instance="939" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
to her heavy approach, the flour and yeast happily rewarding the , I might not have told him. JOHN-QUIONES-1-# (Off-camera) Let him eat the dirty <head>XYZ</head> DINER-1FEMALE2-# Let him eat the dirty food. He was being a dirty man    willing to donate space for the organization should call Renee McGraw, head 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="312">
<answer instance="312" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
boys were watching Sammy so intently, and they were giggling so hard makes no difference at all, and neither do the consequences. Recall the long-running <head>XYZ</head> show Seinfeld that called itself " a show about nothing. " The implications for    the P.E. program. * ACTIVITY Over the last half century, technology-first 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="372">
<answer instance="372" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
with the Stars, " is fueling a renewed interest on the , including two from Reuters. They said that their car was clearly marked with <head>XYZ</head> The Israeli army said they didn't see the television markers. The Foreign    . Lots of activity. Peters waves the tape as he rushes over to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="419">
<answer instance="419" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Candidates Changed American Politics, 1992 " and he has a theory " Statistics are important for the record books. What seems to be important for <head>XYZ</head> (ads) is flair, charisma, " said Lanktree, whose Chicago-based business    As for Ms. Gruber, she is the anchor of the premier newscast on Italian television. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="357">
<answer instance="357" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
politics, your numbers do down and you are out? STASI There is a reason why there is an on and an off switch on that <head>XYZ</head> set, and if you don't- Rev. LOU SHELDON: But that doesn't- TED KOPPEL    'd like it. " Sooty seed pearls shone in the glare of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="596">
<answer instance="596" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
grown in the soil and drinking of the well water. # Yet while Emily 're on the road, it's hard to stay healthy. You're eating <head>XYZ</head> that's not exactly the best and especially when on dialysis, having your dietary    of your comments about how you vote with your wallets to put 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="990">
<answer instance="990" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
ceremonies, food and refreshments were served. Someone had brought some fireworks, so that at dusk SHOW AND SALE: Paintings, photography, jewelry, ceramics. Preshow gala with <head>XYZ</head> music. 5:30-9:30 p.m. December 6 ($ 12). Show and    So if you start with sort of the vows, some nice clothes, some food, some people 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="477">
<answer instance="477" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
watch some television? GRACE (edgy) Maybe... look -- just... Robert and Annie wait set in America, yet doesn't have a Black face in it. " <head>XYZ</head> biases are so blatant that media scholars and to the few outspoken activists within    plane crash in New York Monday morning on the Internet, and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="116">
<answer instance="116" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
and being accosted by none other than Morley Safer and " also facilitates previously impractical forms of democratic deliberation. With the electronic town meeting via <head>XYZ</head> computer, or some synthesis of both, citizens are offered direct contact with    appeared together in public for the first time, and for the first time, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="845">
<answer instance="845" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
that he doesn't have pencils in school, that his family is constantly neon sign heralding Woodpecker cider. Lizzie ordered a beer and, from the few <head>XYZ</head> options, an egg salad sandwich. She took up residence at a small table    " She also had a routine meeting with a nurse who " 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="541">
<answer instance="541" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
arts and crafts, games, music and prizes. 9 a.m. -5 , you got a lot of credit for sort of taking the bow in the <head>XYZ</head> war right to the streets, that every time Burger King or other rivals were    the Virgin is shown dispensing charity, her action suggesting that the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="836">
<answer instance="836" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
going to come in and help us eat it. DAVID: ( which compose the families Scolytidae and Platypodidae, depend on ephemeral deadwood for shelter and <head>XYZ</head> Many also dig burrows and care for their young in them. A very    a cook. ! SAFER-1on-camera: Youve boasted that you spend more on food 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="21">
<answer instance="21" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
television, and my dad said check this band out, they're great. And " says Marlene Sanders, coauthor of Waiting for Prime Time: The Women of <head>XYZ</head> News, who, in 1964, was the first woman to anchor a network    the big chill has been " rendered increasingly abstract -- a choreographed plunge 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="226">
<answer instance="226" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
television? did anybody say that? LAWRENCE: No, not at all. I about public success, but I have mixed feelings about being well-known because Im on <head>XYZ</head> Its nice, but its a pain in the neck, too. I    . We could argue for hours on the deeper cultural meanings of a perfectly 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="86">
<answer instance="86" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
And I think that it is really- it isn't- nobody- none from generation to generation. " 46328 # Josh Gamson gestured excitedly toward the five <head>XYZ</head> monitors, four computers and six telephones scattered about the modest hotel suite serving as    10-episode series as part of its move into providing content for 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="95">
<answer instance="95" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
to start up a computer, youd need two hours to have a vote to decide whether or not you get to go out and buy <head>XYZ</head> Certainly a very different system down there. HUME: And what is your    " # Some of the first season's games have been shown on Black 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="40">
<answer instance="40" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
reporter is being treated as a homicide.... " Harry set the . As you move about the house, your choice of art appears on high-definition <head>XYZ</head> monitors. Music, lighting, and climate settings all tag along, too.    decline in the figures took place in the sixties. Mr. GOLDBERG: There was television in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="700">
<answer instance="700" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
care to people affected by persistent violence in Congo, as intense clashes across other villages, and sometimes found work for a few days, to buy <head>XYZ</head> and shelter, but he rarely spoke and was looked on as a ne'erdo-well;    Paul could barely track who was saying what. His jurors had devoured 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="295">
<answer instance="295" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the stars of " Miami Vice, " and we all know night edition of Larry King Live. He is part of the hottest team on <head>XYZ</head> A veteran network correspondent, Ed Bradley breaks the mold of cool and detached    with empty fast-meal containers, and all the seating was angled to face 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="957">
<answer instance="957" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Science of Making Healthy Food Taste Amazing " (Oxmoor House, $35). If it's a little / KATIE RIDLEY / Staff Graphic: JOEL RATING *** > <head>XYZ</head> Contemporary French food cooked with great finesse. Mediterranean and Asian touches set the flavor tone. >    through the meal and then gets angry after discovering 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="775">
<answer instance="775" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
so it might show up where you don't expect it. And consider. But food retrievers have found allies among chefs and restaurant executives in salvaging <head>XYZ</head> that might otherwise go to waste. # " Our job is to be the    Cat stalking beneath the furniture, looking out with eyes finely reflexive 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="350">
<answer instance="350" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
driver says to me,' They all saw you, coast to is also considering the possibility of a late-night magazine show synopsizing the best of world <head>XYZ</head> During his years at " Alive, " he came to appreciate the ways    life, a certain percentage of what you do has got to be 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="184">
<answer instance="184" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
She'd done CPR on him, and how odd it had , individual Rams telecasts consistently still have been among the most-watched programs on St. Louis <head>XYZ</head> " The ratings have been decent over the last three or four years considering    he went on to make eighty-seven cowboy movies by 1951, when 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="241">
<answer instance="241" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
personality Nigel Slater. Slater's sweet mum, who was hapless in the kitchen . It would be highly unusual, however, for Amish women to appear on <head>XYZ</head> in bikinis, as Ms. Yoder (fetchingly) does, or to cohabit with    Theatre on television, " he explains. " If I decide to place a television 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="678">
<answer instance="678" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
will be more to his liking. # And at the Useloff household, young do agree on that. The things we know works, state aid works, <head>XYZ</head> stamps works, extending unemployment which they've done, that works. This clearly    founded the company on Christian principles. " She doesn't want to just sell food, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1016">
<answer instance="1016" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
cheeses, and meats for Gabriella Caf and Full Pint beer were served -- in iconic red plastic Solo cups -- with food from the Franktuary <head>XYZ</head> truck and Lucy's banh mi sandwich cart. Similar but    of the attendees took some of the food home and their 15-year-old juvenile ingested this food 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="789">
<answer instance="789" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Many families have been stuck in their homes for six days now women are also building makeshift schools, working to outlaw female genital mutilation, distributing <head>XYZ</head> and organizing groups of women lawyers, teachers, and widows. 10 Sidebar    broccoli was yummy and the crackers were yucky? What if her attitude toward the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="737">
<answer instance="737" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
herbivores couldn't find enough vegetation during the drought. When the babesiosis-infected Regis Philbin was due to be one of our guests tonight. He has terrible <head>XYZ</head> poisoning. We wish Regis the best and hope he gets better real soon.    and under Noise Rating: THREE BELLS Talking normally gets difficult 70-75 decibels 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="978">
<answer instance="978" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
conduct an investigation and for the USDA, the Food and Drug Administration, and the Environmental Protection Agency to amend regulations for GM pharmaceutical benefits of <head>XYZ</head> " says Sylvia Rowe, president and CEO of the International Food Information Council. # But the bedrock of nutrition advice, the government's Dietary    strategies, you 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="227">
<answer instance="227" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
nice, but its a pain in the neck, too. I . We could argue for hours on the deeper cultural meanings of a perfectly ordinary <head>XYZ</head> show, while Bob had already turned the channel to watch the Yankees. Clifford    in exile rushed to reaffirm its opposition to any compromise with Iraq. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="112">
<answer instance="112" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
on television, he'd never have been convicted. Why? They never would have had on a stretcher, loaded into an ambulance. The doors close. REPORTERS and <head>XYZ</head> cameramen line the sidewalk giving reports and interviewing doctors from the ballroom. We PICK    of The Sopranos is really going to have a long-term effect 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="520">
<answer instance="520" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
" Maybe we shouldn't bother Tom, " they say, but he Crafts. # The Bounds of Taste # The ability of a hit movie or <head>XYZ</head> show, such as " Gone With the Wind " or " Miami Vice,    propaganda, does it make a difference whether it's Saddam Hussein trying to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="161">
<answer instance="161" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
crow roosts for National Geographic Explorer (it airs June 2 at 8 Mr-SIRKIN: Well, we -- we came to the record companies first and the <head>XYZ</head> syndicaters and we said,' Well, let's do something different.'    at large of The American Spectator and author of Wealth ; Poverty, Life After Television and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="891">
<answer instance="891" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
with lake trout is shown in Figure 3. Lakes with fewer . " Memphis is a transit crossroads. You can get any kind of healthy <head>XYZ</head> you want here. You just have to want it. " The same goes    compensating advisors for time spent. Even the most dedicated teachers still need 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="417">
<answer instance="417" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the way-not just broadcasts of games but an array of NBA-produced programs, Indira Gandhi, was herself assassinated. We have more from Jeremy Thompson of Independent <head>XYZ</head> News. MR-THOMPSON: India was in shock tonight at the latest tragedy to befall    a book on the coverage of the' 92 campaign " Strange Bedfellows: 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="153">
<answer instance="153" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
debuted this week starts with a simple scene: A mother is waiting celebration and praise. They were from strangers mostly, those who saw her on <head>XYZ</head> and others who had read her books. Dear Anya Thomas, most began (    murdered his wife last year and then hanged himself. No, appearing on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="427">
<answer instance="427" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
bring. They handle it better than most men do. Dorry's husband building with a radically different ambiance. Her old room had six beds and a <head>XYZ</head> that attracted " 20 or 30 people who came in every day " to watch    hours of debate on local sports radio. One of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="559">
<answer instance="559" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
enrich their pantry and their cooking vocabulary and being willing to break . // Many say Frasca is the area's best restaurant. Does the Boulder <head>XYZ</head> community resent you? // Stuckey: We didn't come here to say we    At mealtimes, reflect on your eating habits, your attitudes toward wasting food and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="492">
<answer instance="492" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Neal Gabler calls the " conversion of life into an entertainment -- issued the following statement: # " All of us at Fox and Spelling <head>XYZ</head> share the grief of those impacted by the tragedy in Oklahoma City. We are    our cars is you. " More effective are pricing pitches, such 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="253">
<answer instance="253" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
even know you have been attacked for probably a couple of weeks Muslim refugee. Vlatko Menix, a media magnate who uses his string of local <head>XYZ</head> stations in West Mostar to broadcast a hard line Catholic message to viewers, says    Later, he even came outside to witness Joni's and my demonstration 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1008">
<answer instance="1008" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
aid are nearly depleted. The conflict has spread into neighboring Chad. # Sudan each of the dishes. He didn't taste any, but worked on the <head>XYZ</head> as if it were an artistic material anti gave back his plate, injured,    Shakers fed about 1,000 of the soldiers, severely depleting the community's valuable 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="429">
<answer instance="429" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
Canal 9, is airing all the NBA Finals games, making them time, the U.S. plans to try to improve transmission of anti-Castro broadcasters Radio and <head>XYZ</head> Marti, long a sore point between the two governments. TV Marti is rarely    It's called a Tale of Three Cities. And it airs on many 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="895">
<answer instance="895" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
options before selecting. Tall and grave, one month Cosor's junior, he of thousands of people in a Chinese registry finds. # Men who ate spicy <head>XYZ</head> at least once a week were 10 percent less likely to die during the seven-year    Ana in 2014 - triggering a sales tax jump of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="521">
<answer instance="521" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
such as " Gone With the Wind " or " Miami Vice, propaganda, does it make a difference whether it's Saddam Hussein trying to use <head>XYZ</head> or whether it's George Bush trying to use television? FRED BARNES, Senior    UNIVERSITY PRESS Middle Eastern studies, Jewish studies, Irish studies, peace studies, television and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="231">
<answer instance="231" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
we'll be behind it! " A Dreary Downstairs For many families, # Comments from some members of the House Judiciary Committee from interviews, statements and <head>XYZ</head> appearances: # Rep. Steve Rothman, D-N.J. # " I'm not going    to know a few people, read the newspapers, listened to radio and watched television, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="547">
<answer instance="547" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Latin Festival, Aug. 28, features Latin and Caribbean music, authentic food, children's activities and more. 803-939-0360, **31;6950;TOOLONG. # Charleston -- - fastest growth in the <head>XYZ</head> residuals arena. # BioCycle tallied a total of 118 food residual projects throughout the United States. Of those, 95 are full-scale facilities,    noon to 3 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="61">
<answer instance="61" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
India today is far more adventurous than it was even five years ago show and appears in commercials. # " Hey, if you're surfing through <head>XYZ</head> channels, where are you more likely to stop? On a man's game    blockade aside and wave Talley through -- EXT. MEDIA AREA -- NIGHT The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="662">
<answer instance="662" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
food processor; discard peel. To pulp, add 1/2 cup mayonnaise, 1 tablespoon and outfitted with airy rye gnocchi. Think about it: this chef makes German <head>XYZ</head> sound cool. I wonder what he could do with liverwurst. -- J.K. # HORSERADISH-CRUSTED    welfare certainly feel stigmatized. # " I find myself sometimes going 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="896">
<answer instance="896" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
week were 10 percent less likely to die during the seven-year Ana in 2014 - triggering a sales tax jump of 22 percent from 2011. <head>XYZ</head> is a key player. This year, about 29 restaurants and bars are expected    UNIDENTIFIED-MALE: People have got to do something. We ai nt got no 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="78">
<answer instance="78" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the bar against my own will, finding myself caring about a college basketball Carl had borrowed it from his father's room. This was his father's <head>XYZ</head> IV, ther. My father's television. My father is television.    . " Interviewees spend an average four hours a day watching television. They see television as 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="618">
<answer instance="618" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
very specific; for example, a person might like barbecue potato chips in the following sections. # Food Security Soaring food prices resulted in a global <head>XYZ</head> crisis in 2008. Many countries experienced protests and even rioting. Numerous factors have    a month ago. So the world's got its hands full now with 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="355">
<answer instance="355" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
those of us who live in rural America are no longer Madison, who found his niche in Westerns in the 1940s and starred in the <head>XYZ</head> series " The Adventures of Wild Bill Hickok. " Feb. 6. Age 74    done on Star Jones Reynolds had turned negative, Linda Stasi. So, is 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="13">
<answer instance="13" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
were repeatedly copied when the pictures were popular, and they are now of this. " # Like most Tunisians, Mohammed was watching the news on <head>XYZ</head> when authorities released the names of the killers. " By 7 p.m. someone called    the Fox of the next episode will be even more heartbreakingly 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="558">
<answer instance="558" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
agricultural sector is not independent of technological progress in general. Although, prima me, that anecdote captures the spirit of this series. It is about curious <head>XYZ</head> lovers wishing to enrich their pantry and their cooking vocabulary and being willing to break    . // Many say Frasca is the area's best restaurant. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="946">
<answer instance="946" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
food. Howie's soup had two enormous kreplach. Laurie's omelet, with a 's not enough just to seek redress in court afterward. The recent overturning of <head>XYZ</head> Lion's fraud case against ABC's PrimeTime Live further reinforces what most businesses knew    pre-millennial China. // We escaped from the traffic at tiny sidewalk restaurants. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="584">
<answer instance="584" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
his wallet to remind him of his less fortunate past. Smith, Vicki to agree to eat more grains and greens, Joe took them to our <head>XYZ</head> coop. He drove us all to the Ballard pool to get some exercise,    pork patties. // Costs are up, particularly for diesel fuel needed to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="453">
<answer instance="453" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
and to discuss the show afterward. 7. Suggest ways for investigative social documentaries of the 1960s and 1970s were transformed in recent decades into reality <head>XYZ</head> The internationally popular fly-on-the-prison-wall programmes have brought us carefully chosen representatives of purportedly ordinary    about what the Japanese industry did in a coordinated way to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="892">
<answer instance="892" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
here. You just have to want it. " The same goes compensating advisors for time spent. Even the most dedicated teachers still need to put <head>XYZ</head> on their table. In my case, I did finally negotiate a small stipend    Procedures to investigate waterborne illness. Ames, IA: International Association of Milk, Food, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="399">
<answer instance="399" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
In television, we make pretty good money. And sometimes... FORD: I bet you ' Baffled' Officials, Mixed Messages # In late September, Secretary Thompson told <head>XYZ</head> viewers that the government was prepared to deal with any kind of bio terrorism attack     238366 BOB EDWARDS, Host: The man who made a fortune 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="33">
<answer instance="33" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
really do believe our own press, but the reality is that the the number forty-three. When he turned forty, Charlotte had given him a bigger <head>XYZ</head> and a genuine Eames Lounge Chair. A month before his forty-third, when she    and outside groups focusing on the presidential race have spent close to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="726">
<answer instance="726" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
assistance that are essential to building God's kingdom. # ON THE apparently without homes. Tell me about the mobilization efforts where you are to get <head>XYZ</head> to the people in the areas that are hardest hit? TANIGUCHI: Well,    now more in federal, state and local taxes than they do in housing 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="912">
<answer instance="912" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
and raw materials--is the most pervasive threat to Chinese vertebrates (Li production will keep pace with a growing world population, Sidebar but poor distribution of <head>XYZ</head> will lead to continuing malnourishment in parts of sub-Saharan Africa. The potential for famine    of the other essentials that the book deals with -- the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="792">
<answer instance="792" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
we've got lots of food down here. Mr. GARFIELD: This is the battery supply. Ms. GARFIELD: , Utah Dear Morgan: The most common type of <head>XYZ</head> poisoning comes from eating food that contains harmful bacteria. Food becomes contaminated with bacteria when it is prepared improperly    whom return every year after starting 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="923">
<answer instance="923" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
not a limiting factor. Prey studies, scanty for New England did not have eczema and there is no family history of nut or any other <head>XYZ</head> allergy. The only warning sign that your expert neglected to mention was if your    land, anyway. He was a blockade runner, kept Lee's troops in 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="442">
<answer instance="442" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
league's television deals with NBC and cable's TNT. # Still, though the 23 established least. They, too, are doing product placement. They are creating entire <head>XYZ</head> shows. MindShare recently struck a deal with ABC to jointly produce a prime-time drama    carried a poster with a powerful and emotional image in the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="504">
<answer instance="504" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
in person, it's difficult to imagine the mismatch confrontations during his days that general being grilled by you. And when I say, I watch on <head>XYZ</head> I do. And I watch in " Time " magazine. And I    down. " That's what people used to do for entertainment before there was 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="913">
<answer instance="913" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
continuing malnourishment in parts of sub-Saharan Africa. The potential for famine of the other essentials that the book deals with -- the essence of Italy: <head>XYZ</head> (Footage-of-Frances) Mrs-MAYES: (Voiceover) Cooking takes very little time here, because with primo    . You go up and say, you have a... And you buy them 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1007">
<answer instance="1007" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
(lamb stew, corned beef and cabbage, etc.) and more real Irish of grain and other essentials for the region's 2.8 million people who rely on <head>XYZ</head> aid are nearly depleted. The conflict has spread into neighboring Chad. # Sudan    each of the dishes. He didn't taste any, but worked on the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1011">
<answer instance="1011" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
PELLEY: How many elephants have you killed? Unidentified Man 3: ( and effect of law and compliance with them is mandatory. # STEVEN SUNDLOF # <head>XYZ</head> and Drug Administration # Washington, D.C. # Robert Pearl's article about 21st century    large zippered front pocket for clothing and low-bulk items. Twin mesh wand 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="633">
<answer instance="633" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
" Gardening and attracting deal with these issues (Rippe, 1999). Public Concern and Knowledge About Food Safety Issues # Because of the growing concern surrounding <head>XYZ</head> safety issues, consumer attitudes    out the window, at least for this meal. Seeing me reach for the food, the kids took this as a signal 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="550">
<answer instance="550" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
you'll find lots of like-minded folks at this weekend's Startup Weekend local color. Then at dusk they would be whisked back to the liner for <head>XYZ</head> and parties as the floating city weighed anchor and sped on to Jellynock Island or    to sanity; you nurse them back to their true selves; 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="663">
<answer instance="663" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
wonder what he could do with liverwurst. -- J.K. # HORSERADISH-CRUSTED welfare certainly feel stigmatized. # " I find myself sometimes going for days without <head>XYZ</head> so my kids can eat, " said Krista Ziebart, an epileptic mother of    an offensive against the usual suspects-odor-producing bacteria-by doing the following: Get rid 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="270">
<answer instance="270" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
scream for the Giants to go for it and for the Raiders to not afford to do its best. " That misses today's economic reality. <head>XYZ</head> and TV news make money-a lot of it-regardless of how good a job they do    in 1981) is destined to be remembered more for his 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="587">
<answer instance="587" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
by truck. Nearly half of the food banks now buy some of -- the fried **25;391;TOOLONG cuisine (no chitlins yet) is " the kind of <head>XYZ</head> a lot of us grew up on, " says Pryor. The 3-year-old restaurant    's light eaters pause. Yet it fits perfectly with the rustic style 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="809">
<answer instance="809" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
good food. MITCHELL: You know it is. We asked him to take our Shoestring all, end all' for the future of agriculture. We've got the <head>XYZ</head> and Drug Administration just approving the irradiation of meat. And we've got the    , including neighborhood cleanups, housing renovations in poorer communities and orange harvesting 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="716">
<answer instance="716" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
how important these are for their health. But not many expensive town in the world " because the gold rush had lured " too many <head>XYZ</head> purveyors for the population. " The purveyors all had loans to pay off,    to brain cells that are blocked from their blood supply. They are 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="756">
<answer instance="756" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Closing ceremonies and car show on July 15 at Route , where one salt alternative has been widely adopted in home kitchens and by the <head>XYZ</head> industry, showed a 60 percent decrease in deaths from stroke and heart disease among    and prayer and developing good habits, or " personal disciplines "; 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="835">
<answer instance="835" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
The next afternoon, Kimiko pulled Lucy to the sink where a cuttlefish lay No way you're leaving. This is fantastic. We have so much leftover <head>XYZ</head> You're going to come in and help us eat it. DAVID: (    which compose the families Scolytidae and Platypodidae, depend on ephemeral deadwood for shelter 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="286">
<answer instance="286" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the girl with her abductor in the street. . The nation's leading radio broadcasting company is now scrapping plans to buy LIN Television Company: LIN <head>XYZ</head> Ticker: LNTV; URL: http:www.lintv.com,    gush of blood flowing from the youthful body. " 44 More recently, Hamas television featured a Mickey Mouse look-alike urging children 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="425">
<answer instance="425" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
to do entertainment. It can purvey entertainment, but that's not the reality the U.S. government's outreach to Iranians-encompassing the Voice of America's Persian News Network <head>XYZ</head> channel, its radio counterpart Radio Farda, n24 and associated websites -- " has    women are, they possess a resiliency against the bleak hell that loneliness 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="117">
<answer instance="117" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
computer, or some synthesis of both, citizens are offered direct contact with appeared together in public for the first time, and for the first time, <head>XYZ</head> cameras were permitted to show her face, breaking a social taboo.    , as well as of the Israeli embassy there. # Al-Manar, the official television 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1105">
<answer instance="1105" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
and Drug Administration would send just that message. CENTANNI: And one footnote, mild soap every morning and evening. And, if you notice that a particular <head>XYZ</head> causes you to break out, then you should avoid eating that food. //    don't just come sneaking into people's kitchens if you don't eat they 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1089">
<answer instance="1089" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
and activities, plus a little history and gorgeous scenery. " (A Food would take. It occurred to me that it wasn't something that would put <head>XYZ</head> on the table, either, as far as I could tell. I would    Diane remembered the sister. She'd refused to take Kiley in because " my 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="866">
<answer instance="866" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
overruled the Food and Drug Administration's concerns on the hazards to children of the so-called morning-after pill . " The airport will have two " <head>XYZ</head> courts, which we're calling food collections, because they are higher quality than you would normally find, " Vasquez    . " # It took decades for 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="496">
<answer instance="496" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
* Keep your bedroom cool, dark, and quiet. * If there spending. Rollins said he and Perot discussed pouring $ 50 million or more into <head>XYZ</head> before Rollins accepted the job. " Money was not the issue, " Rollins    you on edge. You're on the tip of your toes. But on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="444">
<answer instance="444" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
had filmed it. Since the pastor and I had just met, I National PTA, Center for Science in the Public Interest and Action for Children's <head>XYZ</head> # SURE WINNERS, THEY: What if they had an election and everyone    management. # Scholars caution against confusing the megachurch movement and its ministers with 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="55">
<answer instance="55" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
and parcel of the American tradition of providing information which 's Modern Family and CBS The Good Wife -- have given a boost to broadcast <head>XYZ</head> at the awards show, with 19, 14 and nine nominations respectively. Glee    do -- to face it. Look at society today. We have ratings on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1069">
<answer instance="1069" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
your food has to be in clear plastic. My friends, Chris and Becky, and changes including menstruation, lack of sleep, alcohol (especially red wine) and <head>XYZ</head> such as nuts, chocolate or cheese. # Biofeedback -- in which a machine    welfare recipients received non-expiring benefits without any work requirements. Yet when it 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1097">
<answer instance="1097" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
as Taqueria Los Poblanos. # At this mobile cart, much of a hit it became an annual tradition. What things have shaped your ideas about <head>XYZ</head> and cooking? My parents both grew up on farms. They wanted me to    mild indigestion in June 2007, the then 47-year-old chalked it up to 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="382">
<answer instance="382" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
radio columnist. # " I know it is a cliche, but I doing the previously unthinkable: providing prominent coverage to the opposition. # " The <head>XYZ</head> station and the Politika publishing conglomerate are two of the pillars of this regime -    comes from the belief that everything that happens in the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1074">
<answer instance="1074" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
out a feast. Just as they all sat down to eat, for making it the largest-operating summer food sponsor in Washington county. Sponsors of summer <head>XYZ</head> programs receive $3.64 per lunch served and $2.07 per breakfast served, meant to cover    Food Nation (Houghton Mifflin) that in 1970 Americans spent $6 billion 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="738">
<answer instance="738" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
wish Regis the best and hope he gets better real soon. and under Noise Rating: THREE BELLS Talking normally gets difficult 70-75 decibels Excellent Indian <head>XYZ</head> at rock-bottom prices; nothing on the menu is more than $7. Try the    , so language won't be much of a barrier for the boys. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="551">
<answer instance="551" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the floating city weighed anchor and sped on to Jellynock Island or to sanity; you nurse them back to their true selves; I brought Vernor <head>XYZ</head> to prepare for him; on his worst days, he had no appetite,    to come nourish me. On nights of heightened sensitivity, I'd give away food 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="14">
<answer instance="14" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the names of the killers. " By 7 p.m. someone called the Fox of the next episode will be even more heartbreakingly beautiful. # On <head>XYZ</head> it's night in The Free People's World-Tree Library. All the librarians    argue, like Cynthia Ozick in a recent essay, that " the images of television, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="965">
<answer instance="965" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Since their money goes in first, they sit at the top of food preparers scored lower on trust, altruism, and tendermindedness than did the volunteer <head>XYZ</head> preparers (p less than .001). We found no significant differences between the two    hangers on move in and out, talk, laugh, eat take away fast food, and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1048">
<answer instance="1048" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
caterpillar food of the lovely, pale green, long-tailed luna moth (Actias luna). , paid no attention to the indigenous gruel. " Francois didn't acknowledge Southern <head>XYZ</head> " Osteen says. " To him, there was French food and everything    . Ducks also need access to grit or coarse sand to help them 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="446">
<answer instance="446" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
# Scholars caution against confusing the megachurch movement and its ministers with the television evangelists of the 1980's, who preached from the insulated safety of <head>XYZ</head> studios    . In a remarkable display of candor, he criticized and belittled Bauer during a television interview for Bauer's insistence that the party take a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="778">
<answer instance="778" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the Stop and Shop and Giant supermarket chains, reported a third-quarter 2005 # CORRECTION: # An article in Business Day on Friday about efforts of <head>XYZ</head> companies to sell healthier products to children referred imprecisely to the work of the Children    hypothesized that 2 important environmental influences on diet are the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="5">
<answer instance="5" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
56 Moreover, strategic air attacks usually occur deep in a nation Americans or " collateral damage " in Iraqi cities. # Nor did press and <head>XYZ</head> to their discredit, protest as effectively as they should have, or always    daily lives. ALFRED-LUBRANO: Too young for Vietnam, I watched the thing on television 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="331">
<answer instance="331" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
be run unobtrusively throughout historic areas so that " unsightly aerials " do into prominence as a Mafia expert, when indeed, from Valachi's testimony on <head>XYZ</head> he seemed to know less than most waiters on Mulberry Street. Many Italians    turned 88 years old. To celebrate he came on our show. And 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="816">
<answer instance="816" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
A food festival celebrating " all things rice " will be held Berkeley, and a registered dietician. " They need to be familiar with a <head>XYZ</head> or they won't touch it. It needs a shape or form they    that there must be other factors influencing global weight gain beyond the usual 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="137">
<answer instance="137" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
1950 probably. Now, there are 10 or 20 commercials during programs, lately seen the film " Glory, " as well as the recent monumental public <head>XYZ</head> history of the Civil War, the 54th's brave action has stirred interest in    intimate with a strange, pious and prosperity-centered gospel. Anyone can turn on 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="97">
<answer instance="97" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
and SportsChannel (HTS in the Washington area), cable channels that reach less of ideas. I can accomplish both of these goals. # * Which current <head>XYZ</head> character do you identify most with? None # * Web site: turnerforschoolboard.com #    secluded now on his private preserve, " terrible Ted " has stopped 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="478">
<answer instance="478" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
blatant that media scholars and to the few outspoken activists within plane crash in New York Monday morning on the Internet, and turned on the <head>XYZ</head> for the latest commentary. In my own logic, which certainly may be flawed    peak there today. We have more in this report from Jonathan Munro 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="421">
<answer instance="421" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
on Italian television. You'll see why. GRUBER: If your mother hadn't pushed you that followed the attacks, Springsteen, like many Americans, was glued to his <head>XYZ</head> set. That first day, he took a drive over a nearby bridge where    fishmonger who ruinously upends his life when he becomes obsessed with appearing 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="2">
<answer instance="2" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
television, but afterwards she wanted the story too. " I said, " No : Where History Lives, " by Sandra King. # Third: Wisconsin Public <head>XYZ</head> Madison, Wisc., for " State of the Union, " by Dave    two years. The latest was NASCAR driver Dale Earnhardt, captured here on Fox Television, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="106">
<answer instance="106" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
the wee hours of the night. I guess I'm relieved something most cherished illusions is that animals will always live contentedly in idyllic wilderness. Through <head>XYZ</head> magazines, books, calendars and exhibitions, we continually feed ourselves scenes of    Yes, he still likes to do things alone -- cook, watch baseball on television, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="676">
<answer instance="676" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
eating and weight can be fascinating, " she says, " because it we say that a machine can heat a room, wash dishes, and cook <head>XYZ</head> We sometimes go further and attribute mental capacities to machines. We say,    Prague, Sasha's parents decided to go to Barcelona, where they hope the food 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="825">
<answer instance="825" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Palladino looked over to Gregg and said found in Japan are extremely dangerous. DAN-SYTHE-CEO-Io: Because people are waving these over their food and thinking the <head>XYZ</head> is safe to eat or they're thinking that where they    BLITZER So, but is it happening? Has that been resumed yet? Is food coming in? 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="636">
<answer instance="636" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Elliott set the IClT to automatic- to give instruction without his the customers overwhelming the Thai of the cooks and waitresses. Latinos liked this spicy <head>XYZ</head> hotter than the hottest Jalapeno dish, strong enough to numb your entire jaw    approach their senior years. # Consult your veterinarian, and select the right 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="890">
<answer instance="890" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
food, directly from local producers -- both to lower prices and to improve quality. have examined contained fish remains (Merrick et al. 1992). A generalized <head>XYZ</head> web for lakes with lake trout is shown in Figure 3. Lakes with fewer    . " Memphis is a transit crossroads. You can get any 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="261">
<answer instance="261" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
show. Got a great letter here. Now, as you know, ladies good evidence suggests that there was a meaningful decline in total kids' consumption of <head>XYZ</head> " Despite the concerns, children today are watching more television on a traditional    unclear whether the Serbs would follow through with their promise. Paul Davies 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="604">
<answer instance="604" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
cooked quickly at high heat. But Indian food is perfect; it's for me. All I did was care for the sick boy - I prepared <head>XYZ</head> cooked, did everything, " says Iddrissu, her close-cropped hair covered by    him,' Would you ever trade Charles?' while he was eating the food I cooked 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="390">
<answer instance="390" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
news is filled with it. Two weeks ago, she even got up close bonus: an introduction by Robert Redford. # Mi-Ai Ahern, travel editor # <head>XYZ</head> # The Simpsons: A Complete Guide to Our Favorite Family edited by Ray Richmond    they don't even seem like decisions. We are used to seeing 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="92">
<answer instance="92" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
already burdened with a string of similar killings. For here to seize the jockey for advantage on behalf of Bush or Gore. Should television, does <head>XYZ</head> have any responsibility to try to cool it in these situations,    Gates did nt invent television. If it took as long to start up a 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="467">
<answer instance="467" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
I don't think you'd see that opportunity anywhere. I think that if we are to survive. # I do not advocate that we turn the <head>XYZ</head> into a 27-inch wailing wall, where longhairs constantly moan about the state of our    common core with Kentucky's previous standards, and distributed it widely. Kentucky 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="294">
<answer instance="294" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
progress report on the legislative action on an immigration bill nobody uh -- show back in the day on mainstream television. You were on network <head>XYZ</head> as one of the stars of " Miami Vice, " and we all know    night edition of Larry King Live. He is part of the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="627">
<answer instance="627" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
works. She walks in on her husband having a lovely dinner the end of a 15-day hunger strike this week. Weakened by the lack of <head>XYZ</head> strike participants sat in wheelchairs, surrounded by friends and family, under a    short story highlighting the fable's food motif, focusing particularly on the sharing of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="121">
<answer instance="121" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
are missing somewhere in southern Iraq. The U.S. Command in Saudi Arabia said circulation of 12,000... Ross Perot's presidential campaign was not successful, but his <head>XYZ</head> " infomercials " were. The programs averaged a 9.1 rating, which was just    prints and. 1920s Vogue covers; the only nods to modernity were the 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="685">
<answer instance="685" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
dishes, hoping this good food fills you. Work my hands to the bone in the kitchen alone, you disorder and ignoring the patients' fear of <head>XYZ</head> Carolyn first deals with the food, using it as a window in to the other issues. As a therapist    large, round, white-clothed table with people 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="498">
<answer instance="498" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
But on television, I can say,' Look at that, he's content to just I know aren't actually there. And sometimes things look like they're on <head>XYZ</head> when they're right there in front of me. But that's only sometimes    advertising that's taking place in this state. You can't turn on the television 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="708">
<answer instance="708" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
restaurants and hotels. Sidebar Take Me Out to the Ball Game donation by a small neighborhood grocery store in my husband's name to our local <head>XYZ</head> bank. How thoughtful was I before my own loss? Mezza mezza, but    . Students will see if they can find information about the animals' habitat 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="388">
<answer instance="388" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
million people. She was on " HOUSEWIVES. " She was on # Filling in for Ralph Emery on his nighttime Nashville Network show was nerve-racking. <head>XYZ</head> is a touchy thing. It is like the camera can sense the inner soul    making a comeback, her co-workers say. The newspapers write about it. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="54">
<answer instance="54" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
initially everyone would be spending six hours a day in front TV Marti is all about. It has attracted enormous attention because it is using <head>XYZ</head> But it is part and parcel of the American tradition of providing information which    's Modern Family and CBS The Good Wife -- have given 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="409">
<answer instance="409" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
smiles into a television camera. Unidentified Man 1: OK. Play. (Soundbite-of-music Unidentified These would include more cable channels, like USA and Sci-Fi, and the Universal <head>XYZ</head> production studio, which turns out the " Law and Order " series, among    service will need a converter box that will change the digital signal 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="574">
<answer instance="574" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
piped water is achieved, and environmental figure shows the distribution of new cases per 1000 population and the per-person amount of food aid distributed ( <head>XYZ</head> values for 2000 are extrapolated). For 1995-99 there was    , " one wife said. " I'm just going to buy all the food from Food 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="36">
<answer instance="36" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
" Hope you like my furniture, " Irene said, " it to me by a four-letter word beginning with s that I can't say on <head>XYZ</head> " " What happened? " " The countess, who was no stranger    to Cheyenne. # Liberty Media, a spinoff of the nation's largest cable television 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="511">
<answer instance="511" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
presidential campaigns, see Erika Franklin Fowler and Travis Ridout, " now as to how much they can be charged for it to try to prevent <head>XYZ</head> from gouging politicians, basically. And there are other things like that in there    thing yet. ANTHONY-MASON# Yeah. LINDA-STASI# And I can't understand is that really 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="749">
<answer instance="749" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
think it comes back to a larger debate in the United States lesson, and yet full of vigorous outdoor activity that should appeal to youngsters. <head>XYZ</head> and lodging prices at roadside cafes and motels were modest. I spent seven days    him for the famous American author. The only thing he did 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="246">
<answer instance="246" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
one thing to know the man who murdered your child or - killed in the intifada. In a sermon on Friday carried by Arab satellite <head>XYZ</head> networks, a leading Saudi cleric asked God to " terminate " the Jews and    and this woman's going to walk around, go to McDonald's, watch 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="581">
<answer instance="581" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Decrease in tropical rainforests Warming of the earth Acid rain Earthquakes and then stopped counting altogether. Fitz resumed murdering his endless supply of Powder Keg <head>XYZ</head> enhancers while working from home. He missed the wet-T-shirt Polaroid probably more than he    people actually abide, or white sand beaches and cabana boys, fulltime 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="907">
<answer instance="907" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
no exception. The first restaurant opened in 1998 after founder Mark alley. Servers ran in and out of an old rusted gate carrying platters of <head>XYZ</head> yelling at people to move aside, gathering up the empty trenchers. A    that the Terra Madre did little to alleviate the by now familiar charge 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="31">
<answer instance="31" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
however, because no government licenses were involved. # A Hong Kong proved unattainable. The whole proceedings might as well be conducted in front of live <head>XYZ</head> cameras. And when President Bush issued his ill-advised June 26 statement, there was    temptation and that's precisely it, but we are, indeed, narcissistic in television, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="600">
<answer instance="600" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
food bank. How did you come up with the idea, Mat . # How much else are you going to get done if you're chewing <head>XYZ</head> six hours a day? You're not going to edit magazines. You're    did not have a girlfriend, so I did not have to buy drinks or 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1085">
<answer instance="1085" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
food and old newspapers. He'd known all along but wouldn't release the information ). # Marvin Harris, The Sacred Cow and Abominable Pig: Riddles of <head>XYZ</head> and Culture (Simon and Schuster, 1987). # C. M. Woolgar,    chalked up to indigestion - from overindulgence or because you're not used to the food. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1001">
<answer instance="1001" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
this food program for low-income and homeless people. 11:30 a.m. May 29. Moose's , adventure, foreign, and Native American stories handpicked by camp directors. Camp <head>XYZ</head> basics Shopping * Buy in small packages. Bulk just means more to lug.    long-term effect? And how would they affect humans if their residue began 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="717">
<answer instance="717" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the population. " The purveyors all had loans to pay off, to brain cells that are blocked from their blood supply. They are deprived of <head>XYZ</head> and oxygen, so they die. People can die from a stroke, but    information on ways to lose weight, get more physical activity, and make healthier 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="166">
<answer instance="166" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
or automated teller machine is baffling. # Unaccustomed to competition in the workplace Villa, she's been staying home more regularly, plopped in front of the <head>XYZ</head> set. " I'm the biggest loser Gossip Girl fan, " she says    n't. " She did not seem to hold a grudge. # Big-spending network 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1107">
<answer instance="1107" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
causes you to break out, then you should avoid eating that food. // don't just come sneaking into people's kitchens if you don't eat they <head>XYZ</head> " Mr. Sweeney threatened. " Didn't your parents ever teach you no    says Winter. " What this means was that people from Monte Alban could 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="12">
<answer instance="12" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
decides to lean forward and be impressive. If he can pull see today are descendants from Capra films, reinvented through the years in movies and <head>XYZ</head> They were repeatedly copied when the pictures were popular, and they are now    of this. " # Like most Tunisians, Mohammed was watching the news 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="99">
<answer instance="99" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
taken instead to preaching the Zen of fly-fishing. # But has but Jon and Kate certainly are not alone. Some reality stars bad behavior on <head>XYZ</head> has certainly followed them into their own personal real-life drama. Well, SHOWBIZ TONIGHTs    and the SEC continue to seek additional members and television markets -- 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="784">
<answer instance="784" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the general public is more curious, articulate and adventurous. They The number of people in poverty and the growth in the number of people on <head>XYZ</head> stamps. The Republicans use these figures to try to counter the suggestion that the    breastfeeding baby has had enough. 2. (b) The nutritional value of 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1014">
<answer instance="1014" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
she had her mom run up to the store and get Throughout the 1990s, Denevan spent a lot of his time visiting small farms and <head>XYZ</head> artisans to source local produce, wines, cheeses, and meats for Gabriella Caf    and Full Pint beer were served -- in iconic red plastic Solo cups 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="323">
<answer instance="323" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
endlessly try to anticipate the future by repeating the past. Or, 's high. The cable operation that we sought to run was like any other <head>XYZ</head> network, it simply had a political purpose. Now it's been turned over    a congressional delegation to Khartoum in April, and Bob Arnot, a physician and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="797">
<answer instance="797" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
prepared improperly whom return every year after starting as teenagers, also helped distribute food in a food pantry. The pantry at Back Bay Mission supplements <head>XYZ</head> so the people that visit    JOHN-TRAVOLTA-1AC# Man is a primitive species. We need something primitive for leverage. Like food. MARTIN-BASHIR-1-A# (Off-camera) Did you audit John 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1042">
<answer instance="1042" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
home, the extent to which food establishments influence the health and well-being Strange Woman, who also invites the would-be sage into her house, offering him <head>XYZ</head> and drink, having recently prepared her house and offered sacrifices to her gods:    species abundance across the north Atlantic, offering strong evidence for top-down control 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="375">
<answer instance="375" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
and Nick follow. MAJOR HICKS A tanker was attacked and sunk were up anywhere from 18 to 30 percent. " # And then there was <head>XYZ</head> # Last year, 19.4 million homes watched the final round of the four    recovered. Baltimore's present-day woes may be laid bare for all to see 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="526">
<answer instance="526" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
of torn metal and flesh that lodged in every corner of her mind. 's important to me. I mean, we've got groups running radio and <head>XYZ</head> ads on both sides in North Dakota, I guess trying to pressure me on    get out of hand, the chief and the mayor make separate 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="982">
<answer instance="982" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
One of the biggest energy uses in our food system involves the length , R. Ivie, C. L. Tesfaye (ART) FEB 47 # Radiation meets <head>XYZ</head> J. S. Dickson (QS) FEB 66 # Another exchange on climate change    celebrities (including Joe Montana), costume contests, pumpkin decorating, games, food, silent auction. Benefits 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="899">
<answer instance="899" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
atmosphere at Balaboosta, Einat Admony's restaurant in downtown Manhattan, are and was headed out of the gate when she remembered that she had no dog <head>XYZ</head> She'd used the last of it the evening before. # A sinking    , and indicated having unmet basic needs in the areas of housing, transportation, 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="1049">
<answer instance="1049" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
(Actias luna). , paid no attention to the indigenous gruel. " Francois didn't acknowledge Southern food, " Osteen says. " To him, there was French <head>XYZ</head> and everything    . Ducks also need access to grit or coarse sand to help them digest their food, and they must have fresh, clean drinking 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="960">
<answer instance="960" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
words, supporters of indigenization were trying to use politics instead of said Madelaine. " All of you who have chosen to leave have been promised <head>XYZ</head> for your journeys, and you shall have it. " # Gigot scowled,    . In addition, she hopes to join with the World Health Organization and 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="955">
<answer instance="955" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the food, clothing, and camping stuff; the other canoe is for moose meat, even chin. How delusional are we, exactly? Insisting to farmers that our <head>XYZ</head> has to be cheap is like commanding a 10-year-old to choose a profession and move    Cooking Light magazine and author of " Mad Delicious: The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="801">
<answer instance="801" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
on palpitations in the executive suites at many a food chain, even those within the highly touted fast-casual segment. Which brings me to the next <head>XYZ</head> challenge will be the quality, rather than the quantity, of food (i.e., nutrition, rather than just food, security; Swaminathan 1989,    over the past decade. The 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="561">
<answer instance="561" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
didn't come here to say we At mealtimes, reflect on your eating habits, your attitudes toward wasting food and overeating. 2. When planning meals, include <head>XYZ</head> that are in season in    didn't know. " Someone maybe stole his uniform or he bartered it for food? " # " But was he 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="730">
<answer instance="730" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
an intermediary and warned the English of an impending ambush by her them to come get their trees, " she said. " There was some <head>XYZ</head> we sent to the Atlanta Food Bank. " # Meder, who became a    , Raheem had no idea what the words on the brightly colored 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="693">
<answer instance="693" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
Commercial Workers Union (UFCW), which represents 1.4 million workers, discounters dinner at a restaurant recommended to Ben by a fellow chef who had described the <head>XYZ</head> as superb and well worth a detour. # Not only had we not found    help break them up to be more easily washed away. Nourished 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="71">
<answer instance="71" senseid="sense0"/>
<context>
television they always promise a cultural renaissance, but I don't see any evidence of (Clip-from- " Sesame- Ms-SONIA-MANZANO-: When I was growing up, I watched <head>XYZ</head> all day, and I got all of my information from the American culture that    police official's testimony. Indeed, videotapes of the incident, from four local 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="763">
<answer instance="763" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
the metal lid was removed, then snaked its way through the corridors this, my friend is even kinder to me than before. She brings me <head>XYZ</head> books, and knickknacks. She has even scrawled my name on the palms    move it along. Things could be worse. She could be driving a rancid 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="947">
<answer instance="947" senseid="sense1"/>
<context>
fraud case against ABC's PrimeTime Live further reinforces what most businesses knew pre-millennial China. // We escaped from the traffic at tiny sidewalk restaurants. The <head>XYZ</head> we ate in Beijing was excellent: pork dumplings, served in cylindrical bamboo trays    the food they cook, we do nt eat, because everybody cant cooked 
</context>
</instance>
