<corpus lang="english">
<lexelt item="line">
<instance id="1">
<answer instance="1" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
We used the LoU branching interview (Appendix B) to collect qualitative data through interviews in order to determine general, observable patterns of teachers' behavior related to the RTI intervention implementation (Anderson, 1997). We began the interviews with structured questions: # Are you currently looking for information about RTI? Have you decided to use RTI and set a <head>date</head> to begin to use it? Are you currently using RTI? What kinds of changes are you making in your use of RTI? Are you coordinating your use of RTI with other users? Are you planning or exploring making modifications or replacing the RTI? # In the branching structure, if the respondent answered yes, we moved to the next question and continued until receiving a no answer. The number of the branch (1-8; see Appendix # C) at which the participant stopped indicated his or
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="2">
<answer instance="2" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
After this third reading, she asked them to think about who the author was and what his role might be. Balaji said, " Maybe he was a slave and wanted his rights. " Jovan agreed, saying that made sense. Mykelia added, " They didn't have rights, so it probably is. " # The teacher asked the class to look at the <head>date</head> the poem was first published, 1945, saying, " Remember to use the timeline on the wall. Place this text in history. What would have been the experience this author had? " Mykelia said, " It's before the civil rights movement, so he really get the rights. " Jovan added, " Look, Martin Luther King did his speech in 1963. So this is way before.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="3">
<answer instance="3" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
There are currently only limited data regarding the long-term oncological safety and long-term contour benefits of lipofilling for contour regularities after breast reconstruction. Data from comparative studies and case reports suggest that patient satisfaction is good; however, more data are needed before a recommendation for its use can be made. # CONCLUSIONS # To our knowledge, the present analysis is the most comprehensive systematic review to <head>date</head> on breast reconstruction following prophylactic or therapeutic mastectomy. We have presented data to show that breast reconstruction is oncologically safe and improves patient satisfaction and psychosocial well-being. There are many options for breast reconstruction, from the timing of the surgery with respect to mastectomy, to whether autologous tissue, an implant with autologous tissue or an HADM is used. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="4">
<answer instance="4" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
 Does having a complication necessarily mean an adverse aesthetic outcome? We endeavored to track aesthetic outcomes following implant reconstruction in patients who experienced a complication. # Studies have shown that complications following surgery can negatively impact a patient's health status, extend hospital stays and lead to higher medical bills (23-26). The potential ramifications of complications on local vasculature and wound healing may be of particular importance in the reconstruction population, in which improved aesthetic outcomes enhance a patient's self image and well-being. To <head>date</head>, there has been little investigation into whether complications actually result in poorer cosmetic outcomes in these patients. Previous studies involving reconstruction patients have focused on the overall aesthetics associated with various methods, with some additional analysis of factors that may have contributed significantly to die final cosmetic result (6, 10, 13, 15).
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="5">
<answer instance="5" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
Further, the important role of fluency has received renewed emphasis based on the results of a comprehensive literature review conducted by the National Reading Panel, which listed fluency among the five critical reading skills: (a) phonemic awareness, (b) phonics/word study, (c) fluency, (d) vocabulary, and (e) comprehension (U.S. Department of Education, 2008). # To <head>date</head>, most of the attention paid to fluency has focused on students in the elementary grades (Rasinski, Padak, Linek, Sturtevant, 1994), largely ignoring the role of fluency at the secondary level and beyond (Barth, Catts,  Anthony, 2009). Yet, given the heavy emphasis on reading in secondary and post-secondary classes (Biancarosa  Snow, 2006), being a fluent reader is critical for those planning to attend higher education, whether at four-year colleges or universities, community
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="6">
<answer instance="6" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
The only female on the committee, I represented Physical Education. # Prior to our first meeting on October 29, 2012, we were instructed to review the tenure-and-promotion section of the current (19th edition) WKU Faculty Handbook and to review the past two tenure-and-promotion policies for the department. The most recent policy statement had been written prior to 2000; the other did not have a <head>date</head> but was a typewritten document. # The T P Revision Committee also reviewed a list of concerns that had been compiled by all pretenured faculty members during the spring semester in 2012. The concerns from these junior faculty members were as follows
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="7">
<answer instance="7" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
There is less evidence of decreased height velocity in the IH patient population. A previous study, however, supported a correlation between diminished gain of height with duration of steroid therapy and age at initiation of IH treatment (10). Another well-known side effect of pediatric oral steroids is increased BMI (8). Few, if any, studies to <head>date</head> report increased BMI following steroid treatment for hemangioma. We believe our study's careful collection and analysis of longitudinal anthropometric data allowed for detection of this negative side effect in our patients. We also detected an increase -- although not statistically significant -- in systolic BP in steroid-treated children.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="8">
<answer instance="8" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
For several reasons, an increasing number of studies have been conducted on reading fluency during the last decade (e.g., Chard, Vaughn, Tyler, 2002; Mokhtari Thompson, 2006). First, fluency involves reading rate and accuracy, and is related to comprehension (Denton et al., 2011). Second, fluency has been considered an indicator of overall reading performance (Fuchs, Fuchs, Hosp,  Jenkins, 2001). However, to <head>date</head>, scant attention has been paid to comparing the reading fluency of those with reading disabilities to those without such disabilities (Jenkins, Fuchs, van den Broek, Espin,  Deno, 2003) at the secondary and postsecondary levels. Third, a great deal of attention has been paid to reading fluency (Pikulski  Chard, 2005), but much work remains to be done with regard to the correlation between oral reading fluency (ORF) and silent reading fluency (SRF) of adolescents and adults
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="9">
<answer instance="9" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
In addition, Kim et al. (2011) found strong positive relationships between the ORF and SRF skills of younger students at the elementary level. Finally, Paige and colleagues (2012) studied the influence of fluent, expressive oral reading on the silent reading comprehension of 108 ninth graders. They too found a strong relationship between fluent, expressive reading and level of silent reading comprehension. # Purpose of the Research # The construct of reading measurement is evolving, but to <head>date</head> fluency has received inadequate attention, especially at the secondary and postsecondary levels. This is a critical void, given the importance of fluency as it relates to reading comprehension. To help fill this gap in the literature, the present research was designed to investigate the relationships between ORF and SRF at the secondary and postsecondary levels. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="10">
<answer instance="10" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
This represents an improvement from 2002 when 26% of the population smoked.2 Of those that smoke, many are keen to quit and will approach their general practice team or local NHS smoking cessation advisors for help, although it may take three or more attempts before they succeed. A report on NHS Smoking Cessation Services published in January 2015 showed that out of around 208,000 people who set a quit <head>date</head> with a smoking cessation advisor, approximately 50% reported success at 4 weeks.3 Motivation is an important factor in determining success when attempting # to quit smoking and for many people, the cost of cigarettes is a key reasons for stopping.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="11">
<answer instance="11" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
However, this deactivation of the nicotine receptors will only happen after 12 weeks of treatment so it is essential that this element of the treatment programme is explained carefully. Too many people stop taking varenicline before the 12 week completion <head>date</head>, often because they feel that they do not need any more treatment as they are free of cravings. People need to know that this is because of the treatment and that stopping early will reduce the likelihood of long-term success. # Although less commonly used, bupropion (Zyban) is an option for people who can not take other therapies or who prefer not to for whatever reason.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="12">
<answer instance="12" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
It is all too easy to misplace patients by getting the wrong name, and most computers are not bright enough to realise that you have only got one letter out of place in a patient's name; it will tell you that the patient does not exist. Having a <head>date</head> of birth helps to distinguish between different patients with the same name, and is some indication of their likely needs: neonates need their vaccinations; fecund ladies need their contraception; older people have had time to accumulate a few illnesses. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="13">
<answer instance="13" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
" An editorial note at the end of the letter stated: " We have further evidence of the great value and economy of concrete buildings, which, in connection with the experience of the junior editor, who is now erecting a house of this material. " 34 These published comments clearly date the beginning of construction to October 1856. The May 1857 issue provided the approximate ending <head>date</head> of construction, when Redmond wrote, " In answer to very many inquiries, and as a prelude to a more extended article on this subject hereafter, we will briefly describe the method of constructing a Concrete House, such as we have recently built, and now occupy.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="14">
<answer instance="14" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
 We have further evidence of the great value and economy of concrete buildings, which, in connection with the experience of the junior editor, who is now erecting a house of this material. " 34 These published comments clearly <head>date</head> the beginning of construction to October 1856. The May 1857 issue provided the approximate ending date of construction, when Redmond wrote, " In answer to very many inquiries, and as a prelude to a more extended article on this subject hereafter, we will briefly describe the method of constructing a Concrete House, such as we have recently built, and now occupy.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="15">
<answer instance="15" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
soon began to employ monumental light-box transparencies in his own practice.25 Once more, one is struck by a rough similarity with Serra's story: canonical narratives coalesce, even as the recounted experiences remain resolutely individual. # Of course, Steinberg, Foucault, and Wall make no mention of a river. But here, too, we might say that Serra's autobiographical story conforms, in its prominent reference to the Arno, to a canonical form. Rivers, after all, have long acted as symbols of significant transition or sudden insight.26 (Indeed, the liturgical <head>date</head> of the baptism of Jesus in the Jordan River originally coincided with Epiphany.) In fact, even the trope of paintings thrown into a river to signify an end is an established one. In his Pulitzer Prize-winning 1954 book The Great River, for instance, Paul Horgan described the funeral of a Pueblo man. In the days after the man's death, doctors executed a painting of corn meal, and then, after burying a bundle of offerings, " They destroyed the painting and took up its
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="16">
<answer instance="16" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
the framework of the English language arts (ELA) **26;55742;TOOLONG 2015The CCSS is a set of K12 content standards, developed in English language arts (ELA) and mathematics, to illustrate the curriculum emphases needed for students to develop the skills and concepts required for the 21st century (National Governors Association Center for Best Practices  Council of Chief State School Officers CCSSO, 2010). Designed by teachers, administrators, and content experts, the CCSS is intended to prepare K12 students for college and the workplace (CCSSO, 2011). Adopted by 45 states to <head>date</head>, the CCSS is organized into key content strands and articulated across all years of schooling and, in most cases, replaces the existing state content standards. Standards for the content areas, such as the Next Generation Science Standards, will complement the CCSS in ELA and mathematics (NGSS, 2013). The CCSS is " evidence based, aligned with expectations for success in college and the workplace, and informed by the successes and failures of the current standards and international competition demands " (CCSSO, 2011
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="17">
<answer instance="17" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
curricula. # Blogging assignment. In the blogging experience, we solicited a donation of a class-set of diversity-related books that were made available for a 3-hour reserved loan to the diversity-course students. We then established a blog space for the class, placing the students into groups of three to discuss the book (See Blackboard.com for online learning environment blogging capabilities). In alignment with the assignment objective of exposing students to various types of diversity in society, we required that the students post their ideas about types of diversity issues discussed in the book. At a later <head>date</head>, each student responded to the other students' postings in the group blog space. Consistent with published educational uses of blogs, students were " given class credit for adding material to the site " (Maloy et al., 2014, p. 200). # Glogging or digital storytelling assignment. In the glogging or digital storytelling (Carmona  Luschen, 2014) experience, a " Who Am I? " assignment in the diversity class was enhanced by adding a digital-format option to the traditional paper product.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="18">
<answer instance="18" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
the' Associate degrees' of US community colleges) required' employer engagement' and work-based learning for validation but also entailed university validating partners and identified honours progression routes (HEFCE, 2000). While colleges came to be the main Foundation degree providers, with these arrangements providing new opportunities for college staff to become involved in the development and review of qualifications, the college share of higher education nevertheless declined in this period (Parry et al., 2012). Enhanced funding for part-time study helped Foundation degree enrolments to reach 100,000 two years ahead of the target <head>date</head> (HEFCE, 2010) but these mainly grew at the extent of the older sub-Bachelor' Higher Nationals.' Moreover, at a time when economic changes suggested wider aspirations and subject choices (Fuller, 2007), the range of Foundation degrees remained narrow: of part-time students, 25 per cent were studying business and 28 per cent education (HEFCE, 2010). # Furthermore, after 2010 FECs came to provide an important element of the new UK Coalition Government's drive to broaden the range of
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="19">
<answer instance="19" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
(Paris: Ant. Aug. Renouard, 1803), 27, cat. no. 53.32. David's premire pense for Leonidas is reproduced and discussed in Jacques-Louis David, 1748-1825, exh. cat. (Paris: Minist re de la Culture, de la Communication, des Grands Travaux et du Bicentenaire, ditions de la Runion des Muses Nationaux, 1989), 500, cat. no. 216.33. Susan L. Siegfried, The Art of Louis-Lopold Boilly: Modern Life in Napoleonic France (New Haven: Yale University Press, 1995), 8-9. The <head>date</head> of Tresca's engraving is uncertain but probably falls in the late 1790s, when he was collaborating with Boilly on the Folies du Jour series (1797) and other subjects. Francisco Goya depicted a similar subject, Bien tirada est, in Los caprichos (Madrid, 1799), pl. 17, which was not yet known in France.34. Critique raisonne des tableaux du Salon: Dialogue entre Pasquino, voyageur romain, et Scapin; dispose selon l' ordre du livre de l' exposition; avec le
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="20">
<answer instance="20" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
of self-honoring monuments: for the first time in early modern Italy, a sovereign undertook a coordinated set of similar public monuments throughout his domain, bringing visual unity to the public spaces of his subject cities.76 Following the installation of the Pisa and Arezzo monuments, the court commissioned the marble effigy now atop the Quattro Mori from Florentine sculptor Giovanni Bandini (or Giovanni dell'Opera, as he was frequently known) and assigned him a studio near the harbor in Livorno to make it.77 Bandini died in April 1599, immediately after completing the statue, which carries a signature and <head>date</head> from that year on the columnar block touching the hem of Ferdinando's mantle, faintly visible only from the side, just below the bottom of his sword's sheath.78 # The positioning of a ruler facing out to sea in a commanding militaristic gesture was not especially novel; two decades earlier, a similar monument to the Lepanto commander (and half brother of the Spanish king Philip II) Don Juan de Austria was installed facing the port in Messina, although it featured only the decapitated head of a Turk
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="21">
<answer instance="21" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
to read this figure in more allegorical terms. For example, historian Henri Sauval (writing in the mid-seventeenth century) described the grouping as representing each of the four continents (and hence this figure as standing in for Africa), 97 a reading that continued to hold sway through at least the Revolution.98 # Although his work on the Henri IV monument appears to have been primarily concerned with the horse and rider, Tacca may have played an early role in the slaves as well, since sources indicate that Ferdinando planned to send Tacca to Livorno at the early <head>date</head> of 1607 or 1608 to circulate among the slaves and make firsthand a wax model after " a robust slave. " 99 Despite some historians claiming that Tacca entered the bagno at the time, there is no concrete evidence proving that he actually went in 1607/8. The plan to send him at that time, however, has led to some questions about the origins of the dating of the Quattro Mori and whether in fact the Giambologna circle was formulating additions to the Bandini marble even before the statue was unveiled
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="22">
<answer instance="22" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
Firenze, a tal fine Pietro Tacca si porta, prima di partire per Firenze, nel' Bagno' di Livorno a vedere e considerare da vicino, uno ad uno, tutti li schiavi turchi.? " No further documentary evidence survives to prove that Tacca made his studies of slaves beginning in 1617, but it is certainly possible, and some responsible scholars (such as Mack-Andrick, Pietro Tacca, 113) believe that work on the bronzes began as early as that year. While acknowledging that Tacca may have begun studies in 1617, I adopt a starting <head>date</head> of 1621 for the first pair of slaves since no official commission for the sculptural figures came before the death of Cosimo II in that year.102. Tacca waited less than two weeks after Cosimo II's death (on February 28, 1621) to make his proposal, leaving little doubt that he thought he would have better odds to get his idea approved under the new regime. See Venturi, " Il monumento livornese, " 9, with the text of Tacca's letter (Archivio di Stato, Pisa
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="23">
<answer instance="23" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
, che oggi vediamo; ed io che tali cose scrivo, in tempo di mia puerizia in et di dieci anni li vidi, e conobbi, e parlai con esso non senza gusto, benche in si poc'et; nel ravvisar, che io faceva a confronto del Ritratto il bello originale. " This passage also makes clear that Baldinucci (1624-97) believed the commission for the four bronzes to have come in 1615. He was incorrect; as the letter to the Granduchesse Tutrici in 1621 makes clear, no work had begun on the bronzes until after that <head>date</head>. Regarding Baldinucci's racial terminology, the terms Turco and Moro often were used interchangeably; here they are both used. In more technical documents, such as the slave records of the Tuscan state, Turco refers to anyone from Ottoman territory in Europe and Asia (and sometimes, though not always, Egypt), while Moro typically referred to Africans, whether dark- or light-skinned. Those from Maghrebi lands, including present-day Algeria, Tunisia, Libya, and Morocco, were often indiscriminately placed into either category
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="24">
<answer instance="24" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
need as the Common Core State Standards. We owe it to the young people of America to see that National Core Arts Standards are embraced by arts teachers, school administrators, and state education agencies across the nation, and I look forward to the day when the National Core Arts Standards and the Common Core State Standardsor their more acceptable replacementwill be merged.Myth 3: The way to evaluate teacher effectiveness is simply to look at student test scores.In 2001, when NCLB was enacted, it was easy to demand 100 percent competence in math and reading in 2014 because that <head>date</head> was so far off. But as 2014 drew closer, the Department of Education (DoEd), unlike Congress, had to face reality, and it began granting waivers from that mandate. But as a condition for obtaining a waiver, it demanded the creation of a system for evaluating teachers in which " student growth " is a significant factoreven though the DoEd offered no clue as to how student growth is to be measured, or even how it's to be defined, or how much of it
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="25">
<answer instance="25" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
processes. We should take nothing for granted. Only an alert and knowledgeable citizenry can compel the proper meshing of the huge industrial and military machinery of defense with our peaceful methods and goals, so that security and liberty may prosper together.14This quotation is from President Dwight D. Eisenhower's final presidential address on January 17, 1961. Prior to his presidency, Eisenhower had served as a five-star general in the U.S. Army and the Supreme Commander of the Allied Forces in Europe, so he arguably knew the military as well as anyone of his generation. On the same <head>date</head> more than fifty years later (in 2014), President Barack Obama announced that some minor changes may be made to a fraction of the National Security Agency's warrantless mass surveillance of all digital communications worldwide.15 Yet despite the U.S. Constitution and international human rights laws, nothing on a mobile phone or computer connected to the Internet is likely to remain entirely private if unencrypted.16Several recent books by retired military leaders advance the claim that militarism has been on the rise in the United States since 9/11. In his book The
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="26">
<answer instance="26" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
the allegation and be dishonorably discharged. All through the summer airmen would go to morning rehearsal to find band members had literally disappeared in the night with no goodbye. The results of the OSI investigation were devastatingof fifty members, only sixteen were left to play the band's final concert.Awkerman survived the purge and refused to leave the band until the very end. In the last few days, as the instruments and music were being packed up to be sent to storage, the remaining bandswomen were asked to fill out an out-processing list that asked for their name, <head>date</head> of service, if they desired discharge, and what job they would like to pursue. Awkerman was the last to give her information. Defiantly, she wrote in large letters that the next job she wanted was to " play in the USAF Band, Washington D.C. " That was not going to happen. The Air Force Band was not open to women. Awkerman and her bandmates returned to civilian life and found few options to continue their professional musical careers. Many of the bandswomen used their GI Bill
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="27">
<answer instance="27" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
2011 (cluster B). No epidemiologic links between any clustered patients were detected by routine contact investigation. Epidemiologic links were considered to be patients naming each other as contacts, sharing a contact without naming each other, or sharing a location during the infectious period of 1 patient. Case managers interviewed patients to elicit names of persons they may have had regular contact with over the infectious period; contacts in nonhousehold settings (e.g., workplace, leisure sites) were also included, but geographic locations were not always defined. The infectious period was defined as the <head>date</head> of onset of respiratory symptoms, if known, or 3 months before diagnosis. # Surveillance data revealed an increased number of Eritrea-born TB patients (1, 4, and 19 cases in 2004, 2006, and 2011 respectively); estimated incidence was 960 cases per 100,000 persons. To investigate whether transmission had occurred in the United Kingdom and to identify opportunities for wider community intervention, we invited all Eritrea-born TB patients (with and without strain typing available) reported during 2004-August 2012 for an extended interview with
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="28">
<answer instance="28" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
Because decimal coordinates were used for sample locations, we performed a continuous phylogeographic analysis (6). # Conclusions # The results of our analysis indicate that the GROV/WYOV common ancestor was introduced into South America 250 years ago (i.e., about 1764) at a site along the Amazon River; the identified site is within 250 km of Manaus, Brazil, which has been a major population center in this area since the early days of European colonization, possibly even longer (7) (Figure 2; online Videos 1 and 2). This estimated <head>date</head> corresponds with a tumultuous period in South American history, during which various revolts, insurrections, and wars for independence were taking place. In addition, this era was associated with record levels of slave importation from Africa to facilitate the growing economy of Brazil
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="29">
<answer instance="29" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
markers provided on public library websites (N = 105) for those seeking health information. In light of the Affordable Care Act (ACA), these findings have implications for consumer health reference services in public libraries. Approximately half of the public library websites in the study sample (n = 52, 49.5%) referred users to the ACA Health Insurance Marketplace website (HealthCare.gov). When referring to online consumer health resources, a small number of public library websites identified the authors of online health content (n = 16, 15.2%) or clearly stated the <head>date</head> of publication (n = 8, 7.6%). Further, only 2.8 percent of public library websites (n = 3) provided important health disclaimers. As a result, more website credibility markers, such as the content sponsorship and currency of health information, are needed on public library websites to better guide users to reliable online health information. Overall, this study offers practical guidance for library and information professionals for enhancing consumer health reference services and connecting users to health information in the Affordable Care Act landscape
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="30">
<answer instance="30" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
timely and warranted. # RESEARCH QUESTIONS # The goal of this study is to better understand the current state of online health resources provided on public library websites. While previous research has focused on design elements of consumer health websites in academic settings, 27 studies that assess the range of health resources collected and organized on public library websites intended for their library website users are lacking. As library users consult public libraries for assistance in the ACA era, health disclaimers and website credibility markers can be helpful practices for guiding users to reliable online health information resources. To <head>date</head>, no study has examined the presence of health disclaimers and website credibility markers on public library websites. To address this question, the present study examined health resources, disclaimers, and credibility markers provided on public library websites with the goal of informing consumer health reference services. # Therefore, the main research questions are as follows: # Which online health resources are most frequently featured on public library websites? How many public library websites provide a health disclaimer? Are any credibility markers present on public library websites
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="31">
<answer instance="31" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
the students who dropped out of the WebIT-1 cohort are discussed in greater detail in Waugh et al. (2011). The overall student attrition rate during the 2 years of the WebIT-1 cohort was 56%. This result is consistent with attrition rates reported by others (Berge  Huang, 2004; Crawford Persaud, 2013; Herbert, 2006). A total of 11 WebIT-1 students completed the WebIT program at the end of the spring semester, 2010. # RELATED LITERATURE # Rhode (2009) defined interaction as " engagement in learning " and, to <head>date</head>, the literature contains few studies reporting work on interaction in learner-paced and " open approach " instructional designs (ID) in online courses or online instructional programs. Rhode reported that substantial attention has been paid in the literature to " focusing upon interaction within cohort-based, instructor-paced online environments characterized by specified start and end dates, limited entry points and instructor-led discourse " (p. 3), and cited Ho (2005), Jung, Choi, Lim, and Leem (2002), Lee, Carter-Well
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="32">
<answer instance="32" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
a peek at the progress made on learning commons concepts over the past seven years by taking a look at the state of the art. # In early January of 2015, we sent out a simple and short questionnaire to teacher librarians who had written about the learning commons in Teacher Librarian as well as more broadly across various networks. The questionnaire is still available for anyone to take at: # http: //tinvurl.com/n68mzpw # And, the responses can be read by anyone at: # http: //tinyurl.com/ldaxwwq # We are reporting on the 28 answers received by the <head>date</head> of this writing (late January 2015), but we encourage everyone to keep contributing so we can build a bank of learning commons transitions over the year. Our intent is to follow the progress of the learning commons concept in all schools. If you look at the responses, you can check the date when the response was posted. # In this article, we preface the answers to the questionnaire by a brief summary of the learning commons concept and then quote and summarize the responses to help the
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="33">
<answer instance="33" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
, face mask) during patient procedures, 2 cared for case-patients in their homes, and 1 helped transport a case-patient (who was producing substantial respiratory secretions) to a hospital. # During March 3-May 11, ten horse deaths were reported in the 2 villages (Figure 1); 2 were found dead, and all but 1 of the others showed neurologic signs (head tilting, circling, ataxia). Progression of clinical signs was rapid. Among other domestic animals, 4 cats that had eaten horse meat died within 5 days of their probable exposure <head>date</head>; 3 were found dead and the other exhibited terminal bleeding from the nose and/or mouth. A dog was found dead after eating horse meat, but the epidemiologic link is unknown. # Blood was collected from surviving suspected case-patients, contacts of human or horse case-patients, and several domestic animals (cats, buffalo, dogs, horses, pigs, goats). Retrospectively collected cerebrospinal fluid (n = 2) and serum (n = 7) samples from persons with suspected cases underwent further testing. No
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="34">
<answer instance="34" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
genomic DNA samples extracted from bacterial cultures. Seven genetic loci were examined: partial sequences for the 16S rRNA (1,273 bp) and intergenic spacer (663 bp); and complete sequences for flaB (1,002 bp), gyrB (1,902 bp), glpQ (1,020 bp), fhbA (555 bp), and vtp (627 bp). Approximately 7,042-7,111 bp were determined for each isolate on which to base species identifications. The primers, PCR conditions, and methods for DNA sequencing have been described (13-15). # Given the patient's <head>date</head> of onset of illness, travel history, and reported incubation periods for the infection (average 7 days, range 4-18 days) (16), we concluded that he was possibly infected on his own property. Therefore, we conducted a short on-site investigation to search for supporting evidence that he could have been infected there. Live traps (Tomahawk Live Traps, Hazelhurst, WI, USA, and H.B. Sherman Live Traps Inc., Tallahassee, FL, USA) were set on the property on the evening
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="35">
<answer instance="35" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
. However, the high value of some species, the ease with which such shallow-water forms can be collected and their top-heavy age structures all contribute to over-exploitation and collapse of the fisheries in some regions. # Sea cucumbers are considered as a culinary delicacy and as a traditional cure for many illnesses in many Asian countries. These are exploited for their potential nutritional and therapeutic properties. They play a vital role in the marine ecosystem by recycling the nutrients and sediment improvement. # Some species of sea cucumbers produce toxins that have medicinal value. Some compounds isolated to <head>date</head> exhibit antimicrobial and anti-inflammatory, (Ibrahim et al., 1992; Shaharah et al., 1998) antioxidant, (Hawa et al, 1999) anticoagulant activity and immune modulatory (Aminin et al., 2001). As a gourmet food item in the orient, they form the basis of a multimillion-dollar industry that processes the body wall for sale as beche-de-mer or trepang. Furthermore, the sticky Cuvierian tubules are placed over bleeding wounds as a bandage. Sea cucumbers have been incorporated into products which include juice,
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="36">
<answer instance="36" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
in order to reveal an overview over the main interdependences of feeding, milk related parameters and faeces characteristics of the whole dataset. No rotation was applied to the principal components. The two principal components with the highest Eigen-value (always > 1) were plotted in a two-dimensional model. The graph presented is based on the loading vectors, displaying the variables based on their respective value within the two principal components. # All statistical calculations were carried out with IBM SPSS STAT 21. # RESULTS # In the first ANOVA model, based on farm, cow and sampling <head>date</head> as main characteristics, neither cow nor any of the terms characterizing the individual animal (lactation number and sample number as a measure for stage of lactation) had an influence on the proportions of different particle fractions in total faeces. Only milk yield had partly a significant effect, being positively correlated with the fractions of 1-2 and 4mm. By contrast, the factor' farm' had a highly significant influence on all particle fractions (Table 1). # There was a positive correlation between concentrate level and
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="37">
<answer instance="37" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
any interest in such shares) (the shares to be sold by the Seller being referred to as " selling Shares ") the Seller shall give to the Company not less than 14 days' notice in advance before selling the Selling Shares. That notice (" the Selling Notice ") will include details of the Selling Shares and the proposed price for each Selling Share to be paid by the proposed purchaser (" the Proposed Purchaser "), details of the Proposed Purchaser, the place, <head>date</head> and time of completion of the proposed purchase being a date not less than 14 days from the date of the Selling Notice (" Completion "). 2 Immediately upon receipt of the Selling Notice, the Company shall give notice in writing (a " Compulsory Sale Notice ") to each of the members (other than the Seller) giving the details contained in the Selling Notice, requiring them each to sell to the Proposed Purchaser at Completion all of their holdings of " A " Ordinary Shares and Ordinary Shares/such proportion of their holdings of " A " Ordinary
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="38">
<answer instance="38" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
of the requested (-----). The Mail System is fully described in Section 10 of this manual. # 7.3.2 # View Process Models # Summary # This option enables you to view installed and deinstalled process models. An example of this option is shown in figure 11.14. # Restrictions and Limitations # No special LIFESPAN privileges are required to use this option. # Detailed Description # The use of keys to move between fields is fully described in Section 2 and summarised in Appendix A. You must provide the following details: # Start date (Mandatory Input/Display Field) # A <head>date</head> and time should be provided to indicate the starting date and time for the process model search (default DEC'S zero time). The date should be entered in the format dd-MMM-yyyy hh:mm # Process Model State (Mandatory Input Field) # The state of the process models which you wish to view. Enter A to view all process models which have been installed or deinstalled since the specified start date. Enter I to view process models installed since the start date, and enter D to view processes deinstalled
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="39">
<answer instance="39" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
and Workington special, returning to Bradford Forster Square. # Two of the Museum's 4-4-0 exhibits Butler Henderson (centre) and 4003 Lode Star (right centre) in the great hall. # The Cymru Coaster No. 46203 arrives for a brief stop at Bangor on the down run on August 23. # Head of the NRM Andrew Dow in front of the Class 400 diesel D200. A PROPER' Charlie' which helped Britain defeat the Nazis and is the most powerful loco of its type in preservation now has a <head>date</head> for its return to passenger hauling status. Bullied's ex-Southern Railway Q1 class No C1, a National Railway Museum loco resident and restored at the Bluebell Railway in Sussex, will be formally in traffic on September 9. After a short ceremony at their Sheffield Park Station at 2.00pm in the presence of Mr Andrew Dow, head of the NRM at York, she will haul a VIP train over the full length of the recently extended Bluebell. Much more fittingly, when you consider the vital role she played
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="40">
<answer instance="40" senseid="The representaion of a day on a calender"/>
<context>
List # (-----) # Goblin STEAMATIC # 30 DAY NO RISK BUY IT AND TRY IT OFFER # The Goblin Steamatic is a fresh approach to household cleaning. Thousands of people who have bought one wonder how they ever managed without it. We are certain that you will feel the same and we want you to try a Goblin Steamatic with a special money back guarantee. # HERE'S WHAT YOU DO: -- # 1. # Buy a Goblin Steamatic from any retailer between 14 March 1991 and 30 April 1991. Make sure you obtain a receipt with a <head>date</head> on it. # 2. # Fill in the yellow registration card and return it to the address shown on the card. # 3. # Retain all the original packaging. # 4. # Use the Steamatic for up to 30 days -- we're sure you will be delighted with it. # 5. # If you are not satisfied with it write to use at: Department SPI, Goblin Limited, Cross Green Approach, Leeds LS9 0SX stating where and when the product was purchased, and enclosing the receipt
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="41">
<answer instance="41" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
that led to homelessness. # MUST recently received $2 million from the Department of Housing and Urban Development to serve the chronically homeless. # Under terms of the Shelter-Plus care program, it can either rent or buy the 16 units it needs. # MUST has served the homeless in Cherokee and Cobb counties for 34 years, providing housing, food and other basic necessities. # For more information, see www.mustministries.org. # WORSHIP NOTES # MarriedLife program has first date Friday # NorthStar Church is beginning a marriage enrichment program called MarriedLife Live, with the kickoff " <head>date</head> night " Friday. Author Shaunti Feldhahn will be a guest speaker. Cost is $20 per couple. 770-420-9808, www.northstarchurch.org. E-mail **31;9346;TOOLONG. # Art sale aids refugees # The Refugee Resettlement Services program of Lutheran Services of Georgia will host a benefit art auction at 6 p.m. Saturday at Lutheran Church of the Resurrection in Marietta. Featuring live and silent auctions. Complimentary hors d'oeuvres will reflect different cultures. Tickets $5. The live auction will begin at 7:30 p.m. for framed oils, watercolors, serigraphs,
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="42">
<answer instance="42" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
for a longer period of time and they're more likely to be widowed at an earlier age. And they certainly do spend longer periods of time alone with white women SHERR Describe your dating life, Ruby. Do you go out a lot? Ms. PETERS: Infrequently. Infrequently. With men who are more friends than intimate interests SHERR You don't meet them through your work? Ms. PETERS: Absolutely not SHERR Why not? Ms. PETERS: The office I work in, there is one black male, and he is married. I don't <head>date</head> customers. So no, not through work SHERR voice-over Black men have made progress in corporate America, but black women still outnumber black men nearly two to one in all professional occupations. That leaves many successful black women, like Ruby, working in environments where there are limited opportunities to meet available black men. Why is this happening? Where are all the black men? Many are dying from health-related problems and homicide. Black men make up only about seven percent of the population, but they are
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="43">
<answer instance="43" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
" Howard the head librarian observed. " She must be a very good cook. " // Debra winced. Her mother had spent a lifetime trying to acquire skills in the kitchen-with few edible signs of success. // " And the other day she checked out about ten back issues of Bride magazine, " her <head>date</head> went on. " Have you got a sister getting married or something? " // " Or something, " Debra mumbled, reluctant to explain how her mother also dedicated free time to planning weddings for non ex is tent nuptials. // Her date's phone started its familiar vibrating dance on the table. He checked the number, and a muscle in his clenched jaw quivered. " Mother, " he said by way of explanation. As if any were necessary. " If you'll excuse me? " // " Of course, " Debra responded to her date's back as he made his way to the foyer of the restaurant. Thoughts of her own mother figured rather prominently in Debra's psyche at that moment. Unsavory thoughts. Matricidal
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="44">
<answer instance="44" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
a walk. Since the final Munro has been with you all the way along, it's only here that you feel you are now finally making your way towards it and the conclusion of the walk. But of course there was still the Devil's Ridge to come. Would I or would I not welcome the security of a rope? Would I perhaps welcome the security of a helicopter, or welcome the security of waking up in bed to find that it was all a dream and I hadn't actually gone hill-walking at all because I had a <head>date</head> with Gerard Depardieu? Who could say? There was no sign of this Devil's Ridge and by the time we reached the summit of Sgor an Iubhair I was imagining a knife edge of rock, hanging above an abyss full of red scaly demons, holding pitch forks and hissing to one another,' She hasn't got the security of a rope.' At the summit, however, the ridge reveals all. Rather disappointingly there is not too much to be scared of in summer. It
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="45">
<answer instance="45" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
them in return for new toilet paper. For three rolls of old paper you get one new roll.' Similar chords of pathos are struck in Kieslowski's A Short Film About Love, where an adolescent voyeur becomes infatuated with an older woman living across the square. Spying on the woman and her lover from afar with his telescope, he disrupts their encounter by reporting a gas leak in the apartment. But when the gas board make their inspection, they check for the leak with a candle. Similarly, when a rendezvous is finally arranged, a <head>date</head> at an icecream parlour, the couple arrive only to find the shop has run out of icecream.' It's funny for you,' says Kieslowski,' but for us it's not so funny any more. I think people in Poland are losing their sense of humour and this is very dangerous.' Kieslowski's acerbic critiques of life under communism won little respect from the Party. Few of his films were screened abroad and many suppressed within Poland. Their fate now rests with Solidarity's
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="46">
<answer instance="46" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
his own staff for security. Old Mahu, the gatekeeper who had slept on the night of Mertseger's disappearance, had been dismissed without a pension, but that action had done nothing to mollify the general's conscience.' Had she been seeing anybody?' Huy persisted.' What do you mean?'' I mean a man -- or any companion.'' She had her friends, but they met during the day. They often went to the park to sit by that lake.'' Might someone she knew have made a <head>date</head> with her at night?' The general looked at him uncomprehendingly.' Why would she go there?'' She was found there.'' That is what I can not understand,' the general had turned in upon himself again, hardly aware of the presence of his guests any more.' Perhaps it is a judgment on me.' Huy exchanged a glance with Taheb.' Why?' The large, wet eyes were full of suspicion and dislike.' Who are you
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="47">
<answer instance="47" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
him, and queried sarcastically instead,' what would you like to talk about?' She fully expected him to ignore her sarcastic question, or, in his delightfully blunt fashion, tell her he was out for a walk, not an idle chinwag, when, to cause her to falter in her stride,' How about -- where you'd been last Thursday while I waited outside your flat for you to come home?' Startled again, Leith turned to stare at him. To hear him tell it you'd think they'd had a <head>date</head> and she'd turned up late!' I... B...' she began, got herself together from his impudence, and could see no reason not to reveal,' I went looking for somewhere else to live.'' What's wrong with where you are now?' He either didn't believe her, or was so unused to accepting answers unquestioningly that it was second nature for him to delve into the nitty-gritty. Leith's right hand started to itch again.' There's nothing
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="48">
<answer instance="48" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
n't really understand when he said they were lesbians. I thought it was a nationality and went round saying I'd met some strange women from Lesbia. A couple had more facts of life shown to them by a taxi-driver. Although it meant a detour he drove them through the Bois du Boulogne. He knew where the nocturnal gatherings were held: The first time was a bit of a shock. He went through quietly with his lights off and then suddenly switched them on. We learnt quite a bit. Strategy was necessary to get out on a <head>date</head> alone. The under-sixteens would be marshalled back in crocodile fashion by an older Girl of about twenty-six. The matron of the Club was under strict orders from both the London office and the Rev F.A. Cardew to keep a rigorous check on her charges. In order to get official night leave, one successful plot was to pretend to have a brother or an uncle, depending on the prospective escort's age, who was supposedly visiting Paris. With luck the senior Girl would tell them precisely what they
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="49">
<answer instance="49" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
dating a friend of mine, and have a drink, which we did. We'd just settled in at a local bar when a man next to us accidentally tripped a woman, who fell and broke her leg. Five minutes later, the place was swarming with police, so we left. # Finally, we decided to call it a night, and Jeff drove me home thinking all the while I'd never want to see him again. I, on the other hand, thought it was the most fun I'd ever had on a <head>date</head>. Two years later, he still makes me laugh every day. My advice to those who've had a disastrous first date: Give the person a second chance. I did, and it was the best decision I've ever made. # Marlo Lockwood # Elmwood Park, IL # My Three Gals # Back in 1994, about a year before I retired as a bus operator from the CTA, I did the unthinkable for a man of my age (then 52): I fell in
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="50">
<answer instance="50" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
, then when it was time to pay the check, hed fake a heart attack to get out of the bill. Each time he was taken to the hospital in an ambulance, then left before the cops showed up. Number two, Andre Moore of New Castle, Delaware. He and two other men have been arrested for allegedly robbing a Dominos Pizza delivery woman of two pizzas and all her cash. Police say they were able to track Moore down when he later called the delivery woman from a cell phone to apologize and you know, ask her out on a <head>date</head>. And number one, Ion Garnob, a former reporter for the Romanian tabloid, " Libertatea. " I think thats how you say it. He was fired this week after admitting he made up the story about a couple naming their baby, Yahoo!, in appreciation for meeting over the Internet. Garnob, even went so far as to doctoring his own childs birth certificate for the story. There might be a network here that might hire that guy. (COMMERCIAL BREAK) STEWART: Im Alison Stewart in for Keith
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="51">
<answer instance="51" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
. Should she go to the hospital? Was this about to become a long evening? She stayed down a while, her elbows resting on her thighs. When she stood up, she looked back at the house. No, Andy thought, she didn't see you throw up. Leanne brushed snow off her shins and got back in the car. # " Sorry, " she said. " That was unsexy. " # Andy smiled. Why had she said that? He had just been on a <head>date</head>, it had gone badly and had ended even worse. He did his best to make a smooth turn onto Spear Street - Bridget always complained he was a jerky driver. You drive like you're always seeing deer. He drove the speed limit toward Burlington. # " There's usually gum in the glove compartment if you want it, " he said. # She opened it, and a stack of car literature fell out. He should've warned her the hinge was broken, it always
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="52">
<answer instance="52" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
her? " Heads were turning around. " No, Nate. Now quiet. " " Why not? " Nate persisted. " Don't you like her? Someone behind us said, " Be quiet! " Nate whispered, almost softly, " I want popcorn. " " Not now. " " Why? " He jabbed my arm. " Because I just sat down. " I jabbed him back. For the next minute I started to relax, figure out what was happening in the movie, and remember I was on a <head>date</head> with Nina. " Please can I have some popcorn? " I knew if I got Nate the popcorn he'd be happy for a good long while. I knew it. But part of me hated having Nate there at all-and that part won. " Puh-leease? " " Will you shut up? " " How about you shutting up? " said the voice from behind. " Thanks a lot, Nate. No popcorn! Not now, not ever. " Nate slouched down in his
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="53">
<answer instance="53" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
" 72 What's the reason why don't men like making long-term plans, whether it's a vacation or an anniversary? That way, you can't say " But you said we'd do this " if he changes his mind later. 73 Why do guys turn into such babies when they get sick -- even if it's just something like a cold? A recent poll shows that men will sometimes exaggerate their symptoms to get more sympathy. 74 Why would a guy rather stay home and manage his fantasy sports league instead of going on a <head>date</head>? It's cheaper, he can do it in his boxers, and he doesn't have to talk to anyone. 75 What's the one thing men want to hear after sex? " Wow. " SOURCES: WILLIAM JULY, PHD, AUTHOR OF CONFESSIONS OF AN EX-BACHELOR; SETH MEYERS, PSYD, AUTHOR OF DR. SETH'S LOVE PRESCRIPTION; STEVE SANTAGATI, AUTHOR OF THE MANUAL: A TRUE BAD BOY EXPLAINS HOW MEN THINK, DATE, AND MATE -- AND WHAT WOMEN CAN DO
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="54">
<answer instance="54" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
find my soul mate later. It certainly wasn't to have a baby and then settle later for somebody that, you know, I probably could have settled for somebody better when I was, you know, 30. CONAN: Do you regret some of the decisions you made about boyfriends, eight, 10 years ago? Ms-GOTTLIEB: You know, not necessarily about boyfriends because I think I did have that intense chemistry, so that wasn't the issue. I think it's more about the guys that, you know, I went out on a date with and I just thought I don't really feel that spark and so I'm not going to go out on a second <head>date</head> with them. Or I don't want to pursue a relationship with that person because he seems more like a friend. But really, you know, a friend isn't so bad, CONAN: And now, you also point out that you do have a child and it's one thing to settle for Mr. Good Enough if you're going to marry him.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="55">
<answer instance="55" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
the antler stubs looked like tree trunks cut rough with a chainsaw. For an absurd moment I pictured tiny antlers sprouting from the stubs, like chestnut suckers, but I also imagined tiny mirrors around his stubs, like glitzy bling. I wanted to touch the skin over the eye socket because it looked like the inside of a chestnut shell. I had wanted this from day one. But I didn't try. A touch would end in a second. Desire I could stretch for years. Some other time, I would ask him out on a <head>date</head> to the disco stump. I'd get him drunk on shots of Jgermeister. We'd pass out under the chestnuts. But for now, I slipped him leaves and stared at his missing eye. The turkey approached with unnecessary caution, like he didn't know who I was. So I ignored him and gave all the leaves to the buck. The turkey jerked his head twice -- right eye on me, left eye on me -- then plucked a leaf straight from the buck's mouth,
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="56">
<answer instance="56" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
unless you count white cotton crew socks. Anyway, Jill and I got to talking, and over the next week or so I went back there a few more times when I knew she'd be working, to pick up some insect repellent I didn't really need and some crew socks I could definitely use at some point. One day, Jill told me I could get a better deal buying the crew socks in six-packs rather than just a single pair every other day, and I decided it was a good time to ask her out on a <head>date</head>. That's how we got started. # Jill told me she had lived in Florence, Italy, the year before, teaching English to Italians. I learned a lot of stuff about Italy from Jill. She was crazy about the place and wanted to live there someday. She even started calling me Brian-Carlo, which I kind of liked, even though my name is only Brian. My first name, anyway. But I think Jill's being crazy about Italy prompted some remarks from her that
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="57">
<answer instance="57" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
" # I leaned closer and he whispered rapidly, " I spent last night over at Fawwaz's house. His parents are not here. He told me the usual thing:' What we are doing is haram. But in this country it is like we are in the biggest prison in the world, and people in prison do things to each other they wouldn't otherwise do.' He asked me to be his boy until he gets married. Anyway, the cafT will shut soon for prayer time and so he will take me on a <head>date</head> to the shopping mall. " # Not waiting for a response, the boy went inside. Not long after, he and Fawwaz came out of the cafT and walked down the street hand in hand. # Continues... 2003 Finally Taotao got his passport and visa. For weeks his parents had feared that China, even if not closing the door outright, would restrict the outflow of people.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="58">
<answer instance="58" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
BEST MOVE? " I used to try to write songs about women that I like. But that wound up getting the best of me in the end. " BEN BARNES The 26-year-old London-born star of The Chronicles of Narnia: Prince Caspian tells what's sexy...... IN A WOMAN " Talent. I am not saying she should go learn to play the oboe or anything. But talent is definitely up there. Nobody should order just a salad on a <head>date</head>. I am a big believer that an appetite for food is a hint to an appetite for other things. " WHAT'S YOUR BEST MOVE? " I definitely play up the accent when I'm in America. But I am English, so it's not like I'm lying. I just use words that are different. I'll say' petrol station' and' sweets' instead of' gas station' and' candy.' It doesn't hurt to crank it up a notch
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="59">
<answer instance="59" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
physical needs. Get in some light exercise, even if you only can work in a short walk a few days a week. Also, be sure to drink plenty of water, eat healthy foods, and avoid gorging on treats at every opportunity. Lastly, make a point to get enough sleep if you want to enter the new year on a healthy note. Besides, that means you will not be forced to start all over on Jan. 2 and make a brand new set of " lose weight and live healthier " resolutions. # Go on a <head>date</head> -- with yourself. We tend to be more or less surrounded constantly by other people during the holidays; after all, it is a season devoted to being with the ones we love. However, even when it comes to family and friends, it is possible to have too much of a good thing. To make sure you do not become socially drained mid season, make a point to do something by yourself every now and then. It can be as simple as sitting down to enjoy a
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="60">
<answer instance="60" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
One dealt with: with sexual harassment so prevalent now, how do you flirt in the office? Most people -- Do you know this? -- most people meet... (Laughter) LIMBAUGH: What is so funny? (Laughter) LIMBAUGH: What's going on out there that I don't know. Is some sexual harassment going on in the audience? (Laughter) LIMBAUGH: Most people meet their mates at work. And in order to do that, you generally -- I don't know if this has changed -- but you generally have to ask somebody out on a <head>date</head>. And you know, that can get you in jail these days -- or at least it can get you sued. Maybe you can get thrown out of school -- or at least your workplace. So the question came up: how do you flirt in the office today? Then another question came up after that: is -- and it's Michael Crichton's new book -- oh, and the feminists are mad about this. Gloria Allred is livid that he would write a book with -- with
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="61">
<answer instance="61" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
thinking about it. " The guys couldn't look at one another. They often debated about what system was in place for hiring some of the braindead people in those network jobs, and the three of them had wasted a lot of writing time laughing for hours about the idiotic things the " suit guys " said in meetings. This man was the lowest of them all. " What can he be thinking? " Harvey said, taking another P88 French fry from Bruno's plate. " That one of the girls would actually willingly go on a <head>date</head> with him? Touch him? A ladies'. man, " he laughed. " His poor date wouldn't know if he was having an orgasm or a seizure, " David said, and that got a big, nasty laugh out of Harvey. " Hey, Dave. Too bad your jokes aren't that funny on the show. If they were, maybe it'd get picked up for next season. As it is, " he said, then moved his hand from side to
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="62">
<answer instance="62" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
Little Star, " the song sounding so eerie now, when Karen turns the knob, filling the empty crib and seeping through its slats to echo through the house. When they finally make love again, five months later, she starts crying and when he asks if he should stop, she says, " What do you think? " A line comes to run down the middle of their bed. Neither of them crosses it. He can't remember if they were having problems before. He tries to remember the last time they went on a <head>date</head> -- a real date, without their son -- white linen, lit candles, wine in goblets, their feet touching beneath the table -- and can't. He tries to remember the last time he bought her jewelry or flowers. He tries to remember the last time she took him in her mouth. He tries to remember the last time they read novels on the couch, their legs intertwined, sharing favorite passages. Years. It's been years, hasn't it? So much of his
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="63">
<answer instance="63" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
Come over here, so you won't have to shout, " said the man. # That is how I first came to know the man and his dog. They were from Connecticut. It'd been a long time since I'd been to Connecticut. When I thought of Connecticut, I thought of the woods and pine needle floors and muddy streams with skinny, silver-colored minnows. # " You wouldn't know it anymore, " said the man mournfully. " It's all urbanized and squalid. " # That night we went on a <head>date</head>, and the dog came along. " I just can't leave him at the motel, " said the man. I refrained from wearing Ma Griffe and prayed my underarm deodorant (slightly scented) would not set off the dog. # We went to a restaurant several blocks from the ocean where all the personnel wore lederhosen and Tyrolean hats. Our table had an absurd centerpiece which consisted of a rubber mermaid trapped in an oblong of frozen plastic, adorned with snakes and roses. # " That
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="64">
<answer instance="64" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
him? I haven't seen him in an age. I guess he does his trading on weekends, and that's when I stay out of the stores. " Trading: she thought Littleton might still use that old-fashioned word. Maybe he still lived on the farm, maybe he worked in the mill or the furniture plant: that was how little she'd kept up with him. " He could sure play the banjo, " Nell said dreamily. " Had about one lesson in his life, I bet. Once I was out on a <head>date</head> with somebody kin to him, and we stopped by his house and he was out on the front porch, sitting on the floor with that banjo. He showed me how to play it, right then and there. " Roberta had never heard that before. That was no surprise; probably there were other things she hadn't heard from, their high-school days, back when her sister was still boy-crazy Wynell. They drove out to Littleton Doby's in Nell's convertible. " Why are we
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="65">
<answer instance="65" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
. So husbands and wives at this point in their lives are often moving in different directions. As a result, the time is ripe for infidelity and breakup. " At precisely the time when men are desiring more attention and respect, their partners are typically giving them less, " Diamond explains. " So they often find a younger woman who can supply that. " Don't be fooled. Trophy wives put us on the mantel. # My Crisis Moment: I've been married for 18 years, which means I haven't been on a <head>date</head> with a woman other than my wife since the Carter administration. But in my mind, I'm still as smooth as silk (or at least polyester). Jennifer is a 24-year-old, blue-eyed blonde who nannies for a friend. She's aware that I'm married, but she agreed to go out with me for the sake of journalistic research and getting her picture in Men's Health. The night before our " date, " I trimmed my ear hair and watched 2 hours of MTV.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="66">
<answer instance="66" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
're even meaner than the art critic from the Times. She said she thought I went to IKEA to pick up some cheap wineglasses, and when I was looking at their display modules, decided to duplicate one and call it art. " My face fell. " Oh. Shit. You're not... " " I am, " he admitted with a glint in his eye. I let my shoulders fall. " I'm so screwed. " " I would love to take you up on that, but unfortunately I'm here on a <head>date</head>, " the man told me flirtatiously. Then he flashed me a sexy smile as he put out his hand. " Scott James. " I reluctantly put out my hand as I tried to figure out a way to apologize. " Seema Singh. " Scott cocked his head. " Seema Singh? How do you have a Northern Indian first name and a Southern Indian last name? " I was impressed. Not only that he knew that I was Indian (you'd be amazed how many
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="67">
<answer instance="67" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
favorite picture of my parents is the February photo in the 2006 annual King Center calendar. She died on January 30, 2006, and when we flipped the calendar on February 1, the picture was of her kissing my father. His eyes are dreamy, as if he were welcoming her in heaven. My mother picked the pictures as if she knew she would see him soon. # I have seen God' s amazing ways of blessing us many times and am open to meeting my future husband in a nontraditional way. I even once went on a <head>date</head> with a man I had spotted in the pages of ESSENCE. It has been quite a journey and I have faith my own king will show up at the appointed time. # *Subject' s name has been changed
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="68">
<answer instance="68" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
to my face.' He hit pretty deep with me. He gave me hope with everything I was going through. " Afterward she sent him a Facebook message: " I was so glad to meet you today. " He didn't respond. Two months later a nurse urged her to try again. " I texted him around 6 p.m. We kept texting until 4 a.m., " talking about their children, music and what had happened to them. Two weeks later, she sent another text: " I want to go out on a <head>date</head>. " # He accepted, but only to let her down gently. He was done with love. He describes his childhood as violent and chaotic, turning him into an angry teen who got into scrapes with the law. His first marriage quickly went down the tubes. He was finally getting over a nasty custody battle over the one bright spot in his life, his daughter Scarlette, now 6. " I was sick of the drama and the BS. I did not want a relationship.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="69">
<answer instance="69" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
the street, with his notorious lack of delicacy, calls them lies.' The point is that the feminist, who in her hatred of patriarchy starts from this basic proposition, feels justified in choosing to entertain any fiction at all which will dramatize true consciousness. # It is along these lines that we discover an important but little-noticed convergence between radical feminism and Islamic fundamentalism. By campaigning against the thing called date rape,' the feminist creates immense hatred and suspicion between men and women, so that the feminist advice to any woman going out on a <head>date</head> is to establish a virtual contract governing what will happen in the course of an evening. This is to destroy the free and easy relations between men and women which have long characterized the Western world -- and only the Western world. It parallels the fundamentalist campaign to restore the old ways in the Islamic world. It is a well known fact,' as a Jordanian member of parliament recently remarked, that putting men and women in the same room is like mixing benzine and fire.' Back to
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="70">
<answer instance="70" senseid="A meeting between a couple"/>
<context>
a woman takes off her shoes when she comes to my house. Bare feet-clean bare feet-are sexy. It also shows a certain abandon. " -David, 31 11 Notice other women. I went out with a girl who used to compliment other girls on their shoes or whatever. Or she'd lean in to me and whisper in my ear that she thought another girl was really pretty. It showed me that she was secure about herself and her looks. " -Andy, 29 12 " Surprise me with your secret sexy side. I went on a <head>date</head> with a woman who wore this big, fluffy sweater, which made her look innocent. But during dinner, she said she was hot and pulled it off to reveal this tight tank top. She was hot all right-I almost choked on my clam chowder. " -Thomas, 26 13 " LOOK INTO MY EYES A LITTLE LONGER THAN USUAL. IT SHOWS CONFIDENCE. " -Bryan, 28 14 " Kiss me first. The only reason I'm not kissing you is that I'm afraid you may back away
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="71">
<answer instance="71" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
a high fatality rate. Subsequently, NiV emerged as a major public health problem in Bangladesh and India (7-9). # The natural reservoir of both viruses is pteropid bats, which harbor the viruses but do not show clinical illness (3). Virus transmission from bats to domestic animals is thought to be through pasture or feed contaminated by bat urine, feces, or other excretions (10). Transmission of HeV to humans has been invariably associated with close contact with ill horses (4), and transmission of NiV in Bangladesh is mainly through <head>date</head> palm sap contaminated with bat secretions (11). Human-to-human transmission of NiV also occurs (12, 13). # The Study # On April 2, 2014, the Philippine National Epidemiology Center received a report of human deaths in 2 villages, Tinalon and Midtungok, in the municipality of Senator Ninoy Aquino, province of Sultan Kudarat, island of Mindanao. The villages are? 15 km apart, and the provincial referral hospital is in Isulan, 80 km away. An outbreak investigation led by the
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="72">
<answer instance="72" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
derelicts who write in to this page, and tell the world that your full name is Richard Whittenstall Flat 6 Dascombe Mansions Cheveley Road Manchester M0 7RD That's dealt with that little problem. MATURE AGONY AUNT seeks uncomplicated relationship with anyone male or female, age unimportant, everything unimportant, but please no critics. I have recently lost my job, so please no critics. I just can't take it right now. Box B35467. # Frazzled on Mahe Island # 1 So it was a toss-up between this one #' A sweeping white beach fringed with <head>date</head> palms and oleanders... a sea so blue, you'll think it was made in Heaven... luxury five-star accommodation, with a bar that reaches down to the water's edge, and an internationally-famed restaurant where the food is as sensational as the setting... Sounds too good to be true? Think again! This fabulous resort, a mere twenty minutes from the recently-opened Holdana International Airport, offers you everything you could want from a holiday -- and more! As well as beautiful surroundings, it has everything
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="73">
<answer instance="73" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
Ferrand dry curacao rinse. The craft beer list is also solid, with local beers dominating the drafts, although there are noteworthy imports such as Hitachino Nest White Ale ($14) by the bottle. Speaking of a stop-by, the Commoner offers desserts worthy of a visit. I especially love the spin on the Pittsburgh cookie table ($13) -- a grand presentation with terrific selections from almond brittle to toffee bits and peanut butter cookies, although it changes daily. The sticky toffee pudding ($8) is also memorable, served in a bowl with <head>date</head> cake, toffee sauce and rye vanilla ice cream. Because it's still new, the Commoner faces a few glitches, most of them having to do with the service. Sometimes, bartenders and servers are too familiar, offering unsolicited information about their personal lives or addressing a group of business women as " girls. " Yes, training nearly 50 front-of-the-house-staff in a huge operation takes time. And with hope it will become more fluid and relaxed. Yet it's worth noting because it can make for some
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="74">
<answer instance="74" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
While this box huckleberry is still growing from its original seed-ling, there is a plant much older that has been revived by tissue culture: the narrow-leaved campion (Silene stenophylla). It was grown from still-living reproductive cells found in a specimen that died 32,000 years ago. " That's by far the oldest plant that's ever been grown from ancient tissue, " writes Nicholas Wade in The New York Times, describing the breakthrough by Russian scientists who used radiocarbon dating to pin-point its age. " The previous record was held by a <head>date</head> palm grown from a seed some 2,000 years old that was recovered from the ancient fortress of Masada in Israel. " # The reproductive cells survived for so long because an arctic ground squirrel stashed the campion in its burrow in northeastern Siberia when mammoths and woolly rhinoceros roamed the tundra. 
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="75">
<answer instance="75" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
the public about where we get the things we eat. As Ogden Nash once quipped, " It's a wise child that knows its fodder. " # 8283 BOOKSHELF # The Triumph of Seeds: How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History by Thor Hanson Basic Books, 2015; 304 pages, $26.99 # On Kibbutz Ketura, in the far south of Israel, there's a <head>date</head> palm named Methuselah that is one of the oldest organisms on Earth. While its species is aptly named Phoenix dactylifera, what makes this particular palm exceptional is that it was grown from a date excavated in the 1960s from the ruined fortress of Masada, overlooking the Dead Sea. Part of the larder ofjewish rebels who were besieged by the Romans, the date had lain undisturbed for 2,000 years in the rubble of a burned-out building, then for four more decades in a museum drawer, until it was replanted in
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="76">
<answer instance="76" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
this area. Dhakki is a local variety is extensively grown due to its attractive colour, high yielding, extra large size and keeping quality. Its yield is severely affected by natural way of pollination (Khan and Ghaffoor, 1993). Manual pollination is considered essential for commercial yield (Hussain et al. 1984) and it helps in improving the yield and quality (Beacher et al. 1999). Many factors are responsible for artificial pollination success (Atalla et al.1998). Amongst them pollination time is considered an important factor affecting fruit production of <head>date</head> palm as reported by various researchers (Khalifa et al. 1980; Elksas et al. 1996; Nasir et al. 1997; Iqbal et al. 2004 and Daud and Ahmed, 2008). Efficient pollination is localized with the period when pollen could fertilize the ovule. It depends upon the ovule longevity as well as on growth speed of pollen tube. Pollen grains germination is closely related with environmental factor and stigma receptivity (Ruther and Crawford, 1964). The pollen tube germination depends upon temperature,
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="77">
<answer instance="77" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
# No neighborhood is safe - his knocks on familiar doors are now answered by strangers, and at least 12 of his gardening friends have been killed. # He's sure that many of his longtime customers have been forced from their homes or were killed in sectarian battles, but he knows better than to ask questions. He has a job to do. # " I'm like a taxi driver. I pick up customers wherever I can, " he said with a chuckle. # Through war, occupation, bombings and neglect, the Iraqi <head>date</head> palm has endured. Farmers on these lands have cultivated dates since the ancient times of Mesopotamia, and artists through the centuries have celebrated the palm tree's resilience and bounty. Iraqis still use every part, weaving rope from the fibers and baskets from the fronds, exhibiting a tenderness toward the trees that's incongruous with the harshness of everyday life. # " The blessed tree, " Kadhim calls it, with reverence.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="78">
<answer instance="78" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
 Farmers on these lands have cultivated dates since the ancient times of Mesopotamia, and artists through the centuries have celebrated the palm tree's resilience and bounty. Iraqis still use every part, weaving rope from the fibers and baskets from the fronds, exhibiting a tenderness toward the trees that's incongruous with the harshness of everyday life. # " The blessed tree, " Kadhim calls it, with reverence. But the <head>date</head> palm, like the country it symbolizes, has fallen on hard times. # In Iraq's date-production heyday, official estimates put the number of palm trees at 30 million, but decades of war and water salinity have cut that figure so dramatically that the United Nations agriculture mission considers date-palm rehabilitation an urgent national priority. # It would take armies of gardeners to revive the industry, and they'd have to be as skilled as Kadhim is, knowing how to pollinate, when to trim the leaves and the
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="79">
<answer instance="79" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
. # But she'd keep that to herself. Her father had always cautioned her and her sister about shedding tears for answered prayers. This stint in Iraq was what she'd wanted, and it was establishing her as a prime-time contender right alongside all the big boys -- the older anchors who'd cemented their careers covering battlefields and the world's hotspots. # But I won't miss it -- and I damn well won't ever be able to forget it, she thought, gulping warm Gatorade as she leaned into the meager shade of a <head>date</head> palm. She'd miss Rusty, though. Having been in Baghdad a full month before Dana had arrived, her cameraman was leaving in the morning for two weeks R & R stateside. # " Done! Let's get outta here. " Rusty slammed the trunk of the armored car. She knew he was already halfway home, envisioning his reunion with his wife and kids back in Connecticut. # After Baghdad, American suburbia would be paradise. # " Coming. " She pushed herself away from
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="80">
<answer instance="80" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
of them looks like Clark Gable in The Misfits, while the other bears a striking resemblance to Jack Palance in Man in the Attic. # " Big deal, so there's no date, " says Dwaine. " A contract's a contract. " # " Tell that to Dexter Groon, " I say, " and he'll laugh in your face. " # 12. # With quarters liberated from Archibald's dresser top we ride the bus to Venice Beach, where Dwaine leaves me lying in a patch of wet grass under a <head>date</head> palm, gazing up through its fronds at the cloud-stuffed sky as people zip by on roller skates. A common housefly lands on my arm. It amazes and disappoints me to see a common housefly in California. A half hour later Dwaine returns. He doesn't look triumphant. # " I showed Groon the contract, " he says. # " And? " # " He laughed in my face. " # 13. # Back at the Montecido, Archibald sits up in bed watching a special
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="81">
<answer instance="81" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
And maybe six months ago, I was pretty much at the end of my rope. ROBERTSON (on camera): At the worst of times, Captain Toon and his men sustained serious attacks on 11 consecutive nights. Now, they say, they haven't had a serious attack in almost two months TOON There was a lot of insurgent activity out here. This was their safe haven, their base of operations. ROBERTSON (voice-over): It was to be here Toon's commanders would strike back, shelling Buritz's fertile <head>date</head> palm grove, hitting where it really hurts -- the town's pocketbook. The farmers quickly got the message TOON Finally, they had, had enough. And instead of coming against us and fighting us harder, they realized the culprit or the person -- the people that were causing their family's heartache and turmoil were the insurgency that were in this village and they ran them out ROBERTSON In a town center tea shop, residents, many of whom who've been detained by Toon and his men, are
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="82">
<answer instance="82" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
Backyards of British migrants were more diverse than were those of the Macedonians or Vietnamese. Sixty percent of the British gardens contained flowers, most frequently geraniums, agapanthus, and impatiens. Color was important in discussions of flowers. Shrub-and-tree layers combined natives (most commonly gum tree, native daphne, and tea tree) and non-natives (camellia, jacaranda, frangipani, hibiscus) and palms (mainly cocos palm or <head>date</head> palm, with some native bangalows). Fruit trees were primarily citrus (lemon, lime, orange) and stone fruit (peach, plum, nectarine). In comparison with all of the other groups, British-born participants grew the fewest fruit trees in their backyards, and the emphasis on citrus usually translated to a single tree, most frequently a lemon tree.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="83">
<answer instance="83" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
Date palm is cultivated in arid and semi-arid regions which are characterised by long and hot summers, no (or at most low) rainfall, and very low relative humidity level during the ripening period. Exceptional high temperatures ( 56C) are well endured by a <head>date</head> palm for several days under irrigation. During winters, temperatures below 0C are also endured. The zero vegetation point of a date palm is 7C, above this level growth is active and reaches its optimum at about 32C; the growth will continue at a stable rate until the temperature reaches 38C/40C when it will start decreasing.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="84">
<answer instance="84" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
but benefits the soils of the plantations by lessivating the deposited surface salt and avoiding the upward movement of salt from lower layers. Table 26 shows that the main <head>date</head>-growing regions are almost rainless until November. In these countries harvest begins mid August until the end of October. Rain during the flowering and harvest season is likely to cause some damage to the fruits.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="85">
<answer instance="85" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
Wind is, however, a carrier of dust and sand that adheres to the <head>date</head> fruits in their soft stage (Rutab and Tamar). When the fruits are at their early development stage (green/Habakouk), nearly black-indurated patches are sometimes seen on the fruit because of the wind beating the tender fruits against the hard fronds. Recently planted small offshoots can, however, easily be uprooted by strong winds.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="86">
<answer instance="86" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
Table 16 reflects five-year averages of date imports (gross) for selected countries since 1961. The main importers are India, the United Arab Emirates (UAE) and Europe. The top five countries to import <head>date</head>s during 1996-2000 were India, Pakistan, Malaysia, the United Arab Emirates and the European Community. For the five-year period 1996 to 2000 India imported on average 213 000 tonnes while the UAE imported 139 000 tonnes, accounting for 28 percent of the import market.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="87">
<answer instance="87" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
And when she was asked to plant the seed, make it grow, she sort of laughed a little bit and said, Well, I'll give it a shot, but I don't hold out much hope.' CHADWICK: So... FLATOW: And then you have the story on another level, like the history of the seed that surrounds it, and that's quite interesting. These seeds are <head>date</head> palm seeds which were unearthed by an archaeologist at King Herod's palace at Masada. And think about it: Sometime 2,000 years ago someone was eating the dates, they spit out the seeds and there they sat in that ruin for two millennia.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="88">
<answer instance="88" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
The palm sap then collects in the vessel and is harvested in the early morning hours. If a few drops of lime juice are added to the palm sap, fermentation can be stopped and the sap can then be boiled to form palm syrup, palm sugar, jaggery and numerous other edible products derived from the syrup. In India and Pakistan, North Africa, Ghana, and Ivory Coast, <head>date</head> palms are tapped for the sweet sap, which is converted into palm sugar (known as jaggery or gur), molasses or alcoholic beverages. In North Africa the sap obtained from tapping palm trees is known as lgb. If left for a sufficient period of time (typically hours, depending on the temperature) lgb easily becomes an alcoholic drink.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="89">
<answer instance="89" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
Deglet Noor (Algerian Arabic:   ) so named because the centre appears light or golden when held up to the sun. This is a leading <head>date</head> in Libya, Algeria, the United States, and Tunisia, in the latter it is grown in inland oases and is the chief export cultivar. Its texture is semi-dry and is not very sweet.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="90">
<answer instance="90" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
center of this garden, in its own niche within the fountain of Paradise, perches the very embodiment of mystery and evil: an owl. 57 Less threatening but exotic animals in the landscape derive from authoritative period " documentation " of " the East ": the giraffe, elephant, and " kangaroo " are copied from Bernhard von Breydenbach's illustrated guide to the Holy Land of 1486 and the exotic " East. " 58 The viewer can make a clear distinction in the arbor of the Garden of Eden between the three choices of trees: a standard <head>date</head> palm in the upper right, a more conventional apple tree behind the main figures, and, beside Adam, a " dragon tree, " also taken from German graphic sources (including Martin Schongauer and Albrecht Drer as well as woodcuts of Paradise in the 1493 Nuremberg Chronicle) to signify the (other) forbidden tree of eternal life, as described in Genesis 2:9: " And out of the ground the Lord God made to grow every tree that is pleasant to the sight and good for food, the
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="91">
<answer instance="91" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
New commercial properties are banned from using ornamental grass. The median down the Las Vegas Strip, in fact, is made of synthetic turf. # As Kern drives, he keeps his eyes on the gutters. When he sees water, he follows it to its source. We track one rivulet to a single-story home made of pink stucco. There's a <head>date</head> palm in the front yard, but the rest is all flat, green grass. This is the wrong day for watering, but the sprinklers are going full force, with misdirected nozzles spraying directly onto the sidewalk. Kern jumps out of the truck with a clipboard and video camera and documents the scene.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="92">
<answer instance="92" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
I broke with my party in order to balance the budget, and Ronald Reagan signed into law the tax cut that we voted for. I voted for I.R.A. tax cuts. I voted for smallbusiness tax cuts. " (pg. A19) 5254 # TEN minutes outside the red clay walls of this 950-year-old city, an asphalt avenue abruptly gives way to rutted dirt. Dusty goats saunter by, and a <head>date</head> palm grows inconveniently in the middle of the narrow road like a giant feather duster. Houses hunker down amid hills of cactus. Don't be fooled by the apparent desolation. Here in the Palmeraie, a date-palm forest of nearly 30,000 acres that has become a blue-chip suburb, is the latest evidence that a new generation of designers is teaching old Marrakesh new tricks.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="93">
<answer instance="93" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
her mother, Rina. " Otherwise, she is extremely talkative. " # May 25 was also 54-year-old Bishnu Pradhan's " third birthday ": " This is my new life, " said the secretary of the Dishari Farmers Club, a voluntary organization that helps people procure government loans. " I was reborn on May 25, 2009. " # That was the day that Cyclone Aila unleashed its fury on this tidal country. Around the same time that Ayantika was born on the first floor of her neighbor's house, Mr. Pradhan was atop a <head>date</head> palm tree, along with a snake and a hen, after being flung there by the force of the flood waters that had broken through embankments and submerged the village."
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="94">
<answer instance="94" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
It took a moment in the servant's case, but then Hanani at last saw recognition flow across her face. Only then did she add, " I'm Hanani, an apprentice of the Sharer path. " # The servant finally remembered her manners and bobbed her head. " Please come inside, Sharer-Apprentice. " # The house, when they entered its foyer, was far cooler and more comfortable than the late-afternoon swelter without. The foyer opened directly into the family's modest atrium, where small shrubs and plants surrounded a handsome, good-sized <head>date</head> palm. The tree's canopy kept the atrium in striped shade. Beneath this tree, a nest of cushions and blankets had been built. Here reclined a heavyset, graying woman in a deep indigo Kisuati wrap. Her face, Hanani saw when the servant girl went to speak to her, was lined and puffy, the whites of her eyes red from weeping. But they fixed keenly on Hanani while the servant spoke, and after a moment the woman beckoned Hanani over. # Hanani came into the
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="95">
<answer instance="95" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
As far as the time of birth of Jesus is concerned the only hint we get is from the truest testament. It tells us that it was not in cold weather like that of December. Jesus was born under a <head>date</head> tree and certainly in absolute seclution and out of town.What the Europeans have been celebrating since centuries is in fact Odinmas. In other words they would celebrate this festival as they do today to venerate their Pagan god Odin.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="96">
<answer instance="96" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
At $27, the duck flirting with Middle Eastern flavours - the sticky, pull-apart braised leg sitting on a puck of cracked wheat has hints of orange and star anise, coriander and cumin seeds - also gets a tick in the value stakes. It's the attention to detail that makes this food standout: the smooth, not too sweet <head>date</head> puree; the orange zest kicker. A warm, comforting prune and walnut frangipane with poached quince arrives cloaked in almond milk froth - very cheffy - although the toasted honey and walnut ice-cream is from Gundowring.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="97">
<answer instance="97" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
Finally, our staple biryani has a competition. Kerala biryani or the kalam biriyani is here. Those you didn't appreciate the spice and the absence of sweet in the Hyderabadi biryani, Kerala biryani at KK is here to meet those demands. The sweet biryani is a good break which is served with a sweet <head>date</head> pickle, a hat mango pickle and some raita. With two separate kitchens for veg and non-veg cooking there is no reason why pure vegetarians' can frequent this place.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="98">
<answer instance="98" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
It was hot and except for the people in Medina, the rest of the people there generally possessed a disorienting hardness about them. In a way, this can be strangely charming. On the other hand, our experience at the <head>date</head> plantation showed me a different side. It was calming and reminded me of those romantic poems written by Arab poets. I would love to see more of that side of the country.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="99">
<answer instance="99" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
Polat Nasibullah, a 24-year-old cyclist, arrived in Medina two days ago en route to the holy city of Mecca to perform the Hajj ritual. Cycling some 6,600 kilometers from his native Russia, Nasibullah was greeted by Saudi boy scouts who presented him with <head>date</head>s -- for which Medina is famous -- along with sweets and water. Nasibullah arrived in the city only days after the arrival in Mecca of Mohamed Bamachan, a Chinese national who also traveled to Saudi Arabia from his home country -- a four-month journey -- by bicycle.
</context>
</instance>
<instance id="100">
<answer instance="100" senseid="A fruit that grows on palm trees"/>
<context>
You can continue with your eight-glasses-of-water-a-day routine throughout the night, in order to stay hydrated during the hot summer days. After breaking your fast with <head>date</head>s or water, try having a bowl of soup or salad before munching on your main course. A warm bowl of soup comforts your stomach with fluids and prepares the digestive system for your meal. Take a break if you feel full after that since overeating may cause stomach pain and bloating.
</context>
</instance>
</lexelt>
</corpus>
